{
  "1": {
    "question": "2132445322342511433225143",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "2533121235131244235344412",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "3145454311221451133142513",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "3513453441345111321341324",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "5423242313154214134234454",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "5132442524132452312315414",
    "answer": "wwwwbbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "1124311544422353441424351",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "3422142413153424323523113",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "3231443421451312425421445",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "1141214235531431341345321",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "1413213254233243124544514",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "5432313342352143134442531",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "4453324125214525232115234",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "1331232411521344125321315",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "1251231445541323533323451",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "2344352314444244513223425",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "4424342235453142145243241",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "3322551332242532531431543",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "3155114324421555311234251",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "4321441324122523124144131",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "3531253534144255323142154",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "4134153421113514524323135",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "23": {
    "question": "4245141514142354531453122",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "24": {
    "question": "4324121243431321432142214",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "25": {
    "question": "4453135423221543424553242",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "26": {
    "question": "4453154243143221325435411",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "27": {
    "question": "1134343321112331415332425",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "28": {
    "question": "3123532251334321522444131",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "29": {
    "question": "1213315424314124221344531",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "30": {
    "question": "3543333254242343354252331",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "31": {
    "question": "4233545121212522432123212",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "32": {
    "question": "2245243155322431453254224",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "33": {
    "question": "4513211345312225424323453",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "34": {
    "question": "1341115442325114411311235",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "35": {
    "question": "3242152312112151352123143",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "36": {
    "question": "1524421124125135432123154",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "37": {
    "question": "3435112544311454212413412",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "38": {
    "question": "3554341215543251241323534",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "39": {
    "question": "3153125344321533143553242",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "40": {
    "question": "2451455124151452543141254",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "41": {
    "question": "1452341145534142533121442",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "42": {
    "question": "1242112354245231543231241",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "43": {
    "question": "5335314235512435312335442",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "44": {
    "question": "3324435121431355134144413",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "45": {
    "question": "4455121435145235414435414",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "46": {
    "question": "1341234221325243123525441",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "47": {
    "question": "1424523154543131234332423",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "48": {
    "question": "4124445323443411354233125",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "49": {
    "question": "2445112315315145132322132",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "50": {
    "question": "1133434352534314231225243",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "51": {
    "question": "4331212341351141225221432",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "52": {
    "question": "2543152442112542233534514",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "53": {
    "question": "5341441315233521523433511",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "54": {
    "question": "1123442115354111454234134",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "55": {
    "question": "3422553212322414413241351",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "56": {
    "question": "1332425124133523422512531",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "57": {
    "question": "3124113524433241412552413",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "58": {
    "question": "2314545233233522152452332",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "59": {
    "question": "5313143511453141235311145",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "60": {
    "question": "1353125431132253413253214",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "61": {
    "question": "4543342351344233254353144",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "62": {
    "question": "1452325122311532441552311",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "63": {
    "question": "5423234521144333531223135",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "64": {
    "question": "3331451423453422454131122",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "65": {
    "question": "1251123451115323451243123",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "66": {
    "question": "3542144534413125431313144",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "67": {
    "question": "3125123111513424251445122",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "68": {
    "question": "3351345121121251325151342",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "69": {
    "question": "4242524253412441532441522",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "70": {
    "question": "3511213253242351254453323",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "71": {
    "question": "4312324541322143322513452",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "72": {
    "question": "3321415434343153132232153",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "73": {
    "question": "5242212534322414345135121",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "74": {
    "question": "4312412253454122142232341",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "75": {
    "question": "2512315423213455422422532",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "76": {
    "question": "5244144123343422351321445",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "77": {
    "question": "1354134245141535143221341",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "78": {
    "question": "5331411413132354513234544",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "79": {
    "question": "3534242135234355423312524",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "80": {
    "question": "4325131415232131334252131",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "81": {
    "question": "3514213254321353451131252",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "82": {
    "question": "1225224533321423134445431",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "83": {
    "question": "4325434345215343521212133",
    "answer": "wwwwbbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "84": {
    "question": "1122424151412155231135434",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "85": {
    "question": "2331124152512421243533423",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "86": {
    "question": "1533224321544131124513121",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "87": {
    "question": "2344315324221431153334151",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "88": {
    "question": "2523245153131245134235224",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "89": {
    "question": "4132353144243111123433411",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "90": {
    "question": "2331314225253414352121253",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "91": {
    "question": "2134145213122343535253421",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "92": {
    "question": "4324534523223433225431434",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "93": {
    "question": "3342521231513424411332414",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "94": {
    "question": "1214131124451343345154223",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "95": {
    "question": "4352433135241514521354433",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "96": {
    "question": "1135215341123345321343121",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "97": {
    "question": "1143451243345443312445412",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "98": {
    "question": "4121543124233213541432343",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "99": {
    "question": "3145313444521323251215124",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "100": {
    "question": "2212412245514233421141351",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "101": {
    "question": "2422523154442414251451233",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "102": {
    "question": "1543231225145212231424123",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "103": {
    "question": "1511334412313241314312435",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "104": {
    "question": "4544143524122435431241233",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "105": {
    "question": "4421332411412353334121354",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "106": {
    "question": "1122342351341132354225413",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "107": {
    "question": "2135223541151255234335212",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "108": {
    "question": "1352141213134455243114253",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "109": {
    "question": "2253414453214431523154223",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "110": {
    "question": "4353433415251345533224253",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "111": {
    "question": "1235123431331353154144113",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "112": {
    "question": "2412132452135241234245211",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbbwwbwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "113": {
    "question": "1525341532544242431545232",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "114": {
    "question": "2411453421132133431441452",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "115": {
    "question": "2421111435152411322442513",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "116": {
    "question": "3124254324451313344124153",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwwwwbwbbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "117": {
    "question": "5112322542411522531112231",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "118": {
    "question": "3145121551454231223552341",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "119": {
    "question": "5134333351351324451214335",
    "answer": "wwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "120": {
    "question": "2214525113513314152314422",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "121": {
    "question": "4112252313314531314114215",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "122": {
    "question": "2152545212335423452132351",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "123": {
    "question": "3431115243212244332512441",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "124": {
    "question": "2453133242424534321253322",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwwbbwwwwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "125": {
    "question": "3513114324222544251353132",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "126": {
    "question": "2135125231544122214114223",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "127": {
    "question": "2135152333152434142443312",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "128": {
    "question": "4122245413532111153314152",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "129": {
    "question": "4145152124354112132533541",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "130": {
    "question": "4522321433321414413223315",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "131": {
    "question": "1531232115312311325454443",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "132": {
    "question": "1413241421214315321442144",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "133": {
    "question": "1342313254351121233324315",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "134": {
    "question": "4212511123143323524113111",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "135": {
    "question": "1452443235134512531412333",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "136": {
    "question": "1531412133541423451113252",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "137": {
    "question": "5421231314125423541142121",
    "answer": "wwwwbbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "138": {
    "question": "2341215432413533532552341",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "139": {
    "question": "3232113225251345421424542",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "140": {
    "question": "2512423531111324233512252",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "141": {
    "question": "1523354321454154153212534",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "142": {
    "question": "1552232153445212153543211",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "143": {
    "question": "4425451442144342341542122",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "144": {
    "question": "5434341245324511252435143",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "145": {
    "question": "1242441332224412514452213",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "146": {
    "question": "4434525341435113235443423",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "147": {
    "question": "4331441235153225214412352",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "148": {
    "question": "4231213245125142523414113",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "149": {
    "question": "2521412423315312311551321",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "150": {
    "question": "1313221345135441415152412",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "151": {
    "question": "4353251224154133412243243",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "152": {
    "question": "2124352334324222313511532",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "153": {
    "question": "2144525122431212423352114",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "154": {
    "question": "5131243521344152415135233",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "155": {
    "question": "2154333441242344325253312",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "156": {
    "question": "1325234112453435243133212",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "157": {
    "question": "4324445321132452421351131",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "158": {
    "question": "5432135334214152311412541",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "159": {
    "question": "4142323123342511252422312",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "160": {
    "question": "1412122154352114353132423",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "161": {
    "question": "1342121541321343415245431",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "162": {
    "question": "1522232451212355314422214",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "163": {
    "question": "4431223543343353244153122",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "164": {
    "question": "1425141521254125211411123",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "165": {
    "question": "3242114132412212352412345",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "166": {
    "question": "1524321154511331432322313",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "167": {
    "question": "2312445123121451424131452",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "168": {
    "question": "4152123414442312215215242",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "169": {
    "question": "2512124154324325331431342",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "170": {
    "question": "5214132524214234213525324",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "171": {
    "question": "4342334154211331434545212",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "172": {
    "question": "2514242254243351253452422",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "173": {
    "question": "5221142541451322115324335",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "174": {
    "question": "1212414542341241523121152",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "175": {
    "question": "1544441425511342351341231",
    "answer": "wwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "176": {
    "question": "3414223441113341534241513",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "177": {
    "question": "4353221243352223232424135",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "178": {
    "question": "4354313352342214214335214",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "179": {
    "question": "3212124213432541343531334",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "180": {
    "question": "1521221543534431423534144",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "181": {
    "question": "3342552134153332435243112",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "182": {
    "question": "4213153241432131532433414",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "183": {
    "question": "2132514152531142512312531",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "184": {
    "question": "3115435142542243352314435",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "185": {
    "question": "3145425242231444151224321",
    "answer": "wwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "186": {
    "question": "2344133514213453513314251",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "187": {
    "question": "1342341354325423523152441",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "188": {
    "question": "3413421433254121353452241",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "189": {
    "question": "4351422415233515124145224",
    "answer": "wwwwbbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "190": {
    "question": "2243131243124352512424452",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "191": {
    "question": "5312334245133544321425433",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "192": {
    "question": "5121241235115422341145424",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "193": {
    "question": "2341132354513211354434435",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "194": {
    "question": "3115442132534134354113324",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 5
  },
  "195": {
    "question": "2445234215211241354315113",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "196": {
    "question": "5321431312121333452123113",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "197": {
    "question": "2253431141341231343222415",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 5
  },
  "198": {
    "question": "4321445113542413145222415",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 5
  },
  "199": {
    "question": "313264126335311541342633263154253124",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "200": {
    "question": "441361123545452123554624516535314215",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "201": {
    "question": "315326534544243615553334524531564251",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "202": {
    "question": "335214121545311125564231452113115354",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "203": {
    "question": "345513562321531454143422316145121534",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "204": {
    "question": "154256561424412465353124622541341623",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "205": {
    "question": "534653163512622245156423315214544116",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "206": {
    "question": "165232631125543111121526211453142334",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "207": {
    "question": "134245326152163414414323652421323643",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "208": {
    "question": "152414143126515334531343624135452455",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "209": {
    "question": "226345533256425635631124361452132523",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "210": {
    "question": "645315561555223146534123115463516552",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "211": {
    "question": "154611165243644355432351526231513364",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "212": {
    "question": "642312143561234621463435516442122156",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "213": {
    "question": "224133654513322463464332513241236122",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "214": {
    "question": "624231365253216244531326355641343262",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "215": {
    "question": "151463465134645341141625514226436522",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "216": {
    "question": "161531536515321145512655451126544261",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "217": {
    "question": "321532163425316534254631453216645441",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "218": {
    "question": "556443643252213316431624122524313462",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "219": {
    "question": "345436651442523214532614123563516434",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "220": {
    "question": "431636526142253665153632235211644351",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "221": {
    "question": "624513235165156331361421543632241311",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "222": {
    "question": "111352521644256223342225235434132346",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "223": {
    "question": "554136241652163515632425536321114562",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "224": {
    "question": "143121461352245451242513314225124236",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "225": {
    "question": "151122123456435564514425551254245513",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "226": {
    "question": "611432531343456323125562243136312215",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "227": {
    "question": "326534351532614525244263432116162412",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "228": {
    "question": "535141612454344655351162536114425316",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwbbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "229": {
    "question": "541216452345164425651452335241326154",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "230": {
    "question": "642653641312136425654313513231325162",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "231": {
    "question": "131544415443651324223146463112444653",
    "answer": "wwbwwbbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "232": {
    "question": "236415211654551462132442621351543516",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "233": {
    "question": "511521134226561445452362326143245331",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "234": {
    "question": "434654514264635431552116365242226413",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "235": {
    "question": "353452425563334526263345356524442634",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "236": {
    "question": "611532513236221354165123354112253615",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "237": {
    "question": "445334132564346432254213544631523246",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "238": {
    "question": "256231531343245361321516452621113423",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "239": {
    "question": "365214525261245351334521653152213635",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "240": {
    "question": "413442334541152324425335621253436425",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "241": {
    "question": "546333314356621534165123532642451363",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "242": {
    "question": "612543554414534652256144345561263324",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwbwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "243": {
    "question": "554614163425433511631432412155151264",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "244": {
    "question": "321451413465225154421342134546351613",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "245": {
    "question": "255215625411262152511321316145452562",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "246": {
    "question": "645125311162161515132256554611316235",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "247": {
    "question": "463352241531125643113433524416251362",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "248": {
    "question": "523634153146165443341215134562212413",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "249": {
    "question": "152345435251542136614511414312351624",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbbwbwbwwwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "250": {
    "question": "451236542233614325226124523464363142",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "251": {
    "question": "514413461235143262452431216642652154",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "252": {
    "question": "135452551524523214462151326541315635",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "253": {
    "question": "351354514362236242443615652434153546",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "254": {
    "question": "241236524361355123315345334412261433",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "255": {
    "question": "551643534123411355124451213164146214",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "256": {
    "question": "425512353526612354135531343241431465",
    "answer": "wwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "257": {
    "question": "325613153224243513361412113265234354",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "258": {
    "question": "635635624351453445236514561243355163",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "259": {
    "question": "613323326413165435434211342455153146",
    "answer": "wwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "260": {
    "question": "114252235162112136224341451424463215",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "261": {
    "question": "632324524361326244544643463512231533",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "262": {
    "question": "436123165244651141123456254463341632",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "263": {
    "question": "344261156435412353134523543114613343",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "264": {
    "question": "131524135253426314212416352641354142",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "265": {
    "question": "145421235541456142164214321364254352",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "266": {
    "question": "361445625221154623352211413522324154",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "267": {
    "question": "346524241353534413531463412635643531",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "268": {
    "question": "631154543265244255323416416225531342",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "269": {
    "question": "522643321451644112412265151356261542",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "270": {
    "question": "314565511336545624233144553341462314",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "271": {
    "question": "346335513624154362565123314156641215",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "272": {
    "question": "515144351412234124462531531563323124",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "273": {
    "question": "331213153362512642634521242316226635",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "274": {
    "question": "321565221435465311526423132451552441",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "275": {
    "question": "566424255326124653613524512165356231",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "276": {
    "question": "453633546512235461135224224435513321",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "277": {
    "question": "255135346321261235255346611432334614",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "278": {
    "question": "364114115432523314451216442363253645",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "279": {
    "question": "223116225431511613254216146152233523",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "280": {
    "question": "232652412526655345541163264155152615",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "281": {
    "question": "562121145346324254431435256531633515",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "282": {
    "question": "641322254223453261236243325416211645",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "283": {
    "question": "515331613512251311132364364123321351",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "284": {
    "question": "123126546432213615534421162353451464",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "285": {
    "question": "162543345312415331231644514426426112",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "286": {
    "question": "415433521614234221155341451235345136",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "287": {
    "question": "463465316512451434533121625331461453",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "288": {
    "question": "324231214426242165653332163524446555",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "289": {
    "question": "252346351624246531143464614513563145",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "290": {
    "question": "536315241645462454354231132426113444",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "291": {
    "question": "351144612521134654461434415163524213",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "292": {
    "question": "262442456213312434522331435624244146",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "293": {
    "question": "345331354155152146531332536214612454",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "294": {
    "question": "212315323154235261213266154623261233",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "295": {
    "question": "233211523141512425254535132564561255",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "296": {
    "question": "236451141263253421162232324615212336",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "297": {
    "question": "322314156534541132212453362521331444",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "298": {
    "question": "632234154622532166331162263415421343",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "299": {
    "question": "331254654122523423136241112135415322",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "300": {
    "question": "545462415233232541234546153624225443",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "301": {
    "question": "145162544331312516154424331452464211",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "302": {
    "question": "261142424256142563551652631621526314",
    "answer": "wwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "303": {
    "question": "243153516223221542363115135642251434",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "304": {
    "question": "132526621445153462562114435611244451",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "305": {
    "question": "342452241556432214526241415621122163",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "306": {
    "question": "142123253654164552251546315465446251",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "307": {
    "question": "136443634142313634362435443461351323",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "308": {
    "question": "413225225356635152352164331234246513",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "309": {
    "question": "451463424311623121135534315442524214",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "310": {
    "question": "532213231563413136223345654134335421",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "311": {
    "question": "351652246314413364543546164254615231",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "312": {
    "question": "341345426513534262253134452433645123",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "313": {
    "question": "241131235141451364426114641253263123",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "314": {
    "question": "112453434512231335446221354156125324",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "315": {
    "question": "314251523614365341435122351263622132",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "316": {
    "question": "213236344521456342624534362413244115",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "317": {
    "question": "331224215343655241365412142513221151",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "318": {
    "question": "133165512634553146623412346431461312",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "319": {
    "question": "431363216535642245561432145325134151",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "320": {
    "question": "651144416532413146235165442653365225",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "321": {
    "question": "215135634452113456415263561425251641",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "322": {
    "question": "146123354162545553462251253456221641",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "323": {
    "question": "213365356444534213463152112546241135",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "324": {
    "question": "324465342321163124534243445632156215",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "325": {
    "question": "133261322145511431361332641521215612",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "326": {
    "question": "461432324465513241535641143523512431",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "327": {
    "question": "551336165213211524543163644515235655",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "328": {
    "question": "422513234165433354364411541632151313",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "329": {
    "question": "252365642124435312114652562421136545",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "330": {
    "question": "124162463512115145635441541326125632",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "331": {
    "question": "244315562421424153315461253342431322",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "332": {
    "question": "461522346231532612651243154456215265",
    "answer": "wwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "333": {
    "question": "513461352144215414461525524453614531",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "334": {
    "question": "531325125534515432563331154212241153",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "335": {
    "question": "144235642313451364213426526335554641",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "336": {
    "question": "543215434451436543153343325564461431",
    "answer": "wwwwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "337": {
    "question": "421262264531432641653554542413155425",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "338": {
    "question": "463421232151216243641422442465324614",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "339": {
    "question": "356432234353541263132146224654613421",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "340": {
    "question": "452164316235633541511426262211325615",
    "answer": "wwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "341": {
    "question": "231652251143652555365421424465541212",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "342": {
    "question": "561452552443453165614532534544145321",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "343": {
    "question": "114243352311213456236221545622324163",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "344": {
    "question": "422613512226363524623123246151311461",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "345": {
    "question": "553116565452134621255114612445416532",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "346": {
    "question": "412536651322521415542154435265243625",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "347": {
    "question": "153154532316261531316241445532422652",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "348": {
    "question": "231263212536561323324251643122546212",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "349": {
    "question": "612432323212433521252614164153142363",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "350": {
    "question": "264134516541234625454256215362221353",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "351": {
    "question": "142352443421124435236143534514312234",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "352": {
    "question": "512632431353353241652513235344565425",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "353": {
    "question": "265451563124615524361226125463332613",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "354": {
    "question": "542516161554354132515233135425425651",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "355": {
    "question": "534121255623461152153413316145541354",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "356": {
    "question": "341553653514254151235226515643226135",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "357": {
    "question": "266345443112154534424561531124465215",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "358": {
    "question": "162625635142521624526514443656254314",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "359": {
    "question": "551135315216243451221242132564512623",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "360": {
    "question": "352345531236426121144361213254615411",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "361": {
    "question": "551421463215351643325134224563142116",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "362": {
    "question": "613111342651234421435132514563121315",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "363": {
    "question": "512241141265132614645134261423154321",
    "answer": "wwwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "364": {
    "question": "243144145366456512513653534241611533",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "365": {
    "question": "354161522342325314451251245526213455",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "366": {
    "question": "554331215326132614153415326152425563",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "367": {
    "question": "345631112315421563136514614455454116",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "368": {
    "question": "552154614425154155256341441512343316",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "369": {
    "question": "452623336354654531165324231163323146",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "370": {
    "question": "351321263511534546415253341655116535",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "371": {
    "question": "521335526524243651142535454263534532",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "372": {
    "question": "122463611322464215463516325144534653",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "373": {
    "question": "554136624321446512513654464155341625",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "374": {
    "question": "654143226545543414231654132433515362",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "375": {
    "question": "132561623421261133114245552623456311",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "376": {
    "question": "522324124536313164632452415225156241",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "377": {
    "question": "551336532641164533415136533152326435",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "378": {
    "question": "543243465221352412622551241615412563",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "379": {
    "question": "613552456421162415541635215463244253",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "380": {
    "question": "134631513546161323135262642123126154",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "381": {
    "question": "632123513424245364136152461435344556",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "382": {
    "question": "153542611334344156426515464534521461",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "383": {
    "question": "653141145161256414415256123654463335",
    "answer": "wwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "384": {
    "question": "623511615232132454542331611643364421",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "385": {
    "question": "152536433251521331315425354652215141",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "386": {
    "question": "411343236114441245161453224641453226",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "387": {
    "question": "133125641355153452216243364431352611",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "388": {
    "question": "315462521453623451244612152346515214",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "389": {
    "question": "165233523452624153333513251245156322",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "390": {
    "question": "255153546321251634213234324536155462",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "391": {
    "question": "241526163522454531225365436615226113",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 6
  },
  "392": {
    "question": "521423421645653142332146341561465513",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "393": {
    "question": "246244165432553364434156353254341621",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "394": {
    "question": "643221561352352256125633442253234165",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbbwbwbwwwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "395": {
    "question": "431416144135513264451145346551435311",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 6
  },
  "396": {
    "question": "564435343512516523331652435464652341",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwww",
    "size": 6
  },
  "397": {
    "question": "5876276614256834767315622381774462526173324854157647155661368727",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "398": {
    "question": "3648212681324576543583153725546456861624452376826874123145516843",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "399": {
    "question": "8512347348757126365343117681235437648521214151365416327515638445",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "400": {
    "question": "1314817481453633121852141753448543762351753734657631354252126257",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "401": {
    "question": "5717613383457142753415562747568517283364212318574672835133841445",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "402": {
    "question": "4468473521415368562485576537624178134324538716376435383612526482",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "403": {
    "question": "2576381668152676813474677661321433274658318617425413613346684325",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "404": {
    "question": "6128276557112482131658572251763426154578826772336832634764821352",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "405": {
    "question": "1527364357716218275658547243516283616761623675816182245541542315",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "406": {
    "question": "2682514312776852355716841752871671383455481347638466375345617578",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "407": {
    "question": "7485644343567615657132843168274782276353283614743741586242637736",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "408": {
    "question": "3518142718455627821661356354167351378762726578415721637412844453",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "409": {
    "question": "3412187163811732175625483843216772536324867466154626873154611241",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "410": {
    "question": "3455237676423682316877525686773525741866676284245317122872235614",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "411": {
    "question": "1674435166386735285414342356721574675142148465234215646745711875",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "412": {
    "question": "2782254555348521235174851465257844585173314736547514473264437245",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "413": {
    "question": "2241674771283534285225363764562144752258446261136513544224411385",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "414": {
    "question": "7738454656412753371254717425122181426252581371232375168545243113",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "415": {
    "question": "7218213485476326215117682361752754163877183372267582765324268713",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "416": {
    "question": "3633445541773825671156527462218262547238444587628323174678216271",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "417": {
    "question": "2536487136752235712565846348121654718623245131623285711627665347",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "418": {
    "question": "8112521413687242416468244723168554156367627541572531347638132751",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "419": {
    "question": "8546162327637438322831365131687448124352363475811672823344862775",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "420": {
    "question": "7483665516585674437385321256428348252721853216476127785632374718",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "421": {
    "question": "4742641811573263527716136884742121654377851237523641281528654737",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "422": {
    "question": "7561458647564422211478355567171412473153811265472372511264853171",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "423": {
    "question": "3625287551613182247845156246213434126753654723251523263778365764",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "424": {
    "question": "4118533246442541154762432774666572113584634548635431762877258476",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "425": {
    "question": "7554513551623428653247771386635444256731266383463272561387151365",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "426": {
    "question": "1521735641536178142238575685473273155612525614836623561568375145",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "427": {
    "question": "1163474235251834715863265451261331446287821411164372876522166456",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "428": {
    "question": "7662352144185732135742483764742582455467487353435477161377238455",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "429": {
    "question": "5137441417143468687361336681571575261346367225674563547223477852",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "430": {
    "question": "7524128367812536287723258142335763125741453738162152867562457668",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbbwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "431": {
    "question": "7251634875321224228624711852723633218675476831516543258516252723",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "432": {
    "question": "2336647765472648214277151768356454854621856243174673581272147323",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "433": {
    "question": "3137554345212374533267382717455278451234317621754326752112583765",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "434": {
    "question": "7634135815647363527581143441258228553761318716416418231515534846",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "435": {
    "question": "8316125476651426312548655318243248632574243561375472771852718145",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "436": {
    "question": "6144753817756743642647857516245326545173324348124737556125113644",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "437": {
    "question": "2278331566421713562422718253212621666487738161422417584117624238",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "438": {
    "question": "5251715324635481768233745626854635173852187223353415627885384324",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "439": {
    "question": "4837526731122836334866577524647867142583826347174446347215758374",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "440": {
    "question": "7413653111365327653821751762327812822456287411658715472532678614",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "441": {
    "question": "6517314824785414423671353853376353238271135215878766136474342852",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "442": {
    "question": "5437253647137862721614534632456861158272357362516628564785745725",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "443": {
    "question": "5814372878612512652817713281534781678256762521811432781557161131",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "444": {
    "question": "2737261168713552138626742654523137454187624667237312562847231855",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "445": {
    "question": "6541824377821754214734686114223713256765743653213842751627264175",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "446": {
    "question": "6254123684554167153224873813157171623528644183652372625137815646",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "447": {
    "question": "2467282335541362634726245841364666264135521365784176847713527384",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "448": {
    "question": "2547713625154372723354186626314113585364376715214184273347721585",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "449": {
    "question": "1378514264251847725742831163827238166325462443418541371633312528",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "450": {
    "question": "5174668653153746432846737712855371531448351132677467223728264514",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "451": {
    "question": "7866317585357461175426875127157857654824422517513671541224128346",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "452": {
    "question": "8122674473787632473636586327651446817327245347677215148765415876",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "453": {
    "question": "5863465477361845665284733564276177255414766243372147535813186161",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "454": {
    "question": "6865145712675134513445285687373225161374766341654758561483112241",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "455": {
    "question": "1186533746773524317241512168437553243783625281648551764667451773",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "456": {
    "question": "5862752424342154877546312587521673726613157524634213376854785371",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "457": {
    "question": "6724172536175647467178154472756376462168287741168165343257842231",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "458": {
    "question": "6672564132436815412514785476213737558232181746457572168143787526",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "459": {
    "question": "1232521817168251212857357614248121427864358246365871465281611527",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "460": {
    "question": "2425318772355476175423774872655157645624641548223146743545218767",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "461": {
    "question": "4645483522168475287467132135255485517326715261146374152277783244",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "462": {
    "question": "6546213647133558246536862685542382476541162648645164726458741552",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "463": {
    "question": "1643385273625176476526352558347772718516565712187825574385166327",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "464": {
    "question": "5227253864523157666452125626271443152876515824252845736137348362",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "465": {
    "question": "2567461484552637518651236831374217661385517244623548644173542273",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "466": {
    "question": "6235452832186463212685435887631146435378846527544547368648241665",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "467": {
    "question": "7123456768731323421618723575825634327382568324217254661852386252",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "468": {
    "question": "6121756815468134658137155275434673112186453656428657432323621814",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "469": {
    "question": "7827365735472862368225545434278672314355225821366355862274163258",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "470": {
    "question": "2313846585722333314632784625461443585736152163573862712361574581",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "471": {
    "question": "4832421231358723728113752358764174155535874215631251645865243437",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "472": {
    "question": "2416423616778523322576751524133854637412573252118271345647524184",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "473": {
    "question": "1234613465418872257357156168645783457146432512871832376572548311",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "474": {
    "question": "1847664674123265116685354582167253125512824125431735248637144168",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "475": {
    "question": "2481776576215183871522456877153251451278356283342431455117586466",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "476": {
    "question": "4576255463475728717216635637661227784536316422851253864774253475",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "477": {
    "question": "2416826531245487731835234211376187677451257358125817122637864172",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "478": {
    "question": "7484551213617524683721326732475245778531561374821423347626281341",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "479": {
    "question": "5471563351672226272485654364215766136832823467147642148718662422",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "480": {
    "question": "6114376315374876357584157143533268235642238116654467256177533123",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "481": {
    "question": "6287217125467351517233481376562516148253823342761753611238374567",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "482": {
    "question": "2158536671162568151783363282271558732624572133834631587287647151",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "483": {
    "question": "7155832578621734621471638521651173766268276346514635218761473575",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "484": {
    "question": "4668513487533541621247481673862536847677342521165247181348527344",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "485": {
    "question": "7836324564686372445528162374216375717372126487346382445351374324",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "486": {
    "question": "6476322525346715762553842254841681527543384711735326316724865261",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "487": {
    "question": "1543256236841227673866418171342343134625687154345432718213324513",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "488": {
    "question": "8713632142711841752134282642738311524237412827453447561626643571",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "489": {
    "question": "5316422845732567133218455744815625466631512714848176312464815377",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "490": {
    "question": "8674732712326877374282151151268376234162634614772417375661212574",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "491": {
    "question": "1872146371532477674812512611783772847775456781261757471254116357",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "492": {
    "question": "8151627417833425423755133472178775284132264367773174361862352741",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "493": {
    "question": "5465237834457637735786242578141171143866428473354746158235235721",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "494": {
    "question": "8372426561343815575381361635287812867311254576317168172338776843",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "495": {
    "question": "3186317372314856781473116177328316325634152824623371642827632541",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "496": {
    "question": "7128162711857264852362174167485158232347565281426612678227421538",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "497": {
    "question": "2762551154318627218327468674717221684416387742651276638323161548",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "498": {
    "question": "4212344657267484456872373751217311755364713446282742825326634723",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "499": {
    "question": "7128467557546442226168745811724347351668654723666482251784732441",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "500": {
    "question": "4137768183524157628124253114243118216534267712432463474122715317",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "501": {
    "question": "4532576822676836716361546185754173848675874535263621541256168377",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "502": {
    "question": "3623531446763861631765482115672324671436843174253151817667834614",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "503": {
    "question": "7614473865316872135573147133842522423521148267773245668337285176",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "504": {
    "question": "4755321657126832862471213251265415243348715385422568455323755487",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "505": {
    "question": "6165213734171688783451448413637224544846576483212526478346681213",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "506": {
    "question": "1647115831275442772245311534475646857325241536734843146553736462",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "507": {
    "question": "6515575814276865571844262431542786641253434775217125464732568172",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "508": {
    "question": "1187233245663728742148673875256177537684264245751267844754487212",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "509": {
    "question": "8733417514767832182725442517377657417228767563176358133472648454",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "510": {
    "question": "6253556448573631518715232621853775334772146412853726183644163357",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "511": {
    "question": "5652414713425223587124331215483623846451617735838523261543361573",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "512": {
    "question": "3215437627615285137465583467516747643512654316215165664378562135",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "513": {
    "question": "3534673443675582512523272473835534265841721331565617773828514663",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "514": {
    "question": "5573746126857773617213574456415547163582737854252857223451632876",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "515": {
    "question": "6612834485622145747151831153176868384528231511766876321435846413",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "516": {
    "question": "3124542713617526271346526561782358361542225183246635328174886125",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "517": {
    "question": "5663744353685421315343636457813578361574334511181574248344843266",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "518": {
    "question": "8275271141832547233418152853611376115183143284265476633867144656",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "519": {
    "question": "2483436762544183485527475643827724381325433256778536351243275824",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "520": {
    "question": "6173145281473635145243874365547837148721241335715723643372325164",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "521": {
    "question": "5576463847265411158125476844736651376285421821553365785163528177",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "522": {
    "question": "5817526161332554617564387284142635727541422186726642522714463783",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "523": {
    "question": "5772162342846135255871621623433823345286675178577863152617562141",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "524": {
    "question": "2225465365827314475228577823655535413728876435765728453213158245",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "525": {
    "question": "4654123831324877134576647141331547836252821233477478115335578414",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "526": {
    "question": "2675171215486773434274512175544318412547741653252714133232564176",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "527": {
    "question": "4586246772643526834246513423311644164243273761452611372262571381",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "528": {
    "question": "5616785687312636353467435348566464673285772746661846557372348611",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "529": {
    "question": "2476325172244566182564573635733433478126631217354736284341833672",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "530": {
    "question": "6112681376346215341561483213448585455672253632413827143117532564",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "531": {
    "question": "3245812673345271651875375462787422413755862375141357468231715542",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "532": {
    "question": "2376184322131567374167842423713852724333167837527834366585625326",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "533": {
    "question": "4315683686344551378125542552174371233365224771866762427554768612",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "534": {
    "question": "7756431475386422466372555157318764126745164381731257456634712565",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "535": {
    "question": "7465781487442565566762117527147842187736187635643352768376148157",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "536": {
    "question": "1241783116743676823564176327455831676282348321442768134614131563",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "537": {
    "question": "3655452468263157833656166433784151748336148123262363558462566463",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "538": {
    "question": "1862435137163282837471455211274321374516755313686235781255223671",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbbwbwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "539": {
    "question": "1685127457217843417664384416835265112281273534362358261785637443",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "540": {
    "question": "3575216785371237518136243357748661244456763425187852537512637835",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "541": {
    "question": "7433752187566112526412141841137515124578427686133681345771245266",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "542": {
    "question": "6811735783254516138136352637458461235827416121383658472157628562",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "543": {
    "question": "3512167866234184653148452351757313748226517836274815673327762441",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "544": {
    "question": "6835521751326783345747251763345252258371648215748524673664531618",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "545": {
    "question": "1175484317753286441676383253643176211322346817256364151787375666",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "546": {
    "question": "5358442282554517251487422645527346325875612635843724625524711638",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "547": {
    "question": "6185463762581277514637288465513642752366165752647354851267124842",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "548": {
    "question": "5442733148665737214367585718241771547876657142228367742571158243",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "549": {
    "question": "4617837627751384142166727166424553624817384455663648742133742132",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "550": {
    "question": "3478456713867525743153275613827424455583655627184167583375563147",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "551": {
    "question": "8265123465322741347685711153162556264787234351647821365652536823",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "552": {
    "question": "2214275777538526145743863248561726873451135112464832657517214835",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "553": {
    "question": "6562436223468417638547625144773817612871183776258175322662335475",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "554": {
    "question": "5641173255648253657344211121737538182654824434612535611774524815",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "555": {
    "question": "7861347253367387751286357185435186656714127436186548714327536825",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "556": {
    "question": "5236647843135225568573141318454282723765373661836521874748117652",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "557": {
    "question": "7761126457327146153863113155218764147852764141214823776581455657",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "558": {
    "question": "4575376223465657575478138167142572316648175623826446311558134276",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbbwbwbwbwwwwwwwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "559": {
    "question": "5472316275338421814122161413568112276318316234746823451742821745",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "560": {
    "question": "4623647183537632364126586165532714183465753711866742584342361135",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "561": {
    "question": "1258262636731248281537116284525171238415423661818251563752166875",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "562": {
    "question": "8251672641357634266481453647158175145361653215741422615358273314",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "563": {
    "question": "4512746327841321331463788621427513685144213764211253478611278677",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "564": {
    "question": "8557164343524111181475266426335577635235218344273277186476518377",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "565": {
    "question": "6682463615673284634418633128764534152331586527167432315863135471",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "566": {
    "question": "7174863645326181274857613231567711736524544662378365241335163462",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "567": {
    "question": "2621416743672158343367146223544136751224185436434714522671563582",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwwwwwbwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "568": {
    "question": "7154153445372781245855746781443383437215617763783614865513754762",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "569": {
    "question": "6551826784152673277735825187434276235514637216523617712612684715",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "570": {
    "question": "7638435447528133753323162543324855653841317647822477463123116723",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "571": {
    "question": "6754234478441656547548251573816237413583623354388527361513865154",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "572": {
    "question": "6372185421526141433681851524267673173662778325265867423123512721",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "573": {
    "question": "5355481278436126457677412631447551282647648472515464172552276334",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "574": {
    "question": "7364261824753831351183623265611368271526143832374182637525425481",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "575": {
    "question": "1425187137344561735632852358534613676436421475535842633726554228",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "576": {
    "question": "3641158683226752186342152145816446267118643258765663272114585643",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "577": {
    "question": "7322118114782531528751565533472547526713383233673175826226135372",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbbwwbwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "578": {
    "question": "3761325585451652661475724528631311365426211636425682573124532562",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "579": {
    "question": "6312625864254875746515838474517465218465285733171548272541873341",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "580": {
    "question": "1683662747662854363482355347168134764538652474342331524632563154",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "581": {
    "question": "4784311614642781125341543854466155426368342158737437174225162472",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "582": {
    "question": "7721862175322281347753285648323742817563226427258376634313524871",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "583": {
    "question": "6434528272563318136841724821145651652642864557235712173734538562",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "584": {
    "question": "1474181546186723734423813736324818233476628513282264853486432152",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "585": {
    "question": "4128532625876122831122651675814325142787386273316734152877563316",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "586": {
    "question": "1815143585145226234643824327561674425261126378773441622566862744",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "587": {
    "question": "7532774454178326761234184474628687654247374668512585563538237165",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "588": {
    "question": "5554835136255487433677582733481748224735638126738153566275683121",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "589": {
    "question": "2173541181472163765778257211643237218625458633763568471268521247",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "590": {
    "question": "3714151265712374812366474732655132672148184572453138272673841475",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 8
  },
  "591": {
    "question": "6651217358843217757616833128476512735648274635362712628543517122",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "592": {
    "question": "8155273473263348673454224867225642538673563813751472443353417662",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "593": {
    "question": "6242783527856344125527858534121715263618481124733358517243178527",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "594": {
    "question": "1123526726717584183613425237367483562175616281356725681565783121",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbbwwwwbww",
    "size": 8
  },
  "595": {
    "question": "5228466278712654228513473672537565723866446386128413723521571785",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 8
  },
  "596": {
    "question": "7110589429968472812181179381511871064102511125561189101192417611137581210115981211214747107651147235811282941110101447710127756594108131011825121013459412136118975231047911412387",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "597": {
    "question": "11223712591161191012835811972448198123611974106111237314591033452657911102879631123710831278411831212952111591071610423929754125691118113241151657868711239123165115443672101227",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "598": {
    "question": "85851196141011247911110119111123710481062119121453629311489107123931023491111861161281910243251371245299662964411128357111561044721511978582710312191010122971056231146621131231108711",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "599": {
    "question": "1184511210391012244710811311615108295376124865121148912711310817124981110761411123721163859911384721041012112336191095264221115695810457910945389127110123105128422911675231061299116",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "600": {
    "question": "1011861012511122108791061041251113103281016427352123910411773681101144829610812251246611148266101019111288734897113821011111610113127292461696108123311047245610575623121511138111068974",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "601": {
    "question": "1061518721281031106825911103871262311414116778311371099512751058441261773981106637128482871011181210312412110797327121151012437269103121229810351956311982211751910753491148105108",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "602": {
    "question": "311126651891011176341210861110194119103712110106561193472977111051210673911412889411110911315541041111836757110169311712831121711122101095583712886110712934912618452710126287511011764912",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "603": {
    "question": "10384912152589991212867108541281094135861144965321083121741132981112651996116101081523119214575101081237410265181041081269711824110812119514948752411272241010119825787510126416",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "604": {
    "question": "74181011264511101104123845121167612117108429191052119467581212186101118104108681096102121111379544525712682893210711811261011291076102811451048108171137961254122891110611126591278101194",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "605": {
    "question": "781284652271191191112452106101181471086121159544682129875677431141085119112251168103101127452109213721143109112781734797328129985910412105453816236411699110212138669311499108112",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "606": {
    "question": "58621161041091236687513111084111159841211026493910561129114711111634529111084112279446734584111017512111136349110105126344111212497486242323971051261012761104234591191091237864156",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwwbbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "607": {
    "question": "31110113295111751189212761151042119734872461296254481312101310688711127124458291211183191241161111092810101712258611810412165105112411116121311328392561112986310195227710141268536",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "608": {
    "question": "72101274471686911711031287452784313107591182598116311717910721435119351124117287111103657710101843599311186117810298212537104631121088114826212615610388911511241031811579116754",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "609": {
    "question": "72116410973331567381162126410105721291365114441210136111111083743210861091910121086457345111115798211171012866511739102536327741145125216642278711954112319101211867121031110107321106",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "610": {
    "question": "941039612682712795912410383349110275868115111081254821111107897111735296101236710117179841114786612135325224389961111585496711961226758321191241011172612111053744761115108391228",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "611": {
    "question": "3981669152121051112949710511487231112744105995110810692411711126491311159167124578111731121046785341257638291251112411837112254129310861121172594911195810481237262112674158911",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "612": {
    "question": "11321146918125959465312125105312141042417361758312411761312683637431628135671014811127812681910634431083286738111427811561291068101612811518911421187181245231841911211810573",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwwwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "613": {
    "question": "212951191182149610475212411110527141128689371132311161971211854127610921163411822141125911143812911081076626394101117931037117561223189165210736121110310982751152764101731127685",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "614": {
    "question": "27118108141225821031358126389511811553721012653610161285929811123966157121122711827391077881268112434571941254101712105124127958101345829911112310129102211891543323912910371056",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "615": {
    "question": "69947591232111151253141089562117161025311128810651168641911399210611271084686107912101153579765172381011872911101046121131153112610910418411225182761071038824657695187641135611610",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "616": {
    "question": "692512637114558126952112294811107255988126116715834319102111105978583225712669181178725111112869853271811211109352125810107611191718359782612101124103311101285689106118153721112",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "617": {
    "question": "4108197611102328995231679411511926104163711111714439231101347115116611581046912116731253621215714891021110109101258746854714109126376142899548197439274126101191083412311729",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "618": {
    "question": "276411110283711732101281185410184557921071131057109610817332811928435114110181039726610412563222121016816111115125310823112771310129116101117810164373431281111097421167109611107910153",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "619": {
    "question": "376283895212312104867210159536212295438125317283641119843111268942791137538116127275769811333431189310121047641091067948126434235126111191026681155521114125109111212375116",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "620": {
    "question": "1142374123891141011710154127368394625527871210121111087224144102812369111038251091105461167811397116102473110429310611111101171066815923109512819114479121110977461151681051113712103",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "621": {
    "question": "1244571146362815117345109210251292111478763291353101134798911101293261113725861241010911810471158421286953910876121142811129567133341181132109124171752114118517121046869251011355",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "622": {
    "question": "116111737941121041224291023681191381212654101458109263311184497611161513733104694818263115811124210898211113875109311106654212115782122112483758108731511165941191167118412445",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "623": {
    "question": "945351776485858187112391261299114781832161137112974845521086911644534211151023912118310751181426112108366512111257764121133815611814299512376427621059981711131210821177648",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwbwbbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "624": {
    "question": "31184711119951061151052348124169641031185112285121669652411106541952104118101217211693810447963108116563941095119912326112611331106175124359110321161051082671261739129311255110472",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "625": {
    "question": "911107123461074101281158971084101912127711271039637116594123210585311310732611351298410612359781035121106101143121031681158311103851257912711284710893452725610761198212747910111851186",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "626": {
    "question": "11712498109879383101161195127411211108210241912668399128112212495101186127611121496579865210103835237411126821109541226114210314373511692122179111118105356584810279256461012933811",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "627": {
    "question": "111332169105108361097325112856810410109311102333122678411127241141851071192358119101064781107231112841093859685113105412434688121024119729351061536211103911412107723152129423641",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "628": {
    "question": "71266121086115110315982411106812571066122613118102431161810612786755410110122829971011351254641176127610223591011836101071186114128251297238524434611810962410171165497193125116281074",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "629": {
    "question": "9101257111175644511210127896136988121191107752114389968510724221111091812111091011146812532767685294498965892910431163121117942110531261231015897338472411351041251111165121211810",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "630": {
    "question": "1110947661221083611449107812872857961031691157532694811098311281071191011126181194372116991736841011312123162111238119106212174587911642103212883114421221055964571949212104287311",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "631": {
    "question": "411298412627110311262695910841834912310761142795710374188968514723161925712961126101102681184489512512536210811679811712103916485710517689335116421181012101211728108571413126",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "632": {
    "question": "31126610121511911054311269814464859121932103879739112129411988101114112951261127785491110421115926912610812946622108191211411153108761019111101583621232108161129733579241584101211",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "633": {
    "question": "14738691011183211112651748103421051243610198101151114112896591010211951141675829463123423117911112310574611372122841091053291099101812119171172853121110124646710111515112110471124751",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "634": {
    "question": "84231097831116107169387410512738311761041249121054919211377967321191771111932769581011492121110103116119535972186109816810912459211772269441312831141072681049523512118771111111102",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "635": {
    "question": "957437281091112872124106951731142108710965679231186912171141091511986231262581113118394249611431010127912610448113182106215732487849112291132310310113641872111087119102915492",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "636": {
    "question": "111393106715551297533411528435101278119618631011191212910511563619851210489116257118912376112112936117951262871104971122711081051046421191166410103121018696365247774101012527898",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "637": {
    "question": "1195682712109129771166142122823991041012567791281035648715794582631111101121147410527995141011783961181210172689593928891010376310410551249610732336491891017512131057111281279",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "638": {
    "question": "41265924661114110824125111069398161266111159715118521146710964911011382885112117131285217118211778371256127106542193810394919105625121067321196101149593107976124211435121142991062",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "639": {
    "question": "1291142268337101641099458725487565121071291153241178581657611212114108381104912687311252241117113351188335762611499119118810541062111218425910127611117319812108112581211111210643",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "640": {
    "question": "117109123728146107101110897122651771211279510833247541019451174581103105629121044362975917133597111041108894105124712361281067451031163415292310978258677114118199931041041227611",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "641": {
    "question": "561226473681929510798411610124259156126771034471211511929612673815104941171246773261148641072351951278532411195126264985612310102619261110116847571654129861069371146211512113",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "642": {
    "question": "11775102891264106271284153168891102725119569121087115611211312192449189101148611057111112422871112610543521254101277597103811911272124458126611105487136104112485741265510126341183",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "643": {
    "question": "9106315211451235541723864386151831191074122122119109917752431012813736910614311611238127899141215263831252622911101274395107861121396112749108211512326869110444183931011297",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "644": {
    "question": "981216423511711035102161289452431210392178659741210108493101087425625351114581012593821229427581112417589814912593651121151108978111458248211104581161210276126510111185541121",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwwwwbbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "645": {
    "question": "81126641089311241810971126125106943114107161243310818511146511694411266538105476791282371077281284311112415667611391111123113989111953829105141210411112674991105761612813552479",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "646": {
    "question": "104511199281285591873211964102111059466632821391164510712810721076811356412896124446727212346986911232105211109494110410812171193511941101012946521328576122811942678549810112",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "647": {
    "question": "101010812393421132854654121037961223681107981165724121110110897439105516618561179384212518627291271010110911261131058744119212811623810711496147612875326116189114121178351011161910",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "648": {
    "question": "10121442876710118610711434510121091111110124410558611124559511835109364112987575211796348612710810611435129795145310881107118315627991084453101286191236111115108934998612218711410",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "649": {
    "question": "12510911365891953698212141011941051258951117991852111037261211145129142741083109677124542195104711113101232496148451237781211104116433512783442659996977328124101128118767281114",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "650": {
    "question": "7121135161010726779546311131012141010921111481212914678511115366109103102512111122871010586837358210410689117101167293571848131073811464294211128711111143691712982511107105241111211296",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwbwbwbbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "651": {
    "question": "89242103128639521111274981063124146759114116103811191154125712757948678101234658761011101729101012884135101510845721111129410751126123104105112673461291287143410558611471291136865",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "652": {
    "question": "1047211114310951429522106111112821173611911510851012392467961022611057124103737162129554710103571179293123919101283617847314310648629126432957328149612647211111211298713351248",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "653": {
    "question": "275101210114331067125369111011410115914574612185412172957361110128517311593997511271012814512629104111938127148710673411658111071231184183102451210969610111091241177411123438691277",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "654": {
    "question": "54638177925232146592101458115174864107121783526312411211111641119878105974112856119943951187125123710101131012599141122585610113712103109111496789101121611114835494257318616",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "655": {
    "question": "9354512546810118119624571151012129544711613810101012312541191129108895481262314312369861197471116389441256231181075187737451211102976651810786341256956311312814271289716510253",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "656": {
    "question": "1196253744157119583249117101143889326128711517488631021026111841712295612411591092669111091322381111079117611255384102851291911113724399105111127123121186810914121171610238519",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "657": {
    "question": "46871151219454721286115981510101195919101867358724175101196910251111041711171191531112542531412511369848151066442105542410799118110412119583125261034106645291011941087322107121",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "658": {
    "question": "111291923118849115322291268482101279531081334129751084111510383968211971975311121436121274618995423732568162451191172848591211081234181291074899452127821062101114761012569",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "659": {
    "question": "1246672579118128115101231761053811451210963143612286721593561012101191117667533641159412712331119328105947141110126688511681094171210681125148210392698711101459121121967129891119",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "660": {
    "question": "598247412114461267101287511531314762412465210435936108121071111131105368685110612379247116511126673510751110347927126391112910513781131226118949275107631217895112101107661113597",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "661": {
    "question": "96101226453116922127951173711051111310391122794104411814936711169465727512631185424610911105836912711241232162101189827924127635910827911845121058294711101052611234211041797675",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "662": {
    "question": "7101032111265585610108512573211318961075712312391117109121867512101341086927112874211038937351294648116104111295821073101975111571046881071153589812148468129102972512672378118456",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "663": {
    "question": "41582435121173114795128912861035784461198187724651101066321981021153512189111152126448742111019810112512104596172717238411315710522111191186251234910410110122461111491112917711526",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "664": {
    "question": "10211822113665719872103611124115215984111210361211591969351078644126101104113410246519731675116319211108112210987924111567411831121592993176581111128916411121059178381112551117622",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "665": {
    "question": "7511971811163393761241211810579248311106105269128277745111511181153751238711599619123101126767108148146541087941144611103574521191248719512537321108101195423274167348105972",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "666": {
    "question": "93111612257119951211311810104746211121386101145292461051386711355910216310883675411821011286521163121045172837921143511121042810956361131010111810376925711825171213910107812411925238",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "667": {
    "question": "511411493112525108271106810122812113210741021647611026127785118391132646114117211983110881239742121051991012110632511871097612611111052531953411968106491248611123114731135119712510118",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "668": {
    "question": "1411331282445961038875112154191161812101110823510721146731289111107259449129129236710851055379104652511027124611391710118243510103121177548711912104431011115291210647876841011109328",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "669": {
    "question": "7451851033649109712166611934391151276146561085115491067319452311710712258112924611561031111449231275610126910108473911611105762698311161246231474951541049862821267139102398128",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "670": {
    "question": "4875122951169103271081146921131641287510293115710511199521221056131237724871159351210124911115319211511012912235811851078979210111266754113751108121421791112845125672101276571041185",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "671": {
    "question": "164872312710133781010826111712811912419610526122293510411117921395589611438856843112131093101167138612445410431191263754311116947610562771991053221091312752476151015812686498",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "672": {
    "question": "11569151012992813781051292746119942181115123966194578123785122364741096571061112251031194822910361231141247791112621033411541176981107106399111112512711410128963127102912411184674",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "673": {
    "question": "7110411285981135798131141036759627477612711114733101228519951216733611210376104181282105127851199104783982312971114101465871110351012812411561049775881078536121410610310118487155",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "674": {
    "question": "110117843125118101038119745622117559716126831237552981039110112108651231499648382511210149261110115185381731032696141089251291146115481171931181031211210711118935251041281043116",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "675": {
    "question": "11512311711941214161051169117871276122486329275361096861111611819663227711478912411596412911861110512368192351111210374128112151081499461038117345931074512738610810542952111137",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "676": {
    "question": "1024119172531241117695210583839711749710649127510111132947710178267111192111141091967123769642812127105114217210826195712413210481181076126459411689148473126121138381255109273",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "677": {
    "question": "58312101281127688923148121110632412671284351112275811246332211116878121093151111298108911071041235928611547125510338111211128351133715210611811103657251175691041927894610138116539",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "678": {
    "question": "12326310997421172843411129461086639111035124615111923910386912786114435115310116261041227574514127102109110512101136762887111044810161112941031104211811101210197485116212116117105733824",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "679": {
    "question": "212899615910911105611119487193523854919711102351210969241055841091831028113951171112101214104810423128111111111071126954121107685441267311195511109369867814152118392614798955106",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "680": {
    "question": "1133101841911471015699112481231129854106111858111278113521328101051112610843949321866710612531023193212627674112681341168410810291217537711152128243115291071243681210612535113598",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "681": {
    "question": "11156849123379591261063211688384112101912165951071231110624361131541084411241094111427451111251078994113816111131211727161096895113591112711169210681210483101277875112954772812183911",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "682": {
    "question": "954112881135473121102957610952101071658101291231810223186551759101210449626103682125711910710818461921211128649672109161074575811513115953572104811786956111011928101111126721537",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "683": {
    "question": "11118119833210125631048251129712259103724108838812745711710281117246859105278316331281179576125110511103891145711326121762811131210265235381279811145928151293747105923427568",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "684": {
    "question": "10542810161210116963711611151284364594291021216369112114210155111106869449112273299116141011105163810445112121065211846711871241111510122125521017711893716113103294310410951731211162",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "685": {
    "question": "6289118471154101114121053236797410385119719659210238615511267868851110939103114976385210869716492101212761111028439111111127235310467426861191011123510493521056118981269871034921",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "686": {
    "question": "916710108112511351091011513727612118265719328106391110411281661229311797108437459328861011357118957104213413510938111110411689811105731298471268129589524511236103539612284110119",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "687": {
    "question": "617115612118191098771121154112251198697391299864881082631147129116587137119211213668113121112554410684239212118697336191110321249711356105719711111751139610112343842103911711106",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "688": {
    "question": "1265241031108557863111127711119237851116711214855126103911619512112818116471121111112834989312124108297957984186125210368752491171291011111169871012411101112310711494568441133731069912",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "689": {
    "question": "65373286974562546171183104239111832107544927312281197586921241154376127921053121143171067642111165410991129791237371238196121310487912103412578548112969711113251074468",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwbwbbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbbwwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "690": {
    "question": "1861111210165311169310781237510104773111081221379562145210876511596521017893910156811122329857121171361035118671011110946112459261083512412810461011391811153157912843372898561",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "691": {
    "question": "9983212274359710542591112112814511103106117212376916512114102911658910986311111210931015426473245724101188106112791182143771131108178111081721211425621058101062723911145114823741029",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "692": {
    "question": "31251128721031812143932101187311611872847129108512232111625103108661169953798312104521113638102128577275921171121023668211386521127104152451321138361197831112210617369111010881122",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "693": {
    "question": "10141911833812323103101278111591152676212711157310812161110921198103738112663111136841091757421710676981112251111182911359512410312462731096323111127461119811091210451121191117517103",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbbwbwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "694": {
    "question": "9421011247108939612106435123110310184658129119625312106831715431091163199839241441012661043681021512421109613121511651681137111143110111292981465103724910126412811011125259774",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "695": {
    "question": "3548626111113251079964384112641133611064572391219517104631244811796111278261210211451369103744213511323510116121871192245711612341061112753910321051186168351011124145117910721228",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "696": {
    "question": "4325849110123710497111045133239210101128897311118653472312914117791033264107391812251148276113341151069510481121151297512921110769482910871143126851021127910811724125825107118411",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "697": {
    "question": "512101183114621791281211923710956125311315846835910412721310724411699251105761269834422637112105793153928496101171191891027310510124558310123111969934154712361131117692115837",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "698": {
    "question": "191039511782411585671109471128111345512113862116181110410963314229610354942991258531014899751211965107110119136698125127411631354377341211429717106536109911011272412852351689",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "699": {
    "question": "12581776246111096875811433168112225911862337111219112694853796113179861141386127101951029835212157611841011213912773111512107734292103241226986112958963611912485429721051138",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "700": {
    "question": "106852189510271563126105329810111266586433938310926169111269958311171244412310111146755817431281115106254621031214211512915611210111110941411353562101101127973121834311294672453",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "701": {
    "question": "9824811364175123841054227634351178129101126109482151239596811729311121125632105891279211761512245810391194181210751122105721481911825152101711116153210697113104106152441110328",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "702": {
    "question": "569177321181261810931261257492664101159853118510912712362105710541161110979684311135281218111067294512128638104211231111698810147811242529164105611612103481195412376810659116",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "703": {
    "question": "91148351111038922141011317961249287181011533871349599121131263102911168716593847125112111012481166955798106103175214114812629214336311691298471028127131025429112852686111143",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwbwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "704": {
    "question": "6113821111861076981274102115311155101109311102446196546731282210631011112741073101081079114629837121273991151125475811671242114107569255810919611944510121048635129111109123109565107448",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "705": {
    "question": "310101111168114219610399261215598223654119166461073853272759961023438125836751428945118758923551027118814109106851712101110108234821091047563819925973610114811311421112655106",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "706": {
    "question": "10364576381012111211786310521174651852111104426112710116751187576274729102791011183711679672103151138912117891016910259210634723561141084511271112471156834462976111311512582637",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "707": {
    "question": "162664812736554912113110287695189812235894885679110114236384229675111192657541810113493103276463249753681112284454651108311111110628251210974131284721011815721145111263",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "708": {
    "question": "85691522412910642110511531298712767894111214591143710612871611511317610101511831210195675387117521012747513744412101142111010246510963121351856431021110623727256122379106312118453",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "709": {
    "question": "7682511131481079124711266512211123814114107942711108455611115896242109712111384623695541110571131923610364576958112118132931259241063881110541275211164285871291065216731231095",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "710": {
    "question": "58126397311481711134101921057101091134386121211510110121017493544127411038412616108924810272910981473612237121571196610112451181299310117563146121986889111210215133941675481016",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "711": {
    "question": "432510428471111991851168121027114111895568771971083121261142111169181095131251411839783107758679458811214325712101169641074147519610112932567123132121024411915851057323411101211",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "712": {
    "question": "89795331194821017568651272117564981311261224912725993112661228641387559241131012481411221071145410314356122821910927911146829591111636769129438978121164141028111046571599",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "713": {
    "question": "212115979124111091211108129411236439321151079121112847112510391281163121129145212715631151054761562891237245212735106921824101156417127673461011121651111107312458111961114107163712926",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "714": {
    "question": "4210135127491021142311141241061026311124971243517210421096128123946279839959105246117374912476810281131441091241911321072110769854912611181011234149310111263962485312679510102111",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "715": {
    "question": "111217231036107558117512101026108611411228577410101165112328212585824621210513118446352611361275439617810111139352126446311111106419858121212698411531077110108426101254265127510311117",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "716": {
    "question": "10529224111123179851231076811103104741111259111111248310757491071151123374244571011569111123929614311471063117797125886211251109711311341171067572911126141210846395582124114648710",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "717": {
    "question": "8391265111107157683111153111092115546109738122154711461289351210101769721187412398586379115619941011827644281710912310710895921184731127911812245169811291027164697105359821165",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "718": {
    "question": "9477121036610211312291017258212123511110184736291021084712151171211239111410818114111223361051012822144727111211126951310616117592391026264107945118279433811012521124103115610279",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "719": {
    "question": "812610112488711310251171331298641016101059331122510811211361197814369127211118787124796511313108591111282611510518111239761387114106912956113111328671012126111873610841893612117146110",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "720": {
    "question": "731946512968289121103711521872812568131034741168215312743610119468291271211713278108419115654362111178865322411104113911711108926610263119473682653766649912584921210781167",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "721": {
    "question": "611931011811194211167645128310215112510452112864103101162951781192111261549942951111293312531085679111595831166104921041272143157811596541110111112961195812273104161085418510114105",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "722": {
    "question": "109621261183746991112951054236759113916988412128426851088795101038479128104421349121111042398510416102989107612114710473652122103185391712523810113117101022165121018342109227712",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "723": {
    "question": "6981135310111712116337381041261512761196831411264237115211527810593124976118910127111264587436121112451012544361079837271141071187199111221041116587113884129210111110254816571194",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "724": {
    "question": "41071281141291010757261294510831141212210716541995104681113249615212113611683117951126141268487273987105116711312197425310418874910122413739481069184632114715782104678116101",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "725": {
    "question": "1021021211761271024116213110128797648527521171553710657910121212741111945661101110910412278111155248127631512109384464196978110832113572159610834123839663125119243312892174595",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "726": {
    "question": "410652113111181297116149412111066735910682123311829345104791112531187312111115101631184893582109181110284127261272781291143108124132112931127810111123521410571283996710227107481159691",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "727": {
    "question": "717391549111719481112745103118699117103284101217269310289511897210452612492112381612562238611211117311232123511813910777105161249111375711235911989423771685251612810851191377",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "728": {
    "question": "74210869151112254487122115336477519581010211103117871287541112710119563191171941135106581236571011241012511911236103311224101131210649226567119881111243101110681279538102552234111257112",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "729": {
    "question": "810494447121131111018910273712548724153612410126111284652859122472756110972312131010119849112107121271138532610412113473117101711862341227431126124558125571039166111191258411101667",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "730": {
    "question": "55147281071211728829712111131071011786461239821198383410510268211959671214311292111031810612685741237411328129591126957113611129945106371026987514915179231187614843411010411285",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "731": {
    "question": "1037914762101111113571279812103810412711556246912563710114771011298947251291127538811310105642912834791124568611112873741844121159310119101071510334610127531161095104817411910931227",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "732": {
    "question": "4311191258547398412113671788611221091108334569887139241210624167498125467635122311614710849311111259812176104655731265622810311410710457110124389311811124567321752210694126611",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "733": {
    "question": "1051127124361588312210102979411644829211342451364796812102634111815281271128611112104511943107211112116983115962104129819101111855101231710248511091011388101228119536421111511382102111",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "734": {
    "question": "736310423158596114851837912152116108994721127611910712191111812292810964221068911217376111227167458388610551263119211123114296118510342127921161025510974837156468415692112119",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "735": {
    "question": "11121096739812631242810711711967394911651210616111283412991044111567128252875831826542121181942593661011461277105911111261059881247531229911510186371110411129376711871186112741532",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "736": {
    "question": "5941071219113728496258315117545759833241278121110210167541231111511487629168936579412103127831114521069211126478683110734123112412716115872114521041012536512578457341061287111",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "737": {
    "question": "591013726844371110912106842102910726941253813847845115424174423918101154566101014291291012511211667910681145217103331148679109665243910105821837521696351177121112711198375104",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "738": {
    "question": "1078341112681251210523731411111323129610111710641210351168127851111111374102536125598102591775101269312141011164121075101154119128511172651029741011011638881091123416312264345581271061",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "739": {
    "question": "2461021234117418176101111473310211314410891211294753912291171010288955116111141011812951109674212111078213968754689123111151157741162648734391188108129531098147526112910911106712144",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "740": {
    "question": "6692111085122475364481211101711106241233819164943571110786971108521011724126891101159611123810582651211338351112691056523121411738196105641662953128102128621173210491111199121168954",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "741": {
    "question": "879312635311103611781031184115121032610128495111038612910725711159259710761210811095781113696116104171563651432511612212610512641231189995337251310126265911981112431102111045761963",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "742": {
    "question": "17110936101241811214141038957837271211111924454861191187109111711054103810107994271681057691245810492116497687351144811037105961211352158911576521156835510949691262148106104",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "743": {
    "question": "941710851061011949685111372711510863129492221071242867395211361032881259611310271051248108392454111116726106412118474756372945210121151218531067471074511951238141291141010712332",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "744": {
    "question": "86824911351071128119345118661063105293118812188612210564337111111023112584471812111119510651145810123337121435893772538124910741111810491256811112161451017128962111108265111223111",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "745": {
    "question": "8766819556318234512910611191011011810878351125917467112387511912101210925610583512494911116451079911123912861134426111511113812591011126451231141107823121310811633411381098261111574",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "746": {
    "question": "121037381131025115212710634103112512101194111453864410231114912212141012310827113469528711101311186475211191455227494869485931861025113411210810586267111091578124522111252973418",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "747": {
    "question": "7813564411291017312107934861197611125323110341095112518763697782510214510349682111217951181779971082321010421187912811971084101532613465111074258653112106129937512341127510695",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "748": {
    "question": "9825137410912711012674169811955381191248322471211165819411048971089511269176111123284931114952497710121112114768541011378119167614411648126910215189128397543928935810141011",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbbwbwwwwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "749": {
    "question": "8479385186102821755321199629129746581011577210410911253173667911210544710111911312417986111031152124412104592111106569596181045712411926122722281931110249712510554110311461187",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "750": {
    "question": "1123276851110297418739105123116781193711025337103117129895181041293276111556936111101068851939810113412212831453293791068951151113471195512513278610118531272115641211313686597",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "751": {
    "question": "161112775114834108329134895489581074314612914543128327171234656931711113984108107627613118634238561710542112311225714811247119381162673351105212121086111098114691211871081",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "752": {
    "question": "111212728610598312951010911176811114112126813107587312591051131109765297512444412116317117251251011823671249112285731035127862511312884912361116114810743731129105111845210113712646111",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "753": {
    "question": "251173167129510691278103241046410111257987376672113584121812113238211752482451267493111065873344181011146351236101112119471119588635122109411178871174891013912938166210111425",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "754": {
    "question": "1425212319418268111217105114913731116571061111865754241039410735102128588101711129610247116114112228311819122104410116510835162710125111024352131179951074298139117151993282674",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "755": {
    "question": "13583111244178451263610117219612112839427158477510339112119735727111124611191147262573671173912108927946124875118639212111107810641171051128294810123105641152987547109849111112",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "756": {
    "question": "2681211017471147127911524856310610949127118811191216799281099439510115110279726512831029319471011273124852611494152111010371021115121185102251247961398749386291175511948241076710",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "757": {
    "question": "221710812974599342911012651088677263952911658101234387128778899110649111944125821028563741174212669591106842752811128556391049129311725548101062543579101213101079411982212",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "758": {
    "question": "10116110237645122101261187846951145412629812421257105112128472108369511286967911081112352125965321311827761028311514814110573248121061111238532107918456521044113109758121410169",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "759": {
    "question": "8127105106964114233710851116961211568336410738111106598271103129101163463211631111857124106314243101111567610119234910854781191109434591062364812531110112519871182111182451014527",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "760": {
    "question": "2471211011251143815910210657111056117129618231110210815771069191106441287735109179126148105187834102698117109121185810411123832894111058910745112191277612254181041181111812973821103",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "761": {
    "question": "11892917127731161119127410528105266741113210891027168861151179218112393116412755111638910268845371133111115310108212763106121783116112512982231511729101116452109473846114119810111",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "762": {
    "question": "1121031141119856697131010128541151112119810116410346191118551074612882105632910989456912271191171067431823310119212593108175612101412131112839106391041211010512846369410257939107861",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "763": {
    "question": "612107179610358451011104338121697111046105121183165127102911462629107111848243127146115410114683251218791210458348999748944911112765191071281421142511297510746511531127111793103",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "764": {
    "question": "1124812911410815678237531216241891112101054641249141182106733122466105323110111553493812711541191041113481942853101188127111112484165892876127579101153121110614982386558697212811",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "765": {
    "question": "664882101129129856111312745214744324111586171151298727101031179941085214101838656521151291211783611085312111061111137148327911121015271581111111246112611510879334761210621158115",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "766": {
    "question": "812476297511119899831825441018345122467926661081124111552212551189167127359141081046610943479685594978721663124561010627391168611251191093713961910591228211108216571245",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwwwbbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "767": {
    "question": "7925456118951112311987311024684519872101110122611094851134315688111112125411011458117842911946612412711591111217412910776111042129813611413689146511211827122354561046112351093677",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "768": {
    "question": "10124639271311577295841111161019274695368826356101110471218167105316211261071234965936618634512110272223117891261065811431826975498163248455123537369411848510736123118109",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwbbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "769": {
    "question": "9113522411716926694117128952121012311115119473101127611112989423410815114126874121138151110212771111061231421782521041211781165312825445961047111112101056181094610378593541089741276",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "770": {
    "question": "641178921259107425113831096111336712968171151103151241162511776145811311481096126453117113527211712491353511011139211863111427119985678129436546628310515923121411510610985104121",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "771": {
    "question": "89478112123917323974129551165869111104101184179436362129811857932105461111463721118775115912181011327339211511668462612117783451094789121072963512315897671131041624518111064",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "772": {
    "question": "3544851012715651093712411241227163425119108362912103735341243688721077562101568376121082673911181095191081035101226671101146121153821035243786989382993135411129712465288737",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "773": {
    "question": "117871111063912462911112381057118115116411831283611210732519191013115211141231189541266742491161227102955109326191112611612711894105113192311761127110111751092816412321116556212399",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "774": {
    "question": "1291121196164782789161241105119671619107211106647111195311212121597448331111112835754210695719366286739105112111064811410652397987712126811497359191094512458353621281781191",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "775": {
    "question": "3612810111052924271157693410121113104117662129103891012226104571196124875115321083665111012589951673148104121217112941111010531249810521351048215123161011011108284612877382510361269546",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "776": {
    "question": "1111284512239974261012482111259812117910321143677810258611571012865336827151037781169514126423952188295978124113610115511866231291210210367794810131101281124910511711892619642",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "777": {
    "question": "1119647626111294618791011593289436476125981116765114310812103112123681115841211811241039574516113123910815598111111345386111126794101071055954837116571241019346311102103431157164",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "778": {
    "question": "8131011926612112116112112108911564756117117299361228117752310110515432771925391161012417610118251110436171212261184891531158693105246117911114635592354103711732269611841261231045",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "779": {
    "question": "97995876810221210667115238111011128213722568358269129113119661112475328359158411104461219964124110725114236549119121061883212275391855910736111125114109651247852812189746611",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "780": {
    "question": "482561089737891061086761854454111012148931123837311531610711194811551283841222361918111036761127248612561139121010988733127511410117274875321294111111104366875199847149741127",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "781": {
    "question": "971041012416323912123811351486841151031263102751011652861219912321110510784231041931265211412692555101062115138461112943711872551083861281163114791245442110384113512736312101083118910",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "782": {
    "question": "296261175776410369711227458852332521094721056991112108711357829111913123793671010411556115106843971095101041796127811114889109766111093111212726382784111106981238167842103536",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "783": {
    "question": "11047431127642112210351276944848116101034126929111251110246897121610111283429586111561210101369461215611231571496931012116473714832584135129247876127391128101111151016109733115110",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "784": {
    "question": "11822953163745671112932571010631210121179859941058922111762163144841011951031221176497810111284185349112876511038423756106391228338129311731102652459510636128181323669721012",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "785": {
    "question": "8756542334111011811110569461241013748511861211284912101231173791088811621251711134627839712614364875101282511151191831038281011231198641296115715108591831047782192101251383172",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "786": {
    "question": "112171281010951293481211217885412361275481194983173281121096310915611910881011259111251724511681091372781151614972410759851012463662711410211529105428119126872314924104481284",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "787": {
    "question": "6489711105713715782611611211101357984212611171888613911821151377610991182691151256831256312113211197113161082123117644113969987101278211621087511291182110973456382757128113379",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "788": {
    "question": "7251911101183681119812121016731016743992151945516731011121111923571312228181244771510107121028124546391231910747948744111018721071595897112116147278769812751111167129286311110",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 12
  },
  "789": {
    "question": "57149485352123727311129168686911143110971295110122119358243458986817912554107741196107112648511293411967311185562943188612711511106616271584552108741029686311512114711102",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "790": {
    "question": "5346102645121093116819610411757115311491861011942831053761262107114121091154357859632121031111995108735161267371211111055411181237642108109101125312246612510285463791411641135532111",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "791": {
    "question": "71101251136811910951222511087431112943781112610101125197125585659131010948665117101089616211395461210441011110283751211109110156111319521271186552769310763119101117225811711651045121037",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "792": {
    "question": "121074265239111536810279952101096511651121221510247461113979181312799105181271193511104865711541181217944269953312511213564911547646597211110868312911255746910171101210486893",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "793": {
    "question": "388761110210525764981091911311312149710681114111291157101611958317910114567433511810218262731011839624612101821145395214511102612942592611341187310984846121317111629743851148",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 12
  },
  "794": {
    "question": "11264293577126127121110956587211145126692437635121318410751934671110311710468417129585111311128432231012101599111026571093727561891059108411167769811513424571012137457109114",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 12
  },
  "795": {
    "question": "9712144413155581410171391551124614114107711458158119110361442923141111101271315267481011425141051012131071036129111541154713285141015212108128135123841412105151138471391279106291415418142135129131171221033914141513467311214117249121415414128791413151115132242610138141114915131452193117615142511813181361211127106532141",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "796": {
    "question": "4269311101525811297248912138111416771512121211131554749114211414101061423134793184745118743212661221596127481221283515101314121010615321410748113210911128821387134109131355511972831287231122415145136111314132611107185134361514145746173119136136121487311084121151314794155112810613111235371263931912810711",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "797": {
    "question": "1410711157153142111391293141223146641372111561141195613283131410331426153911054841111759117281021215174115951481413123103611146915213147113913428121035711698151118511342101210126157849111331384135111039662141211237114715335131393810136310121102119149157121121391314662152382291367414411124510131513410855410141376424",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "798": {
    "question": "16132511451568310149124111569105131414115101511172912311451366872153117610412125148135621286911124131371115142126941331101102111414599111108106213414108121532141118494136141013463101442131512551357941110121436117124135101422811793121541541314621198413187813219103451512786712931011586317411152736111131215129234814",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "799": {
    "question": "25151121412713951213116715856111342311145145161114121525946131141175282864141311101236112438231591476131312114135105142113261412134148112210557631510832154141913641165361424173671511597623811021136815111312139262123981571211055441312491511182313143131111567101121015421425261133714138810114634971324131121011",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "800": {
    "question": "71310291213112141551369814234156312191111011221373614126419511812769113112135111415269131410392510311658424111313693631231415410412625141112391219141211510361415104351059111057947121153238969710411135513125132910111111061041310121215313112192423751451441551213137210291010751591437621331214116613541512781418143",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "801": {
    "question": "1381191513104141126371595728951112131211413591015111107101451741210141191031512121413812572125149111331115865101171410613121591247567371561412496644121831077813561422131415741121436215281113526421510712103352121538111333111197611211264107181178121151312881214114212741062141382131879411101514951012152711148391318",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "802": {
    "question": "315111314146312712131861533148659144117111213773111610646875911431357154685110112101011789131411511326131464151111014713473211815713541113610111410511261441173851191311462912213111014719151187913321146712581016441161292610321358224156943561483171314691072814548767715149371413216871532811310411141354476",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "803": {
    "question": "761488310851119136154310111665138223159311101441229951110814461011123101694514281315813101213142273121191129714155638812134131111127561314141110314761139387114212610152856679228113141410471312259151010149131211891115121210131214947512697144211613391167110141021110834126713928873315413101113295126247139561112815111214",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "804": {
    "question": "12141141311121241210151069611414251271111141110510149813629123111541112341451310914767112159136441013115733813578310148524416158911583196941410821496911125157516284584256143157131059973101584141116985148235101583141141361379628131231074135115874261711149131559931141214149813391115413510749714151363678712",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "805": {
    "question": "1114561271584101391412341015361325913711131478295153131281411102231428131135911710151227121081491281135813111481143122107211469131117311910841534462121185133326114975936243155122792846921013151371119631014810849721614215123119112147103415141114698132151235794111210131785912211131115310667101571293475851141110",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "806": {
    "question": "1761141811311313842162321287611596315210121252116618313711101465154910672611141310121113108315229123677710687141591111414544273612810131412966814465231015313911210135121151011183127369841510310610126105841396117531412261154156131997523810141183911313146294171514101015692513156118131411159369122101411210135",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "807": {
    "question": "991017131151141292814612141331121394251091518151014314313124411163101141241311102154918101491110142122131814124911131418310569101013815231265711123141387105121153102714812159109821312461485157311865133510151338111121375388125101131462741251115181310731413842131171466111117312512141462111581013141091146118894613312522",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "808": {
    "question": "15127104723121119128113565731091151494212102141136951514212375211157141352651493536473146914810131056141282119573910126131171210958111313153481012613151021422514871101213413893115711141422449629111310148512147212456712118107151414111101438461165212913913111251155614212101051421436115347613118875314279413111011114",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "809": {
    "question": "3138137141106147352856131111414121241015871111839172561346151014312811351513127710997610121151329113411415572692511135101421113315110631114987510253131483133629175412211885696141041313495126478315141211101982781114712693129121212312141196158111362571511931210113948212141413781361136211141512312681321271196",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "810": {
    "question": "2661823463141312141421513101244611058793311711131413112121545102112713151336141048251558310334411916912512351495117715102111810661522814784133131265371081411325413691374211415886115127576111871396414121314143193121271058136421615537121028149671328413561114121471115811171410123289121321155414211713145151436487",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "811": {
    "question": "13981083711372141441111524111412515961076134314831158101415956133611122972851412152105671415459141211112141711368107412111426111161312159471198510825351276101112513151497612131131015614431031352915443131281084614128141391414315102141051285154661411122139355492511937171212191468610411113311672114113612109551108148",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "812": {
    "question": "102521512381997651381511103137111491392122127136210593155684146621551034935117821154613926121135111513968811171252410151412659108121181392143485151241025751469673101131014154568129121114313696102165142916141552115981112101375371291381521191210112896731218211341451174512213118815104542109511361215341013114",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "813": {
    "question": "61213168915434791051351210826109215471148814541275109361321519813261154111131412710510511413614128101514157121112510146988648361115147412561111101211247103137613141189712113131214161513423811144139131812101512563910154197146102611811366994148451115379103131248913122191211579138381215111103214141178571091265111312",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "814": {
    "question": "465914165310710118921511186514813953137128714141041321031358146210769658911151341314512533157211684910341381511971651433881069811414106715116962114731115210812115515141387851431411127281513716841151438132952115154141081105531311071381211481295121412764839111212638117251512101131294214526131314379615646",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "815": {
    "question": "91323115346914111081538154291131012774510651281721108111526921235108891141261413510137538359121411111144141171252132638911110971561310428131431010741461571211111391059868138127215511189631213121141092154248111585102987612431145694981081111311267611528641213101712111511491113106121438101421127131446315341081313",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "816": {
    "question": "12881013721410514121562138102111412467158131511067792214111841324235101778111281397119111041356632141151311102181071415965124491588231111581375148957101573121114411810739648231015221413813413351215279911122610311442815961213712363412988811151127412711061113238109511236191414441377481014131311714110212116117",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "817": {
    "question": "74134211101041214189141311828793574148384101246239135711158869112128111415313139523965171284137611261429513171212614834313349111281431518210131573991413875213101052594132111781311912111514113533297114815111234219214131612913215564141112133814283415113111096145111161459114112315127582611712415210512491",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "818": {
    "question": "4151412926121102813103159613131234711141487234510721415131361442891231415110987179497613512981371414101214414111031410139913121071431051876341211115126141413151379211310125289111210141411721371334386111721041514915731114127961326810513122789111715510385144823131233815411610101411541321281371610108615711556122491214",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "819": {
    "question": "11014581321261773492114491013111143138915941561757712321071364231191141371110141112121543111475109131212139121114715115811119141310733556421541112941438562107115153711091315811251412144111051081510138913106414137111142152948101237101412771051348391121126534141011159561325128551412131421541194471013116963811142512",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "820": {
    "question": "10923611128121241314111048263126765151396495371015112148626481311296810247113413829411131161521018611151034421111101491214127483213611191011511141910101514144101214885153511214158132741021111357794101114415193214775431534631114241211381111141697312567115121013122108114113141485131015941126813113101587876964102",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "821": {
    "question": "362121322141145156141213653719111114108124514101073411215612913275924995143101113182131141211715452537218941321514106875914124241410657143461529211631251510142751313681555101272144149315127610411311279511141112133151214851121110469714131315621031414131011481495611681315197214101211089411751315956811102381914132427",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "822": {
    "question": "11392661251343151154928121511364511214521315381310759127611155810681193712491141455141127154911410813161311968575101112489101514101103512275108118627215164139133611101615111141167132232121191263108141511514634910976121551451412514648910111261314117161931421221338545101371243711498111129214137151248101672125",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "823": {
    "question": "107914101356613114713134781411369212110511131212481310144269141127410551321281412103196942101351413381512118111615142313413109731514210612761310913107512121314139223861110152146112943751018119122131566128310911111421436974111210813561336373541210213561131458113107513615713724131014121111279625141111013151032811113144125",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "824": {
    "question": "15481123112561371411714131151595141212486167143105134210827712921512108141011125641342444519101181415101391012211471189117913313112746514328101141671011381312143513451458154611212111021281014896146571341169211754313106141107212881511142124510412398612121113710115341314658214681115315997122101019723224156511314",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "825": {
    "question": "1271449632291410871351249314131021415468111214611141374191011997212101118131513913613371519125111722101111931429111052127133714102135378310664551331192761510134578812510101211269953151410961166114913121515791561361053121411641738147510106141341281114141351341092137312812611441973113513210191131377513112141096",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "826": {
    "question": "128314676510311611791117461121312137158101012923137211105810661441513115371269115483110131212985517111014821412109113431115652119131161915881271425675861155131134121061256127121491511121012356438141211710741391546261587109139147333951214591081010122147138101115412514193621514711538339613101431415125910124311164711",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbbwwwwwbwwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "827": {
    "question": "11312368148154115216311212310715111334681343619181464157111075478121521371913211135761191012134112131410141392571281197114158610113213115815197341157713714492131013192110152111451112118101410181114112171213155421572511616592813591214249107685141310914721534810121010395818131031691511251471294213312571081011108",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "828": {
    "question": "1217101315110314985214313118111351457101612145913121731514224108125211310111614612397941452621115107312616561249224109143131034531510412116138391063151211149929571131551466710713212218118101271281521614132117112910468131111131541421334139211812111915452764141096513313615341495513461215511973111510141229791381457",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "829": {
    "question": "62181145912713373129584108148931111381513712731152815914118101231513671191214457641110289657101531311156141310511092891271143971014101168151314121982313811141212762310810751173114261410651381391210151014749111212131191027151198642111157594132111983121155125394951041128912101628144103111514731214111358746102154",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "830": {
    "question": "13111315162411375141271051341097111146281315785121028631215614102413715145631413149111514141434510713391011611115121014131211415103108311118129671410951569415103768645111312111251413371114214410107111481121331091113754311114481591162769132710161151431261481315599311141377157612131275912153248151410112341288101195614103141",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "831": {
    "question": "121582471111461021451426131131859147310651521029341471221315108714913213123144111511266141578510571023121011011213763581541444108812971552117926111510234129719513852247415410111214439829610814441156127131555211136778348936471014117529818101443115137181271026111431451561210108121611719121213141341556845",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "832": {
    "question": "42123171414971431315876144121921563118611138213117315313471089154623131391182544103131128151112839714211231111410967213831215131141392681115511711241013794101152122581010121822351147131541665149981221214133117510327881131011413139111414591317431511211619151310147101258611528671413121435410152811141101511312141112621372",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "833": {
    "question": "7710511542112991414111512561419438141191079487612312109214134981021271011105121532210114899113651211156131123131471531043521197114710528134121512101484514321971081795155811141186214112791031115913514949123810512156171653141415211393813143137411811241314971023638461249861310141512723414134212125921311482",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "834": {
    "question": "162131536111137106411213105611699148158335109149156121112136241429128137410151011112315138613149352915111310151191101013391454313513113621412311832101112931384310627131457136721212111031041413148311459112691591071311851149134147425610913141013426885691514313131055149116311215111151411631341312171011102493159717136828",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "835": {
    "question": "15512813539124465161371392615135114346421411414131181563121011121494151813612141065363214121531753147614110739621113281214109315114111167112761014132610741333814914111011473121051131541391212744611714512217313381121254221311346152131231165114691510813383111111210645514313156141098147110511247115112132321038159",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "836": {
    "question": "5296541121015147583910711814448526153104111214615111441054117144821267632141195158215141039641311311256321322121114879161433112295137164712661335811811741471024127111583571396129107139612312214141591111310479112102123526141694125214128114815371212166591543914111315117358131110141212124341421111066114123139",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "837": {
    "question": "614281519391445131072814371514136814109124511914610134515327179151493481211715728331042131551411691512613131371418151164949871411131013511715311571357101293628612147361411251151071421510141710493861265146711141593225103141247613614101121275866914257121110419210388151637651414101215138115101114123106195411144",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "838": {
    "question": "138957911610128314292915611451471319121051081114974141181353121441021514111213556685362111211083141514981321281313131512613477111014131112859132761335939151911013614848611158148513151013791715318611145513261238134107131591241051411519441021215128146151121312115338941110837105132767613159641010351271241415168",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "839": {
    "question": "10713131514493411212281571111089714571499610145849110712515112851112114161134910535113111134981521059122612564281010911113153131410810211561587413684551012414291513714965861514101127147498113261215141013513101521415913131168121361231013121111587613511712525147931485106118129146124514134741128131521714261012113812",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "840": {
    "question": "12131012131394211101186141315108531114132773110761392111112411214514155921213810114863898113245146591381565913124121412122735187295211391262148101368193124104145159131056156141313191213104810112415119835361311231311313156251461291111221214771110123991134241019111835158913147312514112152191384218661103510137411123",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwbwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "841": {
    "question": "149113367641212110127131191012214861535137611514210814153971282151281084127139821314976131012145142111151144911211813131410511612134621593833141141151015910113711341023678141491139736721013289135112101581461111311139651031112172114121051384471436615112337141012156125314165412117151423104987811102111413299137445",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwwbwbwbbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "842": {
    "question": "1313119861127315951121331115952876121213713711119159134581232961091314141110172410313112813214744510711106196101261412151106254158411071221131412969511481457536121391511531456621512111814745778215149111051213214611131513105584683101221213105811471519121014482141128761475561123117131431415141032159101536438131011",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "843": {
    "question": "85714423447161312127311878214613155669395114141148101325667114651091131211023145455396122101313157741510136983121111414251122913941431212108101551291018111511474612107108245121565111081414861265529116310121131111114315861221297391085116136132104121231227111114816812510131013421517936914151226315667458101396",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "844": {
    "question": "81491441210118610561112166213310114815310912121464141315151102104115114785101211138152484963112151212451410139210158321178714210333867149271114121341352511313121110312897151158131261013214241101163491214861261311123110115816131446712671315104128499117713127911108414131585112423158103131471216156813111112463101010514",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "845": {
    "question": "2147651015812310814424385961372631091112107396111138582111581315121387654117310101236104131471211114529141111321592197101241324911855741573121051112119112635814751331104911315121113467695102751510641087341257144981011356101112761271133138895101421131521010556122781264911051438216891398421101110676152134",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "846": {
    "question": "119101515928846931211197512106911241587152101341161931281351054151610813414107111261435107189515117362218142107141363149125713104142113108159616125811284111191423815841311371210159127146210412161313513141081153126125411157531108681118141223147910289637101321411121155413105813151156421427912813596512710912117",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "847": {
    "question": "31071315141098102114912911136147411412814151041171211131161331011321091312414311268898710114143109101211197133421311371512101464114138461051213914283359101310858574121317142813492814452410121591026124314510713111115725238913151212861134158121051381147410511582107114714341391211512131442311510107414711076915131011144525",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "848": {
    "question": "81221411681810951115121101315412711141359118613138948115101311122231387122104911519671031389612511314841215383210115137112151310461485139121511131111013149101113336412425796111281514494146832116103141511248913291011561083151499110132112486151012111581310138431595109876141241131214103712111346415115591126131163151212541",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "849": {
    "question": "2141478514131046112815889822365315414110110369461410151411115129878159511414251131354131276112103481583362111411415712113111097144141015721386635651410371548113571014131314152971183311012121415111413213536107481131415115162121091412447163214679811111334153125431311221012871141410611712315132511688254751114101226114",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "850": {
    "question": "1141213931365781510131411144108346572511323351014109413611111231473131021128104215513691242141157121391326111254810913141573710664111414223314815121349375152610126118121158119141311681127711159711784319101374151212384271452109611614421213412435899484510621221411597725721391511021161331461519117313152114314",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "851": {
    "question": "4133141721510518914116741481013154932125151210115771411133961111913923111689811411145861541014514112143121412894121411732696791114710633551215610414112886511151014411151312121134147894271217146242912101158111231131291817714151021411810149413155312768101231051412442679274259413101281453116414510151221131014101313",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "852": {
    "question": "12814107121161210213441137141251111155361081337512314134891010146311131083155128612914413161511101259135210143913167810114484951011823136391211141149251514132145101171461371321098113611154131271424111671314138151014139121221181215872359141314151432121877466119714695941031328814123211011339151411138613229141712811515",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "853": {
    "question": "13117154438114121056792510131514126469181561311112642891071410214523111310687948121015458109533117412672295137141288313111951413112101041429912141074153191381411215531161015128137241497111217914714514310841338412410237155911114121195581411810721047133811681116121561051113151073864141812812812123124101415213115613",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "854": {
    "question": "771321111153413414141241161075131111510144697287914912151525611115396311101971114132121721485413111331081541197141381351415142112631328116142711119155211143131062129456871056131171511211471115361587314131428191045135121451713391528141321481573451591410571121191494611157351014411821389116735113865154241331010711413",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "855": {
    "question": "9511013681211461014331071351694159314588347128107156141111119141178131326151212104156111085914149513151371231497151110864128531114963115116814512511312414111172139104813610111564513512291114668121169551414111015671596195431178411131492431562752713151111281321213910415351612131142791411102315921531312761177588210",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "856": {
    "question": "4610741411111354148127103611121348145133678261013458141210972141415138671141313721012711911481710864813111781424132722838156512232151114210714831174910142315121138112137610921534111142181011348451133159141914611111631538210310843157110139111061235781121156109131411814921385321215121474141511121389101443642",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "857": {
    "question": "151011189810561171031429414631551121143714487531411144196131315583121513912613141086141439134121211153106512714112121154138141215111092815111121213147521033141497151481210411512125671012131548514112911151061321095128510171054141439137131131112132151351027113844125121312103271111151214152106102875314391246111274871452691186145",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "858": {
    "question": "99137101121367811141511101431215514213139576113713741591368102565141115381101071214112134151221019414112856814715116871281105484135101107514121117827104117141527314611281413359711194213331218964811473101571411621135614313151381310771551412111313894231102910714108661011191215412121411210311966111211213111421610947615",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "859": {
    "question": "213111261441211859153153911421335149118101110145156738131129512121451102111593965725447413812911710214610731421210111241328915296312393101441131351112136121436561012196185911312106731592138931125155614227101214101551310118149641312961341110610211413281411212966313555153659713715114481126631324471214433121161111",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "860": {
    "question": "315577459141321014191610810913412111821514104129101367710141588971431041512142319138326121414158981113384111581163121469191021251326811111314941298111171428151213104511139351010411261571481628123121510101149111451531461058131012129101372643114885910111597109859121116131242114214132739158116121078101397158661415611",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "861": {
    "question": "71612811139514101411948117133615102461141321212232441159111568615121114510710234841101474138111596591210134106314122411112575131921586741477211281312151411104121796104956425161071512827261314514931584111115185101441471312109524914281213811013111148512410931413137111575628145210412117126114131071291153131611314411",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "862": {
    "question": "1412131115893118108146101013710131121111514849913132610111958731811651328312104131010151295710311211813734461581467489275118143111118121071414101113158464153916811712141121312782102113151164123510116121131441092113121571091391141338131541713124971585171126121081521049816147358126124814471315710128113910151312514142861392",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "863": {
    "question": "131415927113248613312151910677123615414101613157101214524127979111156389514142141364210161331477105159712632154116131059113148511312263113839731313149412141176214518910413131421594137671396291447510103884467185681015111413132585131441019106215266441012133158314911614121015892121114311681521512331112138136876",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "864": {
    "question": "512710934691564141763562951311151051581510137112111461025841144111072121351215811610911521456114110127541291014726141214156852621211161581514131034161412535151413827141141251115868491393710111486108713512413101082119438126113713144129615813575147610127931512110210241291213111586116711123141412122161554103872118",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "865": {
    "question": "6119101342113512151292893813511141279156810721911151210234971291051310611441598511154931212107891310111596231553111371014127453121172814151313854101512513613112911107521319132623912512110107411410911310312615145481179410362145313546815411528739136410714412138671042938321045127986591215134128117843109123514",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "866": {
    "question": "6410151411913121211398946713941212514711821413911336947154811510872531109114132213114492141193111313612551163112146610115114311212691441110168153411327613155478111413631131548214115765121115313414211312913148665447151131164210198893710115151446511111327148145914153111031121011566101483327214412621157113695610",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "867": {
    "question": "512912414561041536613410141128731381291411614811791595131763101013621451271413114141511949314912951351566911410611157391214135112101593921481271056741365101186941232108112146122103139521143114105241415286117164714211131214101411134276987613411101512114513214649111510101125156359131452411121107971111012514121361141",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "868": {
    "question": "811554611512586795611159141311253131057115431077123810561495698510631091178111911243131112715148510614107911267113312410144381013621415910157111212115731311614128467914121539111101412681252311159121314321012141031411956678112155861151210135711111232313914631581041239918119105413642110111210237135411536913512",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "869": {
    "question": "5131512121314104217283288101439714141586127151278573148101272131128129951373421024238311411105967101214410910821513115111169911511238676915911169515112810510127887813411271122151255771211761331314413810151877135156114121438137710711112146812734510861191471491381512711105137762157413148311252131177314118615",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "870": {
    "question": "10131035461014121119159692714734121312191011857439611041321471012142113159345710111147386513141210911286154421281495731311172645831131212971037911071228461415544121061361341117131513411313310751151158101476211153813615614131213481586512253111087105121415121013671531181101491399712138253553111310234744101069",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "871": {
    "question": "6751411313671114124121141112814104278565393811172392126815214613742453128895108121491114153121141051310121468399141112156477125615551339221056867210512141413131115119514381379810151224728131491012133101191032611021215514109571114912121911710154141061210113142410111517161124106711981546512319131091161362214795",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "872": {
    "question": "21083311114651511745139143118512351141215114661012885181339111036119513123873241121121115111063139458143137102291111214612687159511061081411131331271152683109111210757561137122471253549812131421592461375151332137115141669542101512834910291411136111139156613101283262121058141371512812103956861017949615123",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "873": {
    "question": "31391269114131101175276151114813391251041421412995131241015581122151312116685794141512131315721112831012537211886101315113914495136111123988106310132469128111142815974310141514425812410311913214134712631531941012761215514141174146145156910381010241131481101214121541271315101291491345212476138241012213151463691",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "874": {
    "question": "136133111211281587155101071541035118111413612101835159114131327141668119461493131213223146611751591012121110971514113141714411851421213159841011914141214134124119471121161431414811175151191274112410111473321367151108111122141514131031079446114613271121438101548155791413636487166894112851102141313112714352411826315314",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "875": {
    "question": "101133649614510108213156111481353513821012611591091113271213321237651264151391011813131452111015149621441012126981464111031356139510115151892457751244147523836391012513411213612153141221318629107491485131231410310821095131812154978913653121414151011131185313931214410379414137398121064115141174785512109311133129",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "876": {
    "question": "9131293252438142761311411633107591215151410121211115881361339746111275849105124539783129411121321310837279117612155181413781554123126212511814211918512614551093615856137131021431112138597741371461122610157611121311113887510910121314561431415968141175210141215614138614128915157913671145141191087641491112151231",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "877": {
    "question": "12101210110148911136263791312214113148468614144195392158911271211134514106442115111415914710851429513311125681392110856438651141212154131074111449133561210752615813681014131415512671141021471334127151031681314151376114287101213152210145348613169881254412109391491316148159417313111332101213141266218141410148",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "878": {
    "question": "1558121214233268197941110131252171568356134415771489651223161351215141410118127114109434512611413123851361018109123514891388116132133105146101111151419128111472781367338814135125492414173863144111211135221221510114289119610124115497131510867124710145131412119929848311341041132715126121117225515641314411",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "879": {
    "question": "41291561114239121011517427141273411651013119105742961214131110531112128249151492132214146291372143715910145481110379131412215651310511971112141554391013665124115111434121532101479131373214111249121314121171156113156971323591012341214815910112151312796144612121488541410312931423111151321481255791315871281014561111913",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "880": {
    "question": "121414175397212931341435129116871214115252113241712991078131281021412111221349910349121161481027101561055671210142134114118141571310489356122145111125369111253157910914105114615638542910116295121391214881141339487102131113131112111061111031252148782813441215113210914111106151321311101410914587411111315141141013855259",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "881": {
    "question": "931111751491022781098112631471331011137152371222911413131584141259211112942813141273814712629111111510115102794125146128121410891115310867121135621310513131510626712168213106148110525910141135108149311610155131241412177134108941124281548141101033713121012941081512175131433812531421013814813415714121373104812814289510",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "882": {
    "question": "13151121210116103713531061425631015411810141612581021481015619311912103789141351156111541096611743311121287121139815131110231310489610131231210149792714341521116241361011361562121101391710115121091114513512129321516138461539710812141428155114510191081371513378429124141181014357511291215844113104541134821061513714",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "883": {
    "question": "10510314961413129415125111167129315121411841031911123861284155121461075101453215613126151235478913186827103610815117212412141312814135110441210131397210115410811129122361413131071276115128971101394671115384191210514892212941011813768122491315914961179464512151410135914104319729671361735111215118121364921561374143",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "884": {
    "question": "111371115823791966141211810615179341461351412112118410889137156171193992155181014487141237613928121014561212111394115144107817115138151213104132351448128313415710972791510143581021167131491510111114978313512312139176114215731131414749128381141091015893311861614122131091522862711753371213531114526101337145",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "885": {
    "question": "111112797581231054121314812621241239551028611131412215241351110341375591321411519611521145109108147835135641714811101321415741212514281392153941110111251311117955152971014853110611104149912815134814625711314115112108291412819814213649311144614751235910813125786514152131415771013311136128875311214391510121041",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "886": {
    "question": "1156628121311951017341155144155413781212851310613961171241531523114119710645714131042127714313361151081310125893361547111423121135112814116108618441114101121371025112145141484131559141121329101516112851212476141211151128510132394137141231091562559141191613878628154410144215392116715651315811312251051312131366",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "887": {
    "question": "514813411586315212874883149101221415461411311101335613471221413241061321258135613152314612948124141178101410212376151195472511116351421158812412255329311138146101121213941321711551188106169531214714810181315248751119445213116111513738111195142134131226214571131456127141415291065811311010551564121921321112",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "888": {
    "question": "4131235141011415914128143829115615412137611015144985101289631414491124158313581411125281111091345741011512611362461211910128136459581112281114376135121215312711101613102891110742613348110111010145212197151339951116151010321328711126612858610134131191291512514111093921414213114124121013956101131143111553147992613124103",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "889": {
    "question": "2411111125231158610101188961014112381451531314711215411118514107121014410112991111315712992712112131510148811141213915838512714943611010714564910147111051113149271021131295241481113121021156781068592141514141117310105151341181268911081493713981591113125712121115491010991432611938254151411161071341589121061311814313132",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "890": {
    "question": "614711131431069877125261235414346115971312156528498119214111513917212105851371112108711615914121174121311339425521015611014534114117792812115321048210964414512211262411012151391214103541512661441212243129461472965813121312414151329910812553613412581234111117710931589141511412351411210431371035142215945318",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwbwwbwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "891": {
    "question": "411102977312139816392131431156851171312118106531013211157131032141538121011451119713121348225791314111101167651152934412158122211141364107951411241136921085154121373215391212561727866713214121089258311141579513411314410121261134148169772141121351576149931271391042421068210114131471451219112931548613109141423",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "892": {
    "question": "3710153576111111281046118141310314215127922121058119143414413131094611122457213811126214781081671351191481491107116274259116813481245121314152141061192111103131553821144101411148912623147141871329710151161341319114126243141510882111164810101593113123159771445104881191131121596141211811104102415657831112695146",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "893": {
    "question": "19111441331557287143910311281411115311551211159126351058104212112761121112146451014891012136119231214115151041263782115149811010141871013319413144116291141014310122131115371126102123913133107415146311121013714911023546132886156121048911114410891131112461236314129598221264141310811415714125111912138314235124736121010115",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwbwwwwbbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "894": {
    "question": "314853122152156621115132103112217514698210118123229457813711311358412132513105321113678779341412271313710511923128124910621471212511148314111514611101387109315313259105151431447121121113125341210873102116715381419101312141458156312221064213913111111214941371389269211147145621311144811887153141192101312356",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "895": {
    "question": "15913312921021951414891411110127155107261337251315383128511541414109141110111215137213583104311379361452510912155342611613714113412116131315410871046521478210131512119129378109151311410631429725723811412131110131183101341212111439156681411214119771034141311514711154733212129514711153989210411133101312655411211271312",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "896": {
    "question": "41415821181637312951311551210953121198111215101513134591212621412814102611111111331514921497131371163141015106911103528138112714185612621381034914751149310816471485132591441149125811131011531021114149121115611391262219134857141011102101394811141212153102107711671582398311121510461096514131421114314132571532410146146",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "897": {
    "question": "6102411177232118129151312610712149119641551010152418111357931436937512131558713813329111415591831137149210513137127144311672131312537631413810118691444713212310912114819371357371413549142211176131056235221413107814711412113871436141129131512551231412154695211924361311952211015121371014146771196101435521",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbbwbwbwwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "898": {
    "question": "8515341081314101368114714829115131031210614154105127713121469131281014813753115121561131413111211815139610537251412147613810263477910101312111161211562961192631121365781461014861121372121474210512313610111941112713515681131412541531310914113146105159744145113742415910131712518141396141113510113711215141112159751314914384147",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "899": {
    "question": "1391575538871013126131061915334914273122141314111135841015122568311591415826143131814418110111255166276142123813111987112277361381585910141411112101312735243513141331391221013141615145254621931215914413131023108151196101311147151567102132112298351533121292141371489101148121459654971151121312101184141579132758",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "900": {
    "question": "92141046115812313875295234581062111213141271331215131141394512111413155106991112841371334111457121511112111101586131218512131171413431356824311510127142815754111013851011013121117113515682413376721211131019858167101475681272461512538101437811914131015523229152141351179144443101215914781369141311011912436371551398",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "901": {
    "question": "151391212158146810106107791531112101414986148151521014136111313342157911731358171410118614626511137119813145813791225158137312346311311714115101593133158469121311571322107144612123581411254147615123775111643851514781399411458147484716931213287141311121915931143512121111014710386134151111078291411155421213",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "902": {
    "question": "82148215103612513910391411321369814114159512761013816926865471481442121569410101431457615134117101264838144106812113722811539114681112119276146351114921011112131181566561214437111128131013119126789154851111251266913154432613710191511498451314121113341211814131223152514619262111451053713412915113765111410138111213",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "903": {
    "question": "4111021355215106112513697128321571416511678131341011412971541127611131225831185114113114121276105788716491571112291351413514138611137921221013151512135561436893137119133145281512111461173114112551311115114912101519146128381114725399787561132512314771191042101411681513310853111281441113151210412311511710615113862",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "904": {
    "question": "71121251611735141221011101312153281074951462121110111514614157144109141311613113824212151210938115124662111586127101351910112614515789514131310311361210661112154119127139147977710111351121313935146712121118101598111431191354131526111101127321011125111248489122101617111413132512413611114811297558214891441223211611574",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "905": {
    "question": "91129781961543510611348329121014867412468143132145101541271015111443784962615133712610431515118857792915885713143103101413451510667128981541313141159612753511281379131414111231551312186512371381410211451315814136649912431312310382713995141589137115315112341013416429111012377415143123115113117510139410",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "906": {
    "question": "1210213911711681410591513914106142764312514415572621412116138113713101562811291322162281351271081111394531421131107131512412441211714957313416119111410741263113271341285148121014251468153444115131512972110691014631313211381467131281451115113121022142111567912138147651131011211614936515128217853721467131104511",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "907": {
    "question": "71513461356131161086121115741538151371210210683112811429913121188147691511213321211313221259710141115133983710111131154146121065121397414101581131256891226121011910116148128913106412312811315161212118494515141410314933114121213124181371511598152271071294147154158141099361364145124141172108610101139121010159131326135141311",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "908": {
    "question": "551399811833647127571141162412313122714841243967135111410915131611971412185431311061412714859312254365101497156121311810262384611152991314104576101413212183915312385915513747611514611015844621139121113141191094214111321213861510462385119713146898117121391514145426135411121391881415103711146318142141511191012",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "909": {
    "question": "1421112612135812110499881041415674113211214110129104121387713152612421531910141314871115861289514131010761398518210146341413138413101111121591096529131061472959481311213113126101538511795871010213541281514123691311795194131365418136572103112678914441491113614355121105435877271299101556568111113671431421111",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "910": {
    "question": "5152862310124511186129155361061312111117963414115121015121341161311191121051461475152114310124610749513588610133111791136114111341115213131123148621133119138101261051412113571211677842611121487933565101451012156410174191312131173141211101792768132153574152814731371295754613511121291415527116141311126153217498",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "911": {
    "question": "25814171142135116315761092881313541410131295151386421101113141311146151210711349812951385343148117815126921141943109697101213461167131231012136815241391121521442129763181365415121839376141598123107956451311361012681215314291313484122814116134739593711413182149152410141512269613148118594610127458612521131522",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "912": {
    "question": "851144103413489810743101112327510813691010984131331121651491311512107125126479151814109312681510102121422431111191451261810813131514811679614101210131511141343263871171526831111359314465561097215148531431311117128561314234157781124213214101575391414411711910161215563293291513615810131171441761181319142115410",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "913": {
    "question": "2159141110101413105764932315141113967115141245861352111391237156118141348512679101092141211096104657211311553384112411761427411387119103437261110515251267310141387118111371213371466157102613145915568121121131011124614371422913886761110142113815391051069342152121010213147135121571285241014141133972796831412104",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "914": {
    "question": "117514314512116121113109415722104611415413556149125915471241187912111411213324151455510141557131113684121311098410715109111651214813101556811069114367131111774614213121510128213214610153121011511512910131437111141461215131314212410810518981412661153913510121441310212311841417515141027481511112111366811314141111105812122972",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "915": {
    "question": "51315623103814121795134121111152914133652314611215121197941151334710123135182151410911111014117113158101261210152143381549244729151081434710136103126910536311481411710145616144729912151115137412141121071481394310148139153411141310571116102415951531084381371110124625314614101513711810131125133210311451271511313671",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "916": {
    "question": "136134102821018314131181312971015510814163713141313107122461111014921111122481615231214156147410814141312544312132573981011412551111811061339546151361454613146139101410324141061114121253961512119116331515364131097412151168251410119131197151391421412281061101310911912261451241510142451264109103977417143911651381583",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "917": {
    "question": "13461421101214721285211123611310951348147129118211154101339591411041361011124259147155214911121381012111314911514141581131210637131577122135143814112141181121415124512113361061211157812311914110131104125814362887914371184131291351210251714101414541388311511291314101386811125101475241211971491136131551381113511228695714",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "918": {
    "question": "514915142810767125313581282109747119761214310128111552781495151451383913141226942103414561135981571414979832431331461512911214141181352713551042152121461191045811212791095515111048141487310104154569116131481281567926543101110413239111238151436149115271012148713914186971311110133121411515781913915251131041214",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "919": {
    "question": "131281031221532414111149711415835139811131296122131410111181091511342141213121521361189521151061314121059499131101481564713144512417159144132412637869141211112226141013448141551331198961211210107103847111412110587158361579114411514131492966123141351491517219131986112121581453151311211056149127313498992812215111314644",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "920": {
    "question": "1581310597134111221284110169128142771115413109102241485135157411112513714412104684151171282141061281511251929911103126118101314715104731391792814125382111564999121787341514131262231011118914108793151311912541471372969412103153131253131581022411141361311125671211111915741310142131269815101161442115911841576213128129314",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "921": {
    "question": "1413248763931111108344913610142981107513116284311552127147921147915109125468111181412439144133155114458312103511611772157681531124214710131131417131191278349510211731475781415321012110951434111813261572153108148576125961110212911014154771411113651313911752108443534710314311151981262121189157633254714",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "922": {
    "question": "91014311361278731413258832113153141174613742127111131413128159713128145386691413715725971413115101367281214988551421415111410613158213910761111255316341512131210108111314533154814667121265227710138541412151211158414341192512521111059831215298133111447111516551481211913126712511487111014153212141311143724126961510",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "923": {
    "question": "9134108611142123723163611132125137143112261914491311511814212415831431129107265351461531496758141313131212698762154374111412135139101311611415241061475432211228914383121176175513411101112157131447693112951410144236812211991521217212133964111110148791011152483610111368125911574131413510721423111721485912612",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "924": {
    "question": "1151313149108451032771113123712145141421068136158271092156431351214313212109111148110611111314132597124435121181532310413712612313221111276910116641495112575211510132837151411492104131152943131214710616831591021247215138131457212131179128157145424951528131143111012773851021141381211154141518128114311513181410",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "925": {
    "question": "1334861311121091142153715102151013881271131111579385311149155121141441218105321011614215101129713738361218761141213111510521139963411122114210111351161163945871514112101328141591144125233991712856137313941411841121375652811291214581610103912111171544115131215104791632714101085121310711115117141114132712915643101085",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "926": {
    "question": "27413312315571451031185114123111512111041379147647129849125131315662541478377111128513144135102114163124718117653514421512131110124912613597158168213371311910121514111514101613112218414131373121510914811425134125123413183121015101114210213574114153856141412581312297111371029121115102121014798344710528151310151296",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "927": {
    "question": "161111121558612145109193141215141011131475210410510823147161314117914949567515131131112299111431357283410710156814827995122398810913612141461196124415510118211714151214112121411028995510743921514125146438121291577838105261325131424217987158104131256312668810498114813561191411410315786109711215111332545",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "928": {
    "question": "231043696131411271575764149829103157111111371054862412891415641331115125149146103134714210114153589141310277511398146914351275565111337153424381510111479513826124691139514101287141183151245122101093956614415514137511624712861431113171394951115104812354131713413611129121413779431115101551295121584211613131012711",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "929": {
    "question": "414121215546819781186531511111083101321474615115667193710414915118991211615741011131425714154131043111914710711138127221513146101369135712236113710492323115512109615812767111410119111352106141143134719101510512798514215126414111388212127113114561351071842101569101435122119410614612117118131011133111427961510148214",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "930": {
    "question": "1510812113951214231011127109510610271114414113146693412810115594811471653101421213148111084144113663712528111131114814121269143825121492368153105313138142243141215861731312121115102139857551221841513111137109148551214141062711131341011275941512864121410615237121071313149515514615107511954821122515571314310941381213",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "931": {
    "question": "1154132638210101812156418914109131114512935111371291188931541013414153111115331071915146934110852137714431112115213511371410107223410131436128115114822555131410812121413914510133497711766182746116151213957131413815126514144101189291116113124101115142612214731113141912551084510311191210910871364103121021433496411145",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "932": {
    "question": "8513512144712766108911761081814152512114541141412110112637296791411971312821214102103451081061512111010121011512134312761111059128175893271011571431272671071145153131111014615101225556810118135108152136313121412215958437512711131461410110133311148977215616648958107122514112631012121514131475810913111571061412181038",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "933": {
    "question": "4110105131221189514143921141315141171310653915144211018131164145121382397106151611121310111395112351127326313611411371495281101399581431514231412116151421241212271314118103819614521310151211412517119631010155142712967514315133919973156513114881221111315141410114122745395511912247916514108155678151231059198814",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "934": {
    "question": "9131139510141761115101531310122481011956141651169431021012141115619813410751321112314321031151361110713119117110101313121125111331385117132106912149842141212710115112812413593101210876455151227111058141131431415471112612158986134471431012591415145810127131351121010101212147215195144931093612141141241011281313241558714316101112",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "935": {
    "question": "12114138171951069111115124561126196141010611413152147115138513105107111013812216449149112613910115131168212111381710121331547675210117121526881514649610261415281117131313734117121036155863142411568101015121113714111075691383415569398941115714131112791014833512521046185312621411413311041581315376110102867126",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "936": {
    "question": "161011672193122151091391441067111529119121111131384121410155131113510712108141315143131581225813482104981711413131251062111159692136137153113710124149254314118107879122127311411695101015441127151271491143131454863811592213912114741095108145471114415358119103125313116144719116612812591251139101414271681263511915",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "937": {
    "question": "91462710614135134158110447121331375512614111510567133812146111012510111641412912713331141151473291066971101221013141510967814115361241413411421514514852127439111155612813671101215186341411514135146111104717159594161353612714231510121613102119744112811581385891262111410101314159121061341142397614111435215121381794",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "938": {
    "question": "128104111141691514254101913142111547584691465117411125815129109221238151411410125161626121383613753145151086559129141341482915145137102831011121212913314112611491211157410514612411715121389141311321421414698215311615210128131046109512141279131172636154813115183614411103812148121941413315247651149104151523312121313",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "939": {
    "question": "11451415131161271063121312116851587939141154854712101271511139147913105961115713331013121471513196385101214454491112121231016783912131011814213511691141075114133115691231063117112215414989141113137771511141246295113121412315128461010312914133119114357314151134108641521344763413814351213711152135274514103108731114",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "940": {
    "question": "11101311223144317106914121967351036133761385471091113112141471014213113461131235102113410146719138147113123597810455713110541111341215148103313911371565811121482610144612109710315118871295586141091423111415129101251131314141011414156512413113101147581104781213159811514291079632121184151125521121461015731166914",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "941": {
    "question": "1114813131059151262101312361589291114547101375101221591029141331153101461311410712215112138910281216237581594129457101315882111414912133213101051559101010815137961211343145152115610103431712613105213315848649131312625711261186914111241413641011131925131261213152912614511138231157956131031483478611318121215348109512",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "942": {
    "question": "116324231011361535813314515117111310129126810101579122123112141311257761211214731024238514961765121211111389102832151147521457642111587519412111457291110126135414121711131111122149128314715111810264871215139514427113141546119125321451211265129213710944710137111112149526616457121339281014781541631112521461113811",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "943": {
    "question": "25144713612210156321313114125911726151083551106862121596131412104112541514371417789879159164113314244132114111081143127151587145136141391211461082156123131112683912118114114106127655113423141311312511159273681214864121314381015510141291521034136134121112710336151014814629121461051197151213814144615247141185108135117",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "944": {
    "question": "210136714111539410689146415131268211711104529157514214118354441196149101212615787131171114131151051314844923142123131178571537865411142191081356152810891517103115651215229811111333410125139141210546115411521142139134611610879874101511214491312615146155763144261614811141212143278134639111013151038112768913115",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "945": {
    "question": "9141116101312614108821454212136231123144810154865125211131091462127121110215861031134591138695151431112211459991167215129393151221141513110761114413313159813661115771110143411171326513115814145121311111012483656641412115112361310711613512715348851114113101294141234151181312261338101474145368159141461101111834295135",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "946": {
    "question": "6101211101424121751532810374129711311121321439212111310372485115311110610912148127243610911431414759111134131714121267811313154549683251292113101215414910136125281731182141254151031211101931134215131069611211491066251181341118713115121436861248911145165134112712107414391278154113564211139141213631214184622911",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "947": {
    "question": "139311442611151312108131353281110914464119151131546211131314841112531315181131271321455972441298656131411141113973612121581181791066721245217151314341496101192721351341312145151710213913241511089123132142117151115213145412141491086241413451211714869118411121114131311512215111281174126141291351581116591031315438141247",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "948": {
    "question": "5410931155126139102141178123136510612114141114215124361313588101081051142511157129121314469113122811514451315713785141062143121914121345811141141511713295149101514212111133761331131210314923414814193158137946131211643358104481279956121107114115388211613111411137612131363615845851027914132963215131115144181447959912",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "949": {
    "question": "1075410211116211521211576742111583912131091111421357131512461348131161011284710910111272123814510461010614810411931012133567131212155710267614821112131554107621111147781510193810614125137613142149711121752491514101311123156513672328146549131571751412141063283147131041985711312159629111431084535272121081066247",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "950": {
    "question": "56351104123158116794581410821412311126136635144710385312151122638131099111321535151392628141067521231484273310561551181281521131051110810294710315116139114595812621125151438111210913141011101232152695849713111212414910153106125102124211131871423131521146985721311510411341513146171312458109937116514822141213107",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "951": {
    "question": "1511711310421214108371391081011311964111414931171491258731121215328123467715721131101191251429106138771441291061511082141451144612691141091510123138138121115561012439271221199133896171512131097811414111461214113127146254141378955811281391315171051118159144311311822136104131593117157111410129916351015475294713",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "952": {
    "question": "151211107212311485641415141267104211186199115531422427111451267598811515214131481028913367411291151078112154714153937334141446103513312215141291511312526121311714751012291523111641386911111587294113154121412251413156634821110973511121111421511106111374151415194111213326133419512151751471110415127813659182",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "953": {
    "question": "968141510135141112172941111314121013911376815351591471210436210114967137171482121212131451461143157910841193471361314861531013811314974324695110814102131181712414125121791411310124108138111161471281242931011151391428101477353116121213141135844127261411571213131141081011574861222715141161210843134381264213153951311714",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "954": {
    "question": "1441114114512101393712141311127817154657942145114956967122141117910614131212511411015310291415811121481177544731572115814149311221415812114121310111414791234666829915912141351319912104411181021069312514781415211111096101314251519421171051512158810131273101091138127691411514124139945111113142121115586105813915861031142119",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "955": {
    "question": "81013125421415531241013351293154111027131413149814123510811051123210138312151714414916132152814151241113121014314624713931552107451113109971488612187541361111149231251194551011146671121591614451283941211121312212214139116217810575113147142651110444144126115759813714510153111241514913265123121913119141210751161532",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "956": {
    "question": "528839141596412951111015253942527129111348105921761511112341014121211183131315101551013411311125103612115961591108812423131011493148834111197114151111145461227391322121471915561139410612144398514612515911278614111291441513962393829111312628611131161161510351315923849812119151021018131141011131056481121211111519",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbbwwwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "957": {
    "question": "831047711514146215712981410651443111371368728101441115813812335139911138415456281261281549511814711815386856212451412514515111134371310127862119613471112181013177124211835261413102913610514913732361554142913121461101458315111071114411811151246981176138121562113541010158137521064119214710411023910151761128",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "958": {
    "question": "5681741012141511911312121210141111310524815931144635231112972121311101310141234791265131145113178101473128914151528617138291353116971111524212514157137814159113510414111415131099248124596714411141223139461415856419811114159101310112885324121561375610911121153891014683114312103961114124158613212131111567212812141385",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "959": {
    "question": "121411108181293685157121210465273181471101511513761216414512285126391487131310121014951581141131431751098122561106710891441167131021494152148551018141073105812137116791011813121145121012312735415911761048810133171114116787215112312311410851111741413156513914834125215147117256101113781394810110871596213591411512",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "960": {
    "question": "1261181539131213914415578129113114142341101314615121911310141382144141213578141526189141441013681436111259731045149681411141271324811132454751293128921112313123275159115614281046913111116491514310714144513286556111121014111412468131471464915231312111210123741011132613141415861210112251347148311010135661517491427144",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbbwwwbwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "961": {
    "question": "49372144385821261331372815155965102129615121315681211397243138212134611104789310954671151476513258710165142112111154213151337121048397586113572142131092831111126111037101421214159315411615111297312621013114961221251588313711581512863713211412149152125710746442111711113159111312141061451118141213971071512113",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "962": {
    "question": "10697812111015912910579314421036131159712411910125673863152717108963414291112131153149871213510611913121012117712361084915527196152111081046242116139414239151010116113132311612132785910881511229711632347121151014831351511611196173414152251310971135410149108113111215121485291056151791112311159321110121413138104",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "963": {
    "question": "34159813111314145786412965611134112210311515953812211061314921513671111425991573611111313143121573855751249101315118651411810426364131175121584733963568151411103142101513811591061241313531211413710593562317144599411868214131115121016891228381389123171514126111121311238115151469104413812614134883211513127",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "964": {
    "question": "1276111421141151593131026110297531213121441091110612101513210412133117141310113139126835149961141412141068105141424314615982105711121715111411112573551915101268738961141273985122135763510114213821054611114819971411393710652461410115152291211814463614735867341014131212108156971414910152512427711513101210128911232",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "965": {
    "question": "94332118121211513971492131101354125151107485139147621149715117159866126113111410310131224313118712511481527991410213583961213372151311814551251016911987111221053913101415914381198312123119101245151367122111386541267135142185103117157591011151042128131021562895111411349151812108141267991347116131321431510274811",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "966": {
    "question": "153581012141153741310998153121115131084613102119641315714111458679911284532131212571510113112234981310142411136123710131514172156131421012611117481721164321191412711588141015121387111211056237317151331251486514111112713141012131113961535116101115449126159961011571315585712341056814118121014910812111412104215376718913",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "967": {
    "question": "6101313111579142141071213641467612102381193591436101314125138124431375819411741561014526281241313102181411915212116771321128512412541092131321211781351177310614192121621212832511514661511129414371151361092815971010541312159661493156191411271012131113971212191432583813841389121113161457323297151251468613511110",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "968": {
    "question": "9471113111412318195513121426289141071510141231815142131164958711011176524114136126531471231311391521514102923111525110141218725151512149213371211651081137156494108221481101114974531536111562641013113671249697715110121013141487261142114121313510913110141115124742811136113465824121511157911814314492211712551",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "969": {
    "question": "915441212132143105109151041453781452111612551571321112961310841494391253861177910611912221075815113141131112391512637104105119610144114412351410194261173411391081512331013511105215512679191351471111112694887122101521248141114951341513612811310834117109851091414102413117812911101413511372884931614111112414911212",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "970": {
    "question": "101545310311328915142298121215137104513265782962141021112310124111475391012112134333413712158141013921413151374754961382813137512134151711101391131471533101259164131012813611141248239657146910475231448151119122413194678105151461012411721031391164812711129176621114101091214811519461215732311315813811157224",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "971": {
    "question": "111101912851117433131410141513411127125116851311147102124354911527155451313116102381439531136157212136141418126411541214373111109612414898410111513513238111415479612910914291948141310511761394712114101111413388711131351439123210345571413618912911156143826129614741215114129151073428114979121510791391715524",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "972": {
    "question": "2119971051183134213647105314131114681214912131141031110891213514965781031231471527411439381514612312111311739513614621312451108731154122311414967415410713111814116914111211626141015137258141647141112214445131588132845331015141112121314111171536722863681410121314692153117411111121369912456103141161181514125112511710",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "973": {
    "question": "4651219813981542414158135611328931186198111113624357151210710111391183341313121513838102121571361169135514118172961101332108938735812567151141661115101233249131181245435936581317102114313154187712561113115791311129324148661571333814111179103122168677101596119781361549110211556838710561014118128459",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "974": {
    "question": "68111261116151073104513101147169115514281241071514628141213103539162651225747310151091381421338311471214314131098514421111157610134834115121021299146151398111061213378842146112313412111013107851283151752146291061542131991119102121059231101291013481056797148111015121041747273121110107132511111159122978154107113131428",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "975": {
    "question": "311491225312136111267151527113612781489413315111158511412912512843141051265811397612141577911121741026211151371291931081536148151311105121328713711349913121961411121089131212110152113117149213135141181146123641441214189831013115411196789415851271232141011213212513945113111211101356109881131015913213612104411710931",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "976": {
    "question": "5134110338411126151131461449121313154510937101133116121471192415761010111521042114511891452511491211413113312122152109111145576134325679679411341410911751341131638112931581031148514113912221141314113106107251241131271456153311142111338814111357212412109101374154110138326451199610327211118121454141386765105371221",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "977": {
    "question": "5515913879121282149886397141012135151123115103103121457131315814931081465482785412136135137715412113149271511321079133414576571514512314618647151128512359151074106122111438159122914101143131512105786113124799108211671211013153121874119124462381514774314914561012817154951251171514866711413126151111449710583",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbbwwwwwwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "978": {
    "question": "1161267141101051324893171511948141296210761110131111121158213458211641431351215101351911911387144107341565421437961211911011334314149371378129101121021396615128147711133985341241512111466109694123539291014157714157108982118313145510832119131014128413833121531336171197651314101415679146812141141297134101136651328",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "979": {
    "question": "214116313751110158101313814711711925103158128283451121391456648131512821412744951169613471412861122103511176211936651389461314931381513210103523411111591021391297151385141585111010126245956584141311122291495101423613143151191124156121113310145136314621215115141094931316213103511211122291310710636265846151011113114",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "980": {
    "question": "1286451411749151125101311181014453272641212438131384725111215611012611153274581319442281112108369141215571468544101111213415879101210138112369145214714643313129881131291361914357134111359271106326814914225851312127114151215461539121410313104822128614471556991013109611118113113411571474132315131512731114",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "981": {
    "question": "31481714106102111324134213714126381091561111262971511610513410145135451595514312236883811715489326521347138111441651011622109211512831410113136110761481421031137194131185614412391071515614110119712131311381152311313710986121248521242311134144917121251216632147371013681528107161245491227552381291115611210",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbbwbwwwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "982": {
    "question": "552361297144108715134121178166210315514112111374714565149482343151117131398681268859913106372515131211136127651591141096315612136149835147343810101452812811761371228101015113414614957111029714131625121086146514315118107131310131417115781213133991410172661041531514121191054814211611195135131251412991211148410715",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwbwbwwwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "983": {
    "question": "1011962711585282713149857105134111512313611412821114101555126411681013141131297561046611231104910138145112759752137410154614321496111085141971032591112415141411310189811151081261412132749141347919881210169251211315310821812335731414124313971481111551211161013561412142778515771391211231491107145381512128694122",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "984": {
    "question": "2118126171413154557383521574732211031361111161273481510914141314921411510113841210251012157118131114348824741011131415275331123138113159410101458978413312291067371114310910435131671123118532713621210811144129121411271411959941589157145148111912116712101161261014157310713841721014145391211121136279111281414101561311",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "985": {
    "question": "91021315111526124121182314113612731586410132595611115865143731581054131112131132771446111121510137148951913123764671355315879101138241091212110155411688351217102946113835123116158131410131873912215101041125124711378614911734783371311115510139312631014912101037821253123752211294159131411114564101513410129162",
    "answer": "wwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "986": {
    "question": "413118673151061213810137145119151291210131436613121149414112111531189495101269111375148612133966119510815514152129332147212781114241071381231445113111191514101213518121264182812197315481111525109141498636131312712671311414275610921215610131141212351110910618147561491511102811815752131312146104311912486538796142",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "987": {
    "question": "6711481341112321041491213514961511894124119818533244767914745915613134124138489214711175153126413124613941311511131111321412136537981115112101031481268911211411131751312115712106912821113612371012485129679813911722146510241159112103713842751511146116291215105683145111510141212953113276551026481411413199412",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "988": {
    "question": "617151396121451191212111573626121111241091310213124121561311582368423711141210813165812611941415714721031241101192851559116141171146141125149378151267137108146191132471071245512136815111114398357911924512668939152641261479425141131138678721256814141210813103156121141129215134107113651413151651131448214108",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "989": {
    "question": "744101313622115115414361481499615117101376111728512101115381132721415116341238610983138173151571414321094513151332141271491312817213641013151113872291161510310851246113210127138210516103517131012313121114110961127461356331221241214191076581311313215911311181021371421159151234873975212155731410111719448",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "990": {
    "question": "2131110512131799711157147213615312541181091891271025151110613142131713414286129511141381229315131359712967510241138153924141215989131122101114541119105315143131818212184215108476118131149511231236913137154286514761144210211531312313121499625105871111191311325144153128101016892714121539131352615258911121113107110",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 15
  },
  "991": {
    "question": "8971310912923815614211110135110141328171315321431193510446131512131341451111513652714361321279811551113412187226359211431021013398155661117836191531013112124148514141512661214871491314145211115410951151812367611273819122915471544111821481013314699122681341546113510154110121314213631314781011153137963912911011",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwbwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 15
  },
  "992": {
    "question": "6151261329117125311143128111421247561121071277123105141371542116102711641414118915359131011214841336152771461311047549811912853126971521097212844425913121075147211314153158921110214131212149141039861313101472146645187921211482113487101415612911510341432812251551071136151287896134211103711131110512513142153813910",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 15
  },
  "993": {
    "question": "10713334171516579116661214612131631239515167342146223131415610161625191517962713518146710113161413117139101131610615121782133168710112106147817341715111314510712161531281621316467113171014216497143310278141612211917215131661241661361491115141101252118121041115859717161381612112101231016614171248115914715128126913137221636141064145151214716613161111191016124943231314111013177837261968381513111716155149117101716158910654341616",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "994": {
    "question": "132151163112451014124816821141791257161310111101514134958461317106114473310957481116131514136418517413914164613115122510141101714879512635511861387163111432324131715121510631311512178771012941412611411082148951661331361198125143131410211166171110153117611195821311101311266143116251513749549173141225531671017615978161131210178151514613139574107121414638151541121616891133134114882715112517111612101174145109169422",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "995": {
    "question": "1551627649510344151312314125361625724811161310111281011421310612131151712741016118921637177713131410281147114315161012465617131271291511177101152369614673141341312411171516151021616122461411548177105398171511811161313510121267311512174916715156141161016751321210169111114331015141710544146152112810516351614141236131897161158171014166817510133131282931127514912171531615139496134683782111310141712114161151591035111744161147132",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "996": {
    "question": "415612121214971111413168161391110179815681215721111431011013517238101115616151698176251027141429132111011391017131631621563543810176467161515141413291511287511114211410671332171216151591195131531410417379146214125517814315101374161013715310691610817212116138161321715159311278616147155152110114951415891355118167161415171366121017143161414106615771254523177131071616685122911149378149161712813152111155362935126131171653148167",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "997": {
    "question": "14131216111015311102139215731591212141116514114148167516114891641514151614912101317137321041812161511561411811468157639172101316121021386251064911144117141671011417129761116152136139101116111934512824141215381671116513616141791074146171610141451265122111421142141813171276166151051213146514416811821317796717116612911161051231410293761252114812410166151781458143132101013126841161221010108161114471552131261151371111154811311221",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "998": {
    "question": "74910217312111621711361115121215365121169211131467810137148139711754111521651413118168156217141699101617345161516151091317143791235171594421616131361129921261148147121552616317111659157131584141451151341572310141412713969215161517131591107515129610491324164351017919815151471517102132147943316411781416315214171321667128917104146163126151115291113131111318174245156107101239955148164111433715111171387121381461511353316171012",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "999": {
    "question": "175164611121010132162769517917826112161091631314312167310171215105628161523178316315113629415521281112135210102791817124661412975412211415121113331321712121141410961111051661165821691671195171431014351017429121612715281161214113116151513101756129821521126721711414141210575310811957148741131571212168179151351052377614181043138144117312216971614851061614971516136411575310111413128613142103917516131537410283117155915",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1000": {
    "question": "13912496616162151141158551647710989141222131715586102151481213732712109101013171638195166111575213171071102137156314161110109172561324112171514169143311134106111498531741037911217131114834158151265106810312514316141516136151141141759101516586111413125151364516310103281288717194109151343758171621565914163151188133131517121616568131231719721583111315684317681213931012131671716417415512141069111288101512214217611411815163",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1001": {
    "question": "11134583958628719141714161561771653241291098112152810176169174314981115167813144101171191174611641415491712138711271156514109715249161091138315671614231158439212315104461121214132151698115116101251711261612149367713415119314861714114151125151294534141047171061611153161735121411175111513104101621461715981314131021481211725813611281111417199715411171563106571441621016121710115161314991271561028612763461291814131314177",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1002": {
    "question": "5921162874173174156112162717131210151731242511144131386159167171128141616847917141013151321171251011551611113153178614321573121513512613161210159661617671015411516212108141153916161038271112135713217158103217171014161116681386729453714178915151661131281227166713111313910121512116101173151461251613161155943131141017616133716121691521721010581361138111275151661613341414178917131415541811491531027234171316512414471111641",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1003": {
    "question": "1131481762145107311116427166121254141315310911712107102571217238916215141521371512651068121538175214166101597111411138121317151417241681351258171111491243816101541161314517161111191038121612131210147281388103146415781121692161141571611851413175131247121141241371117216115914631741512315199951611631271010714119179181146126513141485122563191041116121129517141315512152314111661735158710129112124316111016131412916121747131151011",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1004": {
    "question": "4289951118151316174101288152869412414311716910938211325643181266710914741794510156871131677101412841516133151115171078121647172125101041381512161549126636716168412171310612141416111721234158814171610151521141410913131151016121514171381721106411111311410311517914821412751151613967104168211472331771375111098512261361612131351687141117415131497415217913121511621651413123145161628177122426131013121391434691351310168715",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1005": {
    "question": "109125481461171610473119416591012611263141514137126121158311591273101714488154113147381651252101749610151421751111131513161012544510168215139161261414752151671531041111414213737816216213513413911613141151214541312162176131681013162111231613101651741698141378517941415172131261473313481110861681115215811143131546135129482111512414613191611161614485317155811151011214821331616716171321614513610483715612136151102158515516911417",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1006": {
    "question": "101615111411165113134288310491610103123171481357613191587139179121084811411261611143481111617151291316734616131615178129102131414213711161061417435216101610712151092151441311517129711510111463713151566215171412116483121795131031738214112131112781011156916546154851310111216149173814117151513751412911101051314817651111621539261111561514316101716751411321441113122516126111471631617161410511984231611151514151771021341411379517533138164",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1007": {
    "question": "91399145449111713712810125161714315921617133624286515316121710891497913814942176141513111016213157815121316213161251051711161031113612141625137941131711913129271711171431641039111014157161541661517131510117161681112733131415109132571798121422131537146161334651411954101642111716414510171316211145917312861172910567121594111416111179310124101622138257146141471611165101331514171091052791917613348111516812310817468815512132153",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1008": {
    "question": "81261615893177421271141751915148326311411131083121011621315987568311161026231245117111415581115142312813115571410174171085910115142131411961214481216119751441413131413154101161776791154212133161516689141061757913151416631316128152511462941011771029151211810411135123176149101751311014915161278113221441211365761711107963111572391169141582210251111135542410163161114917491114151013215108335612916101041411391210617151358",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1009": {
    "question": "112111112571174885141123859611146161311121731441253147133741215881217110134134121011161578176165311146121614911110316269344531112274101489151181151615696153141532135411131487101613121686512111621071414421761315111814103137212616136117841371651141542999738166149145451612111710784156713124911121411591113114141114210847131513128114545893417101121616715104158212313951410166115111610454812614314151311161417115166110121151361181796",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1010": {
    "question": "1271081314691341179865151112171315362941410351012316141231151168216610117417341212851541012214819101686151621111369135373143141191257102137471691781216157106131217112911541514625109634212816157114101671011294615755166313112713141310143616173121589416171611141113451512266368171693101138151387212314554141663127101381016217413138164710141511317212145139315117118277129614161015111517102416716136108129141513141216125111115913171314",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1011": {
    "question": "156171215138314113114716110843176153913171251421491415106151311171315118151466165981147451410312101521081121031612151111315683178815436114108521779141412141148138111776141015413111521171278103179864131198101281687171215151614212104119717616145216117106144217158163151412111211517434105141656713151116351467911216106616101711161316725711210414926872714141613691441216101177893261117786159924141051618153710123144172712713",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1012": {
    "question": "31121321510854911141216716102111632512714674891345881764391211152165712417668161239121454241426114778117211161315645111356141291015178973115161398121107111317461675391423713517610141412891181679115151412101293111611115141015623101211214131414211945913663121414101781612451531311714112517533464893141354161111291012141141681145271296121023411217111262161378459721713114914116101435715612731610549101013131561114127",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1013": {
    "question": "41661217155101511147131071411717971516111310461382128651524151714121011133716710142831646108111512156146714131491231224131511105109212315171415761513864161287711113915425111016143108131212313761416293692151141381812410171665315101296128522163791111162812215912511715541216141031516101487134641212511112178914141011135815112476110421510258239611141471112117511356261715161498164581261151491231014171421031714161891345741621310",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1014": {
    "question": "14168109437161311715511154269131412171168151753169611054515121259179113531711211511184771396191615168121371191417102125214751574613161712119821010413311516181214155141713912115163117714516131257928131111101151616321414675103121414424551116215151213167313512826810109164171511516101179961011314541521713865134101510914112164156561013838917165145415152384101414712121631361344172169127961815151411691124101577632107159",
    "answer": "wbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1015": {
    "question": "142129674171111139315617617109784134145317661516715148161291111611131617371017171510513101171647141486310171313221014471112781710131214691213218161141768310156417931412211256813496311142310101631714515171221188131316176410934932518710159110131251175614945163171591511511211713512136214314149961113132123516113613111210514951617131112471681494101092164121755121611321411373610215971316412101551313145145141613311172814976152",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1016": {
    "question": "31316278141071781176971613381211951717616215101514521310414117411639161591317101576133814121651942111631454128149161231191613672410971014131112514961143121216177510141316141481357917161314161611153114131368141311359821710129161511712613510674531163522167121616417121511842714917815159131371313521131336131012153117141617893161061793151321251281114411415413291210261217157161634108102141781513614417893133810115147164",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1017": {
    "question": "85716121074139710155171697129171214181562101681462151459311381417101341031511416151141362617111394117314102169115147615678821483159616104562171115414126912214151310751081161576111212410921421332131174111285121615916161651614111541110651013923121121667105516171694321538101529717851635311041412571079445461416178161213131074161571453141273121136812214179111101559101612417761335813161521111410515517105863121381116101442",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1018": {
    "question": "162811915313121410517312181381426421091169215137141217251129151314661310131145810111055467113615121581416541413166371017921261371614102595612738451365159281123111019711561014110131011614482914177981117133315114125141146101191526811435101312616114613131111298151041651234891164101512161113921014616410311612714213171111879431179821446113111221021111714128109615281517134313121543817978143654116915111413171413214121513756",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1019": {
    "question": "8213123111513712101525161437961664131481715151114510961517146144171312253104131523141361141238159117151633101121751215142613411421233108176146113164871318951512421531091561613216114981411351124122614151131213162171613569812111836127410148139131314214171291161489161071111731310121513161555311814616212961472817132514413101112141814101346116111715221112131561510101511428164741612959416615610129347174171087131238152161171461",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1020": {
    "question": "55116151710881514111125123126101396417144713817111581111225131036473821012937131681541786121511142131789119371453641514111427916411451012133176153171416211101661143851511681451031714111684121516912121281347124410281493179151115713127617121299325104131612831732413152915412911643215891161221310175101389451151311131762129412716513163611981512516127211062141115173916310139341761014215121671052181381515126121491381113761",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1021": {
    "question": "15917121316461041887710931242138149155761716571115196171016151413752111645166671117241294141015138159311126614510356178211187931412141713167212514241182127216119151411171116131451510413381511111116671516141151168211314972813121615147791532151133131711291487131215814616111681741151637621110391217144131039118142131612154110914761611121251791528113167151695814251141212510952711781210163131146141716108116917821311799131214",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1022": {
    "question": "171141638310113136152127151571496417121416611103132121316109451315121752361411684213541651514711161321010161351412679831711117881211166102481551391487958311214163126112617131273710141315961916123514216117712143515121111741014141317151311169431051381136413147171143101078123912515811171312651714512109851011163687101121613161511422941131351626121415135241871312175391510106757441012211613212314951749375171116277161015106",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1023": {
    "question": "1417125871627139115124107814251615119210132517371269771011514151486151714310212131096111417184331516131115175977414105815211661121912417811314102151241215662711104121421611513135168121315671211426104213157114141109141117126161416121117431291441610748991510291111811281613133717125431415491286109177131261210121513452415112131681361014121751374513212106171313169102731612785116111616837241159521011610141485224143413159111231115",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1024": {
    "question": "16101126123121071551514137174372151097131412818165951710561610210311861013131521410581261414134911316111568331451124131529419514315106116121291211215671791314104435812131511231327121115166161410513613131614161139211151016517721641415113111010681414133151413171211112336587148121610914125611441310811136149585141153238161210101112161217914157131693612615711191710134316131314361215613381411145109144217125267128141116316412103",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1025": {
    "question": "1771261433913916810211257931451391621111062515711291712113715511916156410416101613511156157161282916312395109522871313121411613151243217410121181575816817715712484510214316491255241538136171171434116217161110513296126151048137125317139541012216671614151249101510584106716814831017111515111101051310111368116122141423517227821052463121213151275491015167144141191617519111743131612152146821541091310581412152914713",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1026": {
    "question": "10152147821641971139115115155934213107861611314161710111013131081014812156361341651613136144101562123817126111441513101591792915149131711163105345147151112217879135311111412101681371182723985441122659610141315141631719121310214113612679171315138101611777121710126181663213148121644351217268134911131411121215165121179662878161339815107143147117916345213115798161461751273810416314121321110514171016121014235137168984158",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1027": {
    "question": "1157128141615496531079131314721616175912152111431611321621212411514617128910913125101171615621341513178512159313112141315472106510513179213121416151315781484161123317111151099111114132111415132481510765916191317151213111641411612234171351667753142891310711114952910172371312342713107186816945135141213981547101035111681721243610914949135171015126116165613431572139312171087281151210151081439315417111021113531281373214112",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1028": {
    "question": "9116118251531512413665131013161275177219815816641581110141213415616291411777314124123653113121595179135441510216781161621731141221513219113105771114410151363812931612112141456313141413108421152981710261875101611101334212571131612911441714982151151099614361051411169712151716611313851478810110136997316322151310691211111491777154133151216918106121514177121613273911101481796139641614234121345511875134151791691141236",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1029": {
    "question": "1114910215316101173831464810141213171211111615173523417481011317216145115612210169114151341311141019541541010561412910111331611717112824371076512141611111612571716122714315413101195961616778213111541414101371644121111652171531491614429101218615186510141361361489515371252493135151129231712510616341132111038101241616816137311133356798161037111217151283161115177510472141116149115114216638334101771621714531141613122107141212",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1030": {
    "question": "107313491445156511121658121046102816521413971114794103411414148257759851512101446177171623981192811516513411115131461016710143314987121163511151761713111138921441142164121015514136111151716171113313712158941751615614114711848712101468123911658185163711104146151731219141151761613106581327122151116613108121173102141517312158131711101164641315587461311122511149216148341632151051613610117891213141114173121315113138151112614",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1031": {
    "question": "14111151271598425131331021314101715516715101561221194172131691421141014751085315716171210291115118541231141517153121451181610166716516119121715122198141010841410516921171431261518597115421011117151641681113119910146541711785215329111351191481691017154121216104815361710311197981111281010117111451671132168101511716113112131731416591216101834161021413111415121171221311516151419153111765141112710613911539541411421111354914316101715",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1032": {
    "question": "771648175921243141161137114537132121214161781016616434128564717169510111114141435151683124131115921410158113512121328644215117614212113155216110167831176131494714159521116121181312151621516811471341244210861117151371112107141698113102711516712815174321514142121041110131617141491696171015983141611141611165131654110413638153141217141298104514314961411162124128216147639211149531051276615914161747813815751224431211146171513131010",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1033": {
    "question": "631014278610124131691644728493612911444171051231341316868395147217810141658163417414121316121151221088161311151517154615941121714215951031616574101071659812161721614121515104131131210217166994716111716117101417712991315263131715109442147161112114731581412171016101381236941416139711121241548101531386316131114374161231315161371672151591111217108816921566106118177131413155177119163413864141112156141415719434101312396",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1034": {
    "question": "141610121515352961721497575211138517369123151651552317315971438631671215151642613111112431065911713711111615621012129155310981416117101151575326710153114112161517121013714912561061783161694926613131161212859741516111710151143162941112151086731621812138411416915157102314389153716861411154131352452986131011310151012116111515910311121431661682179141234151010316717121198111421216101517125229151661615176310121178213211465",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1035": {
    "question": "6893141594673213115112210915121016513311108171446731481715275211016111439146715912413102161210121131538104613121221108513131116315121012115161211131116471381265161311109171513821493911314147415459617161841138651116214121071510311121153161317611281139752141795112431616137151112267111578914111661781213167416131142215311651249810177141324613331091161315181213117817251613141669151212164131215410152611106177131315913168671134210111415",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1036": {
    "question": "2576910111371716811144111961371514143101176117124101615712321751131514661847641689251314531012121431131711141644121226101514107151411192313813173612212179125412788152131151051736114133112142723811156121445101315371618915173111151323134161231675697381741926614171212516142127317621512145168491016916519412126101532175541493121510651211163111381255286101716116101115911451381011711481569531661718291541681710151310103136",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1037": {
    "question": "9421014122413716131181493134121614151511131683726413514837188101121512913126816245111073679175716212417169761141281181654611431121049131264684316161010172493514121116591771511125641315101261114161131029751297171166161117131146177212116163571012101657132314141061611134237914914121531217161331271116171310811414658149121211285161641314171311101715108112122614915371616915173249511416131389715103616127117151132414101316",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1038": {
    "question": "17771510136141112412123514374121514762181517854111129161117761513645151025541712147297610161411413481618176291425141511516131716696141215112138715159465111410142612873513112101771151548813163141315615561178321312985164291614211133315516781218648213101094614213111122167610743115981615141213213171121565613165419101443102161942811232611715115101214141571611112212611659131213615541651441191373311716164151039835261715",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1039": {
    "question": "126110149327173410975112938110124151171677914513416108574121121131761133117671041235102132138811171638815441271514104116127791143816151446141021316912121310531516811351413715171091415983219161052194716116121115171015148810164121061771416973611716896312133171056117215751210168151176101224813616341581415176101213162171014251431376117111512116691371262138114315161410171511921319104771698512311621614910113679141776",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1040": {
    "question": "1621535478511127161417131217215841311157121016391612152144316310165421613181731171362841097142165141161791216734541411102414587167510101251431711015981043171615213784281515125111152278121639410614810125256112317108542178122101199141112215155191451411142114131614717312169151091363173214165511151198131410166461311513217717911817146111515163122126411617311369814315161222167142116517826410133991326731014865717311215",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1041": {
    "question": "152715314561611156104913811104516316610713112141517101413931710416159947611284105762131171481981415110152121117158671541335138111435691316771210110121516131785618431414101415715614141521411101731425317116169625124111108661161710111114491012158713121037911131242413156616817171664912113151411137161719128910101121715515166693715141112151012414317141576914131761871110128571511121158161713616910611152272115101386101411097171244",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1042": {
    "question": "151791688731163911416239155106421016717142111869151234914131779151581013103811510391712971261131516152512171261113108398171147413161116913521015141512752813126161443146412181212610111315821313516162514217743685411616911123564632813112361477111421121641516136106495234311912711651361817310141131210132531088751616415314311148461551116711171261311111017148168791415510131315171615416741123616912116151413795812411034",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1043": {
    "question": "31411213715813611239171651167141514835341013914141413775151714151212122101116121117621112710368141315345231565101615713812114179310513161015941613172642124351610810561121517149147171033131411261011151710156814211633473171910135151181131141213112161410157411917146415162161671338610171512913771051188167156314851612161598132149714611917163612141513127161086111610841315117910731211929151766488103115165131471024121651416131161513785",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1044": {
    "question": "41231416515997342106151361112111716851314715144101021241310111414581159153111076172311231381013119148713114610111616592153712178101349441412161131715161571183124571012411713231372816821641249101151138112142610791710451643671611451611131238714101716821571114134810561215341291631112168214769741591317510478161546161211219471411104139317153116163214166111537125451088111115511491213164111314917681491261012713111153241410",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1045": {
    "question": "8169351181151162146108810516111213121715136143317213515912106148173151171581714916915943111313612821331381612153514614111243712141368171399111651687161348712681117157109911211217816561413131671076106281317231417131241051415157812109481275314174161711121615113106138521391323561571432881161511612782854161112910171314311110154313541586791212191210137611151721171284107461451371310914213815216154371014171611111213182",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1046": {
    "question": "1689414341281115510612711413121448115510219617131645851516152148151017169111661351794121710151110310169175105141111581656311144119610134101757112147141538721151381012491710515148181092956101613161215631421116161291131314768581791131489144161291512106115513122106612951141431113101458121121317161431513711561610591513101415691113681713151410281692311413157642241135155121431514110310141111113323415161281111131678354111014217111612",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1047": {
    "question": "164965121181316617721414871312921481158141811416610871612310414615217154917198151126151116414341361310141213456121816311156251251011146115924814871616106141511312101181281910138161251016151217111181314141252107161101114491511517495413147128171186651910271121310512741313129105141415341713711101215223811102314168714815412541131741110113691116815451517121311617116138989103161214771361117105147993881612412989111413161612241081116",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1048": {
    "question": "9411141614361352878151212414711481065101316176153114172516121314101331527991014417101565116161215142811388426673151116127116479129351315841613251115861312821516167102317129191211617149421281018278166135121293157516310145215193414114488761321412151041571321586431216121531628511833121291466716151251787941415162331311315254916109111210141714112316716131561471101241327753124101113611141416125123872129141142915469",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1049": {
    "question": "104101732155115913516151101512115163151196791713913516215355121481121713106241671191012149511612432131463191111131014516126781117312594983151010161111314813521517261243615146371117741231311216113148105431410119151121714875664912152917113991314941147158515911271563178112111516915497169101414134111515123131810625281216147164171136916111415516546101712113716581451031511217419629101521369147115311428913171481164631152163115",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1050": {
    "question": "8111621691117716141717107416114391341061511714813117511416812111776164791621512214163671713919128116101531710119141011216121611135133510111366214101191386713722164111111731351514915167610341116131166213121114351512171312129610614210131571114691217126131216315981311273131514512166149151117715161542121511141226871192261635341016983166135171513916812113410661213621516314874161217311510111563512545162391742616144514831101371551116",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1051": {
    "question": "1393101521315410161419116714889131164317108151261317134761314311165101612913151561438161295341738111811113139131041516541017711271021364589818213152748571911315814861312101691761129413315111121364172916115131525671213831111318476161031523145169614118125108113331151721410158114911739651641531612133875641381111714937268111211107128151610162141513148348511161771344851617113672191314151012121112491079113735121415",
    "answer": "wbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1052": {
    "question": "346335211410128721368115617108361121014125413751214652141623510104215231151214941261041258132161314171166167312958101211265116617215107813871271613121172104591429111534516959145131612631011411179832131712457414351613371411013712251615863912122151541611107133166101414991093856172413151114814315108156412116139139514611392107148951673617315948712216513113921251065148442171649163841586135127513415821413166",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1053": {
    "question": "981217137241651361031159101511910151645632158178611614217711512166314313412112538121410961355151715181311913711671431095161221084615328510171311111516132911107515814726122115410977151615111348121116171375152161989141243151281214121261353733912101314381611141715122151710411151610145817107129481475223131216115171114151084173131514411311112121261165481411510366110611113712142165889410613115111271910153121462124152811144",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1054": {
    "question": "35131411715510251161612136141715911348113121116131010712961316154159107163172121514127138126441510133217517114584111101510166613896109835167158132141211111161610615151212238131115141331517481256109121115128144101281310141411481715515314715111314210691744916111541111315617147951315164181215101121184135119517829317211131681492117135478106312341116912510115215118415161351237156910171013781616111121711512143916151661551149177363101711",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1055": {
    "question": "3410121715251615716811431751011139126312158281734151771341114152911313168810179113610813895169127215814410111364214951161113101651013151211681636241771313112169851471461231716168329191312151181049183161314721515981331017161559710615171111421323843126811597111541710122115162151523914812910611141214111116313731215912105495421110116571716151771216174151311116138121014722781598410121761411113163121617271316811013124257",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1056": {
    "question": "277121315511017781168344168171021513151597414696475493171381514111010121155141127916713211078112147811529115716151664143101061457154616121314179817111214169131357129103215101313101615173101212749141151743914112117417101613151621741512611061651415197426111412731101117108316892517910171441615161359161417144168123712129111511141698116111107349121613531074812171511616121132131161713315778941617101491451371616691213101241117",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1057": {
    "question": "1316151531316127413111451649131111441356710111512161688121091710688971421431518917153142671312152123438101713101122151499715471679614178313231246141991741461312111614215129145143175410174101428133177111215135141410153129917611131314161311121511723212165921243127391351186101611321110131212154141312178318871115148911874174571312615314117259149378101414916834732145101171696124511113913161114151711671237119141661047171131514610",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1058": {
    "question": "12871161417713151112293472416148115171015122738491141547128917132131611101661121917103351415211154981069162101314312910158411644101311578114176814594102156162111101712894153159163128163927157171413512551012715132631621115121111153123192841410513161515118813310571614137914216105562147123131131566176131141112216539110115141712311411581556715161161335871096114871111122171087279712111313146211103167128841129710341513121",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1059": {
    "question": "31186121314581491616131715121317814161511731151310955466162383121111171521091015312111412425216917137161516492384171515121514112141532171310119741096186121651353129267141211148411557101014813111063168141396115171016914938810931411151313612515178410161528143110991515613712126131329158116171459151631775135912108151716631610101417111713412221081381415111614161074131768111241615912391151711613314101471111213214910357916612864111513",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1060": {
    "question": "11149164715355118613121021841714812316710910615135123141189414131616105415172827615441314132151239164841610111316417146715131414141691591161711143124247101731255216111110783992131291571017143521413121211410739135111213431539514161115617841317111514101332155111312916821415163137496413169315139145111510178161311141051413128117142153766138479101111788161211153131311651011616791313123524101510781214161113513910143161210428313197415",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1061": {
    "question": "16117591535786112911411111182714316576111710134101311121217814515413528711126157451310711149841719115413111021311416412156331314312974881716151105191213437513115410142166310189131741112151415712215615111281916141012474551363162176910131481151531453162610176138149151311771101612253576814151210679164111217125761514941101710141615131072212331713983121113141210515415767155623916745101614171112111416171273561211310411411",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1062": {
    "question": "17311281591026141371239816114811112163161527911014611673521551712101192132915111651021743111357123412537121314141349615625226175749910568815361915711141461671349171255111015169721312416531471316413558174142315211371087691016163131115151444163167112513971575781114105131546913111131432177725991251071551613511351714811131313146471321014515613111115171149381137614934610132151799317138411217310514169118157961066",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1063": {
    "question": "3121249149101311621610736139411157168691417216313514710161111177825391136312172131481435977159613101786157101612125161132139358812267916103151711514152161771111311105861241521421116812133681489153107171314391135107101516465113111317642537381417971661514161317115913121078165158149110152914614413512171014112513642119178133147953156912812412186111132759171411413981031612108147116821016213951414212111547106561217115148131169",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1064": {
    "question": "41448651112161513162175101343161715441011141151215681711101564752143116823101514162148171335771214131413115512673109614141516810712111646167141513105217916133141249118271231264171711151262411161365161697519613314151142717916121610429151141012174813151214511413761416779810117359113121598142357141271351614161715141475614149710872691610131217212165473151151616101715821511014161112415910174112611163111111013121582512161109615101132102",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1065": {
    "question": "107143102111261291715413115810141331177812151414155791762643109139111211141511151335106161645121593711141151361225175681110313105123161481017151216349129410161169316512161221241511171514213131123674103547128114151314261773711911611179841351415912141636111125981513161381011214735412151354177131116913141337121112658141691611010311615793412216141712813107151416101758106266414121516812149471010139115146129613111213215731415413168",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1066": {
    "question": "73121716113144101513125148165651724910154131481391137541615891111217421515132313517411712910151461321111981631015131015117641614141016127121543186155161713175211154142671212107115513111711236151114341017166614921015123917384697151417614111134351113161210113691610215816121441387343781321248115151115104101681112591712311671413491413151141763816841551421668178951011131141237111612151410411132164157161961721652613414910739161589",
    "answer": "wwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1067": {
    "question": "461219151016156175148151361156121415214910153716121411111632411314714681549109217461512591121911516137114121691511218271417513147559131861521641011981796314710161691591454499111651411336141214138713105728112161341783134516151310131413171117114512181712105851471215371113141276811151415176151652931381211574245589144610176124148173101011161312175151421621131413817998151076189161510135682617671013141145421631541310268711",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1068": {
    "question": "5151110861112416131411123161011149678761613213133101512312171216119161065167169131311113545314169101291517118135931478631410101221614911031555844176137976581513672281324514114764313215812416951063516131498582111412141514179171474111081215155613161111262510121016103912715413315841411129154541617221416151109177416263451381183164101391711115111445493631715102151314781115162515146171316171131284156516173841171316159731416",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1069": {
    "question": "715141313791241117648171127410611314142517168169991631017161311128515461111110831541121775315136141511101784713121313114165214251738165491314111158123631351691141017121621171642615132333712111411917111161241382884151099211131716141623134105936871415103451415129106151345216753212117151016107121312141091711128161567116151614351113819121517611741633112891211431411582101347101316645142101339121121483111147151651513552981",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1070": {
    "question": "8314161491251116611872171371791112313115811451214619141751411171458813164411213861543271613711551418134510913151171295321865153141617104141382151571115158102105317510146131210517267385122110691651622149181037101512131111115514164261213191175610516132128810914231116451466103713141514169571121412316431621741591341611102135101091716649287139113191115674177461371412181613781261211517251215109341511510914115712111691062",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1071": {
    "question": "5141116141513111041271092161741110151172112137896115311487131411161521191181017671416165113111110112941561514631178211916121017711410691542513716410131614121312731771617699711214458164911317101410261413591224517316914812316413381513151365168116348411810141251291162151314738162101216171215108116161456141332134158141016751116112161673712211513171212415141614813102168715131117158129144167131431474156882516101513811191412833216161717",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1072": {
    "question": "27310135131163114917129916710728975731215113111112161611014101156381699423512121154494710148101710151312613119316171358104742111591631671110141710512139871541331612513711741631465871713216911712151311217164811101271481611035615117116149510482143671125913119111081021637171510613134101712710121511328413615141127117549510113898149414167316516151011951112171181792151510141613111131031515571411886971621010981461415117117136483",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1073": {
    "question": "16651151131659112141579461617131221053109813171481714143167591388711111101626947145769155312192113114101541486105173921411369121831412785815134749162106161281013111510721181310141215111711413169511771615111613867316881217885715311151591312614415117331212631151413112165811361521248141251517911711158915121674871755311310410311514112713115161312141191012145671616151311131061641011517139941114812533151261714913788115164115",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1074": {
    "question": "112411961328157141289108151231413431610171511112132816413111165383112172144101216131511513575101662413152641210141312111314951771064118281564121316671514171182521194141411107613713721349161463101657111171437139101567825143512598816231771125133614316112133514491071771113815414168174176931610163117810123141761521394356168315761316111135974813551015589121061673142161321115141110112164461316113311177131541071256211837",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1075": {
    "question": "14914127827111013115151749712111421539101061768916116914131671514421777610521561411011151715716169458249161354361106111671513171413314661149915261541567111716510116319131583131121538246295111128614135111291151411421031617213167142566121581091016524101131315917137141211114162338713158115615211831610496128515653141711151571914612161323481111431612111751349215151561512131325412331141057169610152241381416314111613510",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1076": {
    "question": "129814316171247161361011584135316107215896111411161139159310175112274813161011113617712772549101612624871621310814167121215112513161681112314171573101210161556138141589241761217141041121479515161113312516151381691511104171311127710107413331619101214851711161781110619821374563155813129116151343131017166789151117101238516109761416101228111361365158916417137171141851669632111681637191213171162151101014214351541610111111178163",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1077": {
    "question": "76121671315161513149815173156710105491531316817137141311136941510102754417162127141716451711693651211167610239612943131125515893136211161116112772173810151129562377111101114717586131615110269125216101515610871371119141735917517133101621441516973106112711581613354129151291146131462531012121421365961137941741451151711431312101456781611112213101651114417415481175615121132161147141156171210143961724111551610476298",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1078": {
    "question": "168151613167155174412141111116413315214911111012158147177552147103138415719129214176541181015351013116951312121155142111310441651216114513315104514711386281475512131213114193114682161519113913212161017161716812116157516112681531112462816951617361213101214161641213621101117101219149911511114178321641012511411416915127961583855131215151161213710518823915121617910813141263374111013968351212717161711149415313710616146512135174",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1079": {
    "question": "51416137611015104183111210151310651191314715381548438161412141492513915107911264102312134811451615163151191102148141311412141012891041211167101381114617111057147106541514398213747114161381413695217836161512124791152510113142101955101410163862415871614149293411127121388651721315916511381510774161183109731511148141491056912421138112109165175114141111516416365157111013929101211810417136141391633587217815125711956131315",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1080": {
    "question": "12213814258911151113621716156289164178141151213111421615122214395111716816187171010816131211379914291432131512810417111165101352175163812141211561651171361315592112316141610812114151471310261217191613151712116108139110142351621512741515311153214129617310315101141213641281371191416214711617101558726143910137104101571151412298121431256111617791167134881691421931012184116452107125114111631398151544151111171171121041515104313",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1081": {
    "question": "13811162145171610813157181217382754710912164916131556116121021911141641514171511131059414271761682123161141481637917510117146154161211481117151314134169101529512141213387131441711521361517810911919381642131073156161415516294916171066171681332913611195101174131061163685212214771615111791216356521471337142137156495141017871391516432741211981765168512614121661316745152957417412621611514219811512159814425741461131610",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1082": {
    "question": "1612171054731711213412811121310651122154139475121713831516213121098156512171316281019151217141112795981378161510610514311431251015951711314154813115217141213101665312141210159488146331757172121391123161610317711143521371911211347351215911178141653131651131412361471321125144912513216481016712176129741726517152101426162118158934310166121171431514547649881112131710101363196821777351615141381521011516177511014131666",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1083": {
    "question": "57410291111743114111051851515121274161361711310142811151641354423159817144146131187158932516121731058127141591611212621281316179610654231371231614131171416213115163216101221610514121314381271617210311210109116512141494571163510151683171312916415512156115987414133163416842161541315104171371114311312513151714716910102314515731517101487131110319119171248311516310791410137171613107871012144161226979111311121429121685411613",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1084": {
    "question": "82111213913396721442155115131314941012171678143927151014161413176625991281154122159136171016711416169211131671141248616135101645111561614381017113712314141646621131311558910106169812213211217637915671431258713411328172143131577171231410159552114615115812111371334171659912141617106515161133111034152815111141271231015917715113431059546712147117141410111711148122938110162175710131167139111516144312123264191428716139105",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1085": {
    "question": "2171268111482811313101031115141371731495101321216511171361061712465911141131413123611015811152391674512108148911546121271517299611341614313558161287133910165617917161014143115358104141316131761171210465461214112101613532168210151191111131251714413361087173694159145161181264510376121113313131513141717387451231692104562169103921567624317101611431617143215107125151176129141412103612171478313516164127971531415461582",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1086": {
    "question": "5168410159121713137151176316107149115195121713361347435612817914821391011146116281016111171314169155358416241011547115917141089331711656451112139132193101411621011174155796212115314111171545688139155121051114142411613813125515131784346215149101611519861110163141513816126171251314211814391016131411317411515135816129102113151077931315812545114151091656248711012141233161563142132215935541212713814166151059117121412",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1087": {
    "question": "161024610121782111121415493471112121021718151410513711142101116615153547131416813641610914151412311514117149157161331244151127159151071316864165316182141217258141171591421610311048131323485161711712141091372163151781414110839612141415231714127101664131695116115581101431075949811531557813126481017145141131487142916491715101215125151048112126153157117514121715398101111151316141111216612941510111816101714171212115751617144286713",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1088": {
    "question": "4169151465131551111348137151612516139101341171712322101416111541695213115817421348842313611131410211769710122121412765136146331015431451121567971161145371771751410161221248512694101610613311141313111011721012313416121251571481117116141310852412345117161151497131131251105123646151112104461167839513154171711547101097231214137313151712513376163102114134791111032153816674161713573841214271149543578161528117127613112",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1089": {
    "question": "61321491610168121591171349412751621314115581161110167137158841439631423154141317816152971214516712214714421517110816710917621011163414131213122151141631411124171658510115142558413151211110119683151011477191312631615875123514125161711610714212138613121286511161151131210411912173414378251151013166515321116761317161589147161116158615291315111753811171211214283146415151114135181510971613163411612419610103141151011513417712",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1090": {
    "question": "91411116161012171613851115714151712162161582411111961431210515167431119711614137916214553612152131881061578101392151251711164111311615108178144974214661613815412132566101516117111215917316714712512181015105491321411981736291282616112351514694121314126141127916161368101716115483616177176112121545102135514121161110467153891548361011149131712210176541171516314826410171112531516612111151091414417141241039811127615531513816",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1091": {
    "question": "1171634391012351091317523811269111789174121341536812196513110131171511451110916764312410815421472176129105111315172136621778151114411131317791051641511161483179461412126931125148474116451513153101114111316171416165710391412456101261654118738171431034118156121679561325914174151610341091117141241010891671021538111711641410215771134141385135131214111826131217511931095715921148138673161011171411310134151465243115",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1092": {
    "question": "131410471652216861271151061073141216813211125177491911775151216171113136889121015131241163157812161121513529101671261411439113121612110233989153134171476416711121092141741459101515141521656121412299131443125131115616610101152178112173411116415132510641383115151731411615914127616291215775141341214212815172614114291567988133101191613279841298317125712174611132161411151031084561012131419731713152161122141696745111011162121",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1093": {
    "question": "9478971612310191711414145168721213411158111113613817411413152391215141571011612104121521014113161379104107161610126111421013913117213101615162914751214847172156178814111161034724112217153915481514632101169131534952171216611514916101218513164891241411612151511061635168616213421611121416101512136148417162574316112118810391551213914911125241761542316138102699171681311415131316151336411231715155510124816118213814111612924710123",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1094": {
    "question": "210115567821297310710161085212121716457151396139101011721613311656108912961615111289137410101611211712813116217442114212615155215915111831031291316121173639721614312654910139128310166152314116167414561135101115817112141627116131216915761116410144511916711310103134710148221313211437101311146112916141510713939428177125111241111810114851491314313813161047121561371051131214113174111194171275107253101121459417614911152133",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1095": {
    "question": "1146913161210161117618316127152171085113215941471417815716119711713123762146178154138912431016556141285987161117711415117313317411416257167151271181716214515167135141216102435361234141281021316141741681210879651110132516131091216672391411811651379610135131710125144533810111112681031410479171415128314115715121314161258179432113114914168681656213565143421171081091512791231047216141391617831312116126412959915310781011",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1096": {
    "question": "1010915514556785324817315487614131011151412131610741413151431771161581181246311912101471116411721555751410110311142129688998111012462216721315101214141064112169512131411143714231262111310104115131113111512214131316115310135671711531391581591077451261331915878126132111614741311561334122971711513142717164661214815591076116145172154151613191016128151053171354861291114689452111451316121711131613161614113101765141315131141",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1097": {
    "question": "611152111789121331671414109641010713151232135614152812514491013673271515125141351611381574111197368126163415215931171314851711161282815956838415622315761510316912161561781210215571741441361117532151731310716117121281347723981514611313854161011161296414717113211412108131414314134146135686931713116101772414111496376491116876321210121447161151651411315121141117103613710958612171471615145161369314144598581314151611126",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1098": {
    "question": "1626131211157510111498421717221064931611110811135741772111313837111161461598111541610816141239510111715141249139577157172881613416121351615117613141311125112121061416172931211761510615416135928166141211510714531721091666175121212911078111081110101514171447412952810131121271563121153714329516158171010612101381716815510102151112341131511911410317314286215157145113101746813151916106926131531374111416161681087171111154114135111081496",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1099": {
    "question": "141331389114391101567258916610119741522917138312167865561311617314941464632121711671031611415166291681713714579141236171013718163641691057999171215671621211810436252151239891024111414126167817412149616107152311110361514111641210541521511574156314816331491132210111114251371019831311146717103129413951012216611473710107171119149612481151314154851021741673892412151114161515327101211812594137110935426851712111614",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1100": {
    "question": "18761510955817247121216541279171031111021310515713716711126523121114151614812175146144110679101511541112131551751015716111211131359104321612114811731415151211914141312174516332791157131712151078414535271316161423178215151016125114461165891516154111017112332156521541215517371311111386151114161297131010516101123131271571411611110231787106115103912514629129811781611453172513106541316971191410131165881761038158391121524167",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1101": {
    "question": "7101114561115872129369131013144113164171101541612275156101101316811141217421612783154136171058912141121147125814101116217811684516104162539121111317915881391686211111443521711012471031314132815612161151531122611210815123791416916391141718151698102516177589161611223161521361414121557391337111748151371514101351271163959104216143212137156811016311151111316134126151214616291114981117394238513691412715416287416661341214615109",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1102": {
    "question": "521169131214528136131037232810114611165915101216103131211614852141221681913117101615169331241514162141471345216171037612794411267101431613981511514171712126131113981510161423151691612186616171321531471412710217912428515611115726694141011581713438128119141017161614631313161153131171529715141014416511316112514177941412841379105313116157161111510178817141315421131232210936516415137171613661410482116147854151611310911141716",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1103": {
    "question": "115102711388373611610161198121417141343652711016101614471517633611210138713111471276792395111610172103101767312358141121616612156212131514814161311910919141281015516211151713471711713538106159131124761576911135315112161315321737881221166101414951015929161131186124731617526553151616167413234161484151010111214157121281023441316117145148936381721661263913111210166768841510717816251114139714674817169101211414141559135",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1104": {
    "question": "816141351543101712953741317105941416719383512104922711617631210983715105168737121416124115913616111081671514916141216171348353696137411410177211171412916342161197107511104131063214165871513617934171514995131121161312131012101516314315137416119817615137129199571711312105574169214111731461141363751112113610346111571447139121098381215141411611665138111014291551684141212231417461282410115610162112395166158310131694157",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1105": {
    "question": "81281511615717214161449243611121516151511612141017310311225118101492351541362145872127451310115715101311111216414154179109786113151017881913662714313114114121315121352756149156112516161791313114121014838127414143691516111126101414161668917111216141212415142310674385319515121193571211156116171681321421169715361451585171247127193136111671517161015114761339213812146515516641091514712759481617111031151041114132121171299311178",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1106": {
    "question": "81641516131793817471121113417121591611971781145361131041214813112156171144374684121513531511516171363128137148131621691115151516741011321461745748414729166831713101587111381411127151721125613151191410111656121642839415915487510715137133326148122143631511131656141117248167111174610131511113851016313124159174128616212614310310874119131511614111341661310931181415973171146151541615713210313111361714114512181629101210",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1107": {
    "question": "524129716131628387171171161451211417153134656710142151093176111212135141387913141317979156114136102410215111071458361691610124556241421611581681031291016716146131543171244101710116156672144835122166131482152179210551411665121517110391211711421315121559526711410811714171317103614931015182712151611111217451315212516245631314172971615315511102146161411521068379513611161715811746211610217129514141112153313581414291610749",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1108": {
    "question": "8210161371197101415133112145613710104141651412892831511747412316662110511131113711513101719714769571293141065217111612415136212105910131010101871631517317161349157381346121414169123141412715715817514112103154213161482122751911116112431281112271116510613131611151652169412834714667144411610151513294181191083211153151111713172572151637614111011381712173368191215714131114810161412121021791311616104158471214151513210619358617164",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1109": {
    "question": "539921161317131512642812161116721013148131491646469916174121441081116147315178149642551110111641516104141411511712711131593216135103111517616976129581484631211114152381051621110629161138145915171541312155111635610116738141398615551154213181271613143814148216917161513161559210169151083121224141327515261789771115101612713116161651031071113241751571213751577151615149517321116717451331586614121611210111088121017161514111211021692",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1110": {
    "question": "11256127123416291216151025913178117109312846147144161581766321079157131231411171016914864161451517364114107131125178118656131710132148161714312141016101376431515103117141411139113541014817562121657111116158291714134310621776761638125135159811151151415132161196101774791131516121513147491571011171483713957191623141794112931061071413241112210171161021531698111214111158410165821164131661315175931512111481377101181639513",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1111": {
    "question": "18615612225126174210765694171688715131013121277151015283121619641116710910115421496126117783841017126911326151011633210511311161141172126741110121091471169114886481562147151691713513516121111141061241311410713515114171671129314108613613910154128499147131611155713256151335161115819102286171614247151017311611141315122411133659151012516171414211148101441343172791251053112210179101181581112146571776861269514415214213",
    "answer": "bwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1112": {
    "question": "791424161510131215165613712138107511281014591710131613451711212876513107141511176147516312923416815241010859231012576141967512131512111716161152814941015131722113657914368783634251117321161210813411381171411169531256281321541417711116121089671335142315169151317126471428159154121071148174141114151316210179410135661285516712761444511108153126381114104952312111161112314916613118144161247132197122111381561711421031",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1113": {
    "question": "9112511317197101228415615748141310161611151713693751351323115881612411169238121513161214192411712111216151459341217662118147149571617151515211451281613296111671241514281711337171151335113124715161016138141627101651617141314111241313118115923717631171873124216632151616514136143131615510112122717179112179234712126162131416151726114101118951137167104121116289372110614151371175410111217214834123141041149710853161410151732",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1114": {
    "question": "11691447126171166101012353174881516141224951210641014151213515126173111628511114176101131316214134135229111101261216682161374141781191559137103821213128176812179141331541105119813152312112521516746171651639141023134172149167851217541611610133915131698916111213153165713143410144101241721051315815516103127513961045168663151465138753329101014111712158121024816431611717796135927951411115578316131810312151351741312166117139",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1115": {
    "question": "851551781416499117821275988141112153256131617417162641556121231310914119151116121041451111628171081315764161285382141311910451512141713163610131445118214131071454111612113281211786621589417911162145612311967113129134171452410417148102131614681715912910217131498711145610412314814737171210132106551681561115163168141712151610161471495163132971104122171511438713978241711916411122153712169410514815126131141211514111448162101557612",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1116": {
    "question": "4512331315172291310515107215191627151051712634141115317912131110212144171416911366179138315121461215562418859141621317129351116141017715346131013121312127101715141041316121125123312154141151651212815917113142118131112591713157816411681711112813110111513859121321013213511134941461571181225175167143101061539101354162311141212115861725341012148315511551071034915710111213112814317141131612664141577173869121714101612438154613111328",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1117": {
    "question": "1776151016121513258161141481314157183315510162111017416132101617151141025941412124917128136102118158314711081134511171312102151413312121539131031481769111295616581351831561714791391461251023151071143913112124101241113516121526141767165149631112481111113515261010914617212441379121321214415214813101310317151161514912164757351128910179511421261415134617371012823167141041211121363915811132471615697413121410611431598931412106165410",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1118": {
    "question": "6726813111315413716126935142773164174161210812151231017216815101599131111316169543141084111267131521108611715210141215811167564111514161311781652127310917314111151341581267210147981275694131210143131538161311417951214941113861511723431681047121316191151637794516161461017111149312157561514912101624141252812223141415139131784121361212131793236111558112101341416231185681512151411122171691010358432111351491316146513810410112",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1119": {
    "question": "12113136921611210415715104521213101549761107171611321731511021461119131671362167412138119116513913656421113163552141711121541551125112312712511421713167121851768121014931121512916121732131051686410141543461416174137226931418141161315532310131631736216977415147111713512912101411732131216791179857121256210114176145113311715169108111788162510114161473117116693158310641101317411149571551211856176152913612453101215164",
    "answer": "wbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1120": {
    "question": "14112111101595712145104417136317217114165121651051513317111915169310412874151211457193417113661611117423168141511109751067214841114171612156125129317814691111146101512151311659137101187152815141712115144912697121315151621111471093172103254816141211461598111414121713391715285611433151174711161113109741510101651461115423321165913981772941115101151071715213121689391518161011216411117985138715161745111338310511461515142",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1121": {
    "question": "9103112123116121511711317141586451610141317951210337126171011591161511116841659116151315141756104316612398141112271013417955111102111316964810157144112113171412151386914331011111751367151253841621910135610109431752131121661217161531131561214941058512813225114210161014711157457141217211161315961241151012133161411151617972491413441310910121558861611339115156712415122111451571612157110239811713861491416177651113111210381124",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1122": {
    "question": "121498131216851061716121514371014141324162669168175312414107101611617125131312932415171513214951311461617158761112111321114310510676416599131481310141691510751722615331118614911162121331871614151391319175131612811912148462102161681791365615111487117132551416111014141817164121610143976168171622134513141416121012411591771314238155107841423166372101351112131116810151012413107163172631141077486312161415414816915173155331014174",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1123": {
    "question": "3811612513914101737761151253221794139821114317146714234101317131361287531316121169154151424736248511132127161105101523168935151154221412157813151010941472111211181116131041215149168155111317151461317141541616911156531210111014111017415912147210195819388212151571051331441731219105314688131181653271158156105491017214371315101291513841465111141411151015837171491114105418166714157571127312491741534211115721455813112",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1124": {
    "question": "1691713531621315971211414621413916177118101212155941131216674861245139121510101793631613135121291431414513149151114171256679437116154659241410517118515111281561164211141510716173492141552638817161413458916216141111131537171681075111515613915168261213112615914105110131612311715772161217106131174912515161217951641028147915211621147131210314141115816153149105104161513168211124714125105810153769416113317101031419341415158111352",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1125": {
    "question": "1364109716310914151125127711351416536178162181511103171814115113712116124142121555111571310131591741212101445971211171591116156871161117291312114109510121628962941241714157181661110271103169726141363101017111216151491513711152171312143842101585615916135761243141612151494133171241742251477111361541015978415123111716139217610177591115169264412165145797111086415710141616123115145361617234118812137113153671012498145221",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1126": {
    "question": "16251368121112135128141576311101516216312141781165111314145961615810371615171225841610853217121463314161247251779141061413115368414113141716616151111102311111317147141012763154313731751113415541612101311614105161617108115361311612481461214141157810162153961712168786124113152581694176483714129118716131651668741331079131017111791115157311681712414393101221491231413611528159107125715616846911214121451310410713798131165417166213",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1127": {
    "question": "10112161310971610831152118142471125815913716717211962128810411461615973158107141616115131159114101210321611111721012114391113171015857131627784611596851113128121631591414171216171215141197854151039742921046131119675103144593213121011410161317142911151791610711136311131414413679151394310217181141014121615515154416513138171411612133425717156108619411141017123151368111212131413114139143175141213751681751039248161311171216156",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1128": {
    "question": "16917141101516715864653219252164131510711411912711117551014510139832146151214815107811534118101369175151321015687111264141711410931524142133179611383511317756311294121610421616156165101739413147111381107987123645321511410121681617151111243914415446155921710151611081131158481392141266101617131715481123141166141710911815962861714413131015853917213645103141521101110164513612516381517102971131413417910151415112116327",
    "answer": "wwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1129": {
    "question": "1165391471113107117151248216131112154531416671761051210916814116178131021543131711611711235510961714111089715318516413144297131314111358112121741017151615178226911142523137111151012151651413112711451763698175131042312155713413515621516712814961011161251743967113118168131510723141181681517515661141191415101311125104121011068121491331617102318451411147101218641472119158169491116216715414101617312813314149111012127983151314173",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1130": {
    "question": "179311715244714551316105682211115117103612741515141510161197910368151712498161512101012517114761414151479141631262161715531081610151242655191317161271511110214111783614161486171331215589141610157101721162172133410681299113391631613121711647138621035187314710415139216655171010125119161417131643182127561661411141212331543281535161213112174811165149171116431549101635148713121314101576518111213396174131471131610118616169185",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1131": {
    "question": "171281312115515991671438213512161441417615109113181914161481511713171413164595111510117117141216141663216912109536128101113171339716154716135149217316162103161575141131481195716132111331648105415151761548531321291321259118141158710295634133168111127911551716714126842115145713812231431661449513151010811141791815736611412111810493516126884132163114961429751810111032181716515131391411124144141789141111357631115127",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1132": {
    "question": "5121564108321551013119621491549171471151493212484311914110516871313548977562134161431721014313611597671412852616111651084163161271513172151691486415733131155148221112810461651411121111531759162128101183178414613141510121317265816913137128167711481391417410155121014416451411101512287313414131112173161427146152934101073121415122149867812156111013241467161312815165108153456171631482121771510141061611921121831217",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1133": {
    "question": "215761414159531316151112414109637121615171121312111415613542178151412141143225151110842121513232161556248212771119171336131616143131192110510101113746158910315661310441611515121411714217511813415315109168811271596114131035128139145101316817982151261511181715101111108249141144316161241115212141471515814177136411031171067148122517166517168722586910613118217136115914161591111510214131451061679131711214123153876101414127174121631410",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1134": {
    "question": "1414102169151119461451211134165112847151391012791133211386161441013414713145915101212416761111614133143171361135984278151011210103416176131617511112141216912862131597513141313814931213101384975161696117881415721011537161612168179371762151314910161316121581014321513117125463733781312121314111716251510131145151173176216151214857210105141113216811391710621214137101113322106155961341110151593921214111615661275131612141471734215",
    "answer": "bwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1135": {
    "question": "2895111431211107141214173415923110111416121491136481415313516710114451481021513131610116161715162361497216137234512151513291151037151712412136761248106791610113129359161712146451014512111712168224139613467121739147381516126121411101787124921516514216614985615101710413117315113121375143521412101310151012116961481013311411517741711615795101416311107105215814211949101710131512312115159111032713717154141641012139111626121143105",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1136": {
    "question": "41111851746129141541128115771281710149113179642147512164467174137151373102614991511157213813121757411151761621131223381413146211176810591612510155516861114941231416121099111211510107158131121171316101134716814711817521569141761041531236121416277117616131141743510101981312368151515111316717113596383721312153171613141119415169154710117812831131451113717329212161551614771017121431318121021556716513129112175586119151031333",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1137": {
    "question": "171142412109167814513614151489101216112845111131366381171214216610811312121513458911131714163161268710269131456116123311104151710115156187131112147344256176110915729111548145911151415978112781611121311710923556134846796614371614141241795811161059131412617941111057151416118949713131514310122317121113141916106549127153447101275141315114863171489135161312215119714131016171381211161748113159221316101451599941516361116510118",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1138": {
    "question": "381399171225442108118711316412517121412391072115821485981116110841361417414991611411154152631015917131616102812118815281596547143810115151313614213131715371615121661110851511391571051291613171141347410171215141691215311141691637112924831514717891112141216761725162341113132101211111349674211457113111031586851771213104121015510214131177109168311123134151691387671114312171691166143457132183610485431612111091217131341415",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1139": {
    "question": "61061615214851121513221611591116711215118316621051315149131132911338312614713117310616316917158181231481011649171011136111374381216661551312371484141691391513531866121017141614136175121513111153213718231054161381021714216138691211813310714851241562171612171368831615710135169391013617891655213314997128238917101671411574131164715941617721213102148131121613917358141085121332171318141215691121775169354129211313761417107158",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1140": {
    "question": "112538167141265136151342111341241114715931731614131614174913361112111521017414161151133192914381310113212871596941321411758131314916125161116894316102145126141113133616848568111061412162741291371257517515410101631122762681334910161551371521214117472151483139179151715111610426131011412981371517811987134111012317103562161433811317541516161311147681511126110168141045112616531517136241211171261079169111117613121415451543",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1141": {
    "question": "425147614115394124101781351269951210411311842921141331213151665621714177117581314714611981581169101446175762431311111510310106151397712286174141811451616791115314613915272121410118151591361345161110310815101514174147166145141678111102172163414136154133114616136141011265613111481061721412151459471211717514741514111346157171568421241391051115637146851095173161015521278713111781421854216128198159214161611513774511010",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1142": {
    "question": "22121711015531416996165111751463710112121416714115813151014112165126321112171011434171167146713910851312611181414410251615177136172146113111215167510941431471481253169622131173115121191316148811446133971398114612516104173411614161651212115378614911024101625913311172711146266113381451041610151221677314791042175513133121011121616121011914211313131212517895124614111315171413215167151013161713216121115106410432117138156116123591510",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1143": {
    "question": "631361741121012143151169813151115125176472141658911211915814121173158136816116716141441513811386121771424581511031569511710911127101551112911363111546281649101516615814112133514139134412237111081561215251261481715214712941437813286115181211911151031012816129151041711487131217161091215181112158492108146115231211115917110177416171159146131021251915251071131181141283314161771615251151546699111312141281543171316143974212136",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1144": {
    "question": "978146752129113810341751159133151081051121451616142961011475171215156133721617111129131138291371313111614895461037178161583951017131216914151315762410174121131171571434210111312329516151012166111421171364669131178111614101116131416148531381215896911610166127146211217158117511157163611216451721561048816172119141351221010131563156139345512217216121714310511612941387176127381011128569451212915416111071341310214135",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1145": {
    "question": "61111514171055316251398111512105817142713591013781171241617178121511106213431315131111611415178121279714112610101113351643581512133141441210521710211151261016157881539714812545823661127224101314815151615101131226121221191081451484521715121513141114675101121161713448925381411115814104649215137816331110811839105615711614111221628115153314914171110651718131437631015911593122581678115112691647714161791351514211516971321016",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1146": {
    "question": "1517116113155792612354141048910128515251675613119131110121711314412612684721061111613171581114991271312549951016139141613851361121610112151546143121681611102513141717541251214109126243138311158841111521145712251721013111317561169615710122815161412117965714815142111125316104781411171419616910716212310134711781213171411373101058961641521246101611291594121752147111141441351082610216111721556412161425712481113104",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1147": {
    "question": "5171211151410164141212713361125812846131613161591714166711161561513173849785126164771431211122171391553161413161713112768104224787121521516117891463131171510122111487241463215939141710115416151057278621711514112128983571413816841115710561213511621512489713366101477117912147656491747101521617111369731610142316155107321361110151016163131015411741416148179105116161514121102571516961761349121113161110101598513814332121",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1148": {
    "question": "71714142128311166411346815103115216121129141361517711510156613118172597541013111171612515101114211268910916121215261348313781591613115217106111154141117621084147611112625181371414613144129159152811712427711105171513121691121182119151634712161614110310181143101261017791116131111128915914216152171051322751711561048912313111036541611216161388141174261144312715161451210171211143613410111251361588251141217713101101521034121671",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1149": {
    "question": "108141751541151917136129451769710311151231211113161211161315145139481021634810101413161211311211515347111611913158127171013147361531714612146213111091015755147411101113812628121710921295146101218716211141612171133171141551197128161031241421167141513296172112109171145867451399613151612635162396431014147161291179841312651021091351210716154617862111313185141191646175212742153131310916717751151628249131416426710781535114",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1150": {
    "question": "8151741258121335111414141141973314169141015151752583715410715412131916116152123131197159164103151611122110158226171479932614153161745311451012694231014711253121591126410311415614215127861613175131510617128121515141168411295184149617167315213912541115712417111471313245231391613111361712415315137181710121410122316164641099131165111681231512104971626123651410711615121051457117102161159341611411611151359161414257",
    "answer": "bwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1151": {
    "question": "81331115921181721216129113131161513171437113956121310763456161728161014131135104163111325916115122512155131411744162615193177111110821431581212136119151722111311585110141614486104917414112128581171516131161416216812511715171331510151010161497111312164510114315141798610728131174615963254412171515915691131621537913811041114111175216131221217481615615141110191114616710913231511121175132415121056914161743131174121514111613586121541763512",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1152": {
    "question": "1713310112872149365415716310651371763112799161653143371268479151691710814510791661574141113422161512335755611718131369811271575610416951416127168325139661441031171510664151151731942716721311165173101153137291191212517158821651011314166311676610912141351317911513679131411191514231010810129161114231712881631610138151198147161391279217581128131036141788511516911591418412712171015763163294111215910515148131",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1153": {
    "question": "510162172155114961615451251721581114151311611912431685513431627171513166517914645112231691161116151371412101161159521711136142151065117121381317116546811171291049131551614172715681359957111102111116111210716715499311514131710131365361174145879151264121316127153115710941641312261514101176133139451029712106131614138415419117417141116845141413216141416313513811102611616791275101582316216488111413611311781141213932213",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1154": {
    "question": "123241211481071713946411168513212109158111675810748136815176151521012167612153648131617657181414281271152614914781251571314141211481783796161581441178117151358112921634581116131661214169151617448761151491112164512172510213671631261410141215789111171014871310122111415155514216817111071321214672915695571310313642111412797161410157108264216111218510761414113917111210312169154143125112155141010171610115179891645153312116",
    "answer": "bwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1155": {
    "question": "7116101458827111441549673218171411410954114372111345468717133314991111451521216551717911116614910133111078152145171917412127101233131171614416161451441112131471111812651011111268159161843132147217814104151493121312512510714151613410125161284101476511291315517134712141351411962101116112216131512315514128414116141091314121144261416735104151275115106951312177111686715281221571015569131415171064129121610211851724121011513",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1156": {
    "question": "385107167178661613214517585413517151691431213676115171581610286384121343618216511915561410411411942178812123715164131597165147151256168210351510213638271711291215316113154136291147168171110817914584714421616613512131581441224179155141716310116159410163741378817610156121613711851431219421237941161761310111310151517141781392133571078511165121738163211521310147981416553710147131721011101171312910131682141110537",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1157": {
    "question": "821414312971516102547717861342127101241161516913131712761519581662106374867137298691516112171511122871644176236171031751711715712128111491011121115913210846351813171693410812416158176107413991613139831617415231211151496517131114107249714164152121587106111144159177512129112417132161135151665998152164177101611612317147101216679615141311221611741151412681613171391262617779156913510105881412102376784161215517131092",
    "answer": "wbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1158": {
    "question": "13110141072124849611151714610121311014735277416141114961284811131417122101516151781516561611446941310411124146131171681678515256111241315141216117341671078161512315171264141386813329121617861211109141351251412415111589517131512101316106151521314517938129415141561417416321281691121415131984914103611211217172911139101514815315712281415141627102991375171512241171511391016121421186137554217144614101611133939148101713411126151721115",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1159": {
    "question": "15145987131129516217410112131413410177121511793511174516122110131491261548921610169423876131217381212241105311114966115155171113101291498211164471421741611552136101521294861131011117169151112102161713531511159297178141010161231127101461672951121154114916261421016868711715791321517106356741131314981612793212111014113106131615121726814111713512921010441517791106131216101411831211198786101652141613313102814141617104311493106",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1160": {
    "question": "81311143101231817411415651121281544101411541765276451016131438915101423101317111514243271113169581137151241768613241412193839101711101374751231413271415491536325148131217121061314891472102101216543121678121731631412514131161021314821213997155171211871349121683651715611241251121513103179181665266126311131713147341412153171414116915627416131081591310521611146109711134148819121744132641123141087933714111641210172135",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1161": {
    "question": "141392315156176411148102710216682713711131689121581131526131461116125731713121021216910136147135246157911141439171082121613101058109147642161151715852101311101216151461671178311111731486416112101571011314169413510513810151721211131386161581216171610239416141594361611138171615521148107161116155591239161417116410131391012371317156161341531013121117162131101635138414175714161412151081314911214810124216151171611636616151727791616481014",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1162": {
    "question": "1151736822515941216413143571591211161124101615714823111661329416417157410810691595111272316211591471172610161515115841112106151510131741011312518213161041012314715651469210961081659498135159211121291396811651410173151124611141295310614137816109171215211183141412101171065910161661468135414114173615817127815923986105616125118151210992121441171719785101117212461691411131683710141545311711171298162121115714149133184101176",
    "answer": "wbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1163": {
    "question": "715814111714212101161662496447315151551311291621413128133141210617115459128614411211516132610151217310151531221216411714319566131098216256101216210742543117943116481714617129178101013144161068111211596143587331041513310128151189151415483131062741611179513151121417385101514142713494717108161611191516126124101587171411138171061543839711111581251315411661121417986151243131627101316151129812123141779158114141761313133101610",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1164": {
    "question": "17149412451311174216141112106131048161121393816514125541419382156613323161412811161771513114101021189297513410631413111415867101615122617101451629135151581721261537101171214133211638177141111555161623159121614498101748187151231476786571810911155141151115587161091326135291615121111413533121016171096413215121813177141513146815813311129121112171326141710126516757138143411165137417815431211714829611731108141512745167115",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1165": {
    "question": "831811118715761711169106111438121487961251741013165912437817115161111814811614151331011115127115416171351191546151210871108341367813912131711416251121311141616121341011326177910512126417194321115913882128111716863512141271591662171237795349714151171714128161621015413213710161581171712141313123714171023155169491513111012879171313161557128161410421516135941015817977231412114161312101412511915373810749310155131471778111052",
    "answer": "bwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1166": {
    "question": "125111461341587161122435111310978276312414162515156121575131541185610161275291510118168936136144414617121510161411116139131072916161397714164581010151715167461494110321012891313341416285244111511712816141511374214595812116815147166332122994131711631011141551041111287313158121017166111161454471212164561217169127157101448310121634615285117147931129121616351171310211556857131381231417661521316414981352141613386841715714",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1167": {
    "question": "142311131012412461615913175111911341614122461217147321014714916541212121111528752121217136519161110633175161371516968716119841011117111615121591581328147311135281589111716141616613451758111035117712121112121714169151410131032151111413153312510125251761171651610971417382121115136210147887517161115512339117154411101411137312518167731514133131111612211110381623311471241214959515531596821311741215101710148961224112155674161",
    "answer": "wwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1168": {
    "question": "4121071023131463161159165428111789101314153121316151611171281316981112421131015163312614515810914612161410251443171314961267814111310716536842178661591231611125101266714115149815631515114168121310211715111376158514791611101282312177711159314105913615115111421631651275134615101113310841215313676146314391011151227118171641417612141312417316111591410210984691211615513133171026511111916811131310171510231691410171547510691185",
    "answer": "wbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1169": {
    "question": "6151621761374812161246313168527142815461111119131716131214471491113106511513712151310855122415171121066410910101210319814210131552144815516121771194121395168133310617141512712692310102941112121613811157151310131669111314147162535143612101721613157121164113582141316141051512412227110951316741715162151335127711411891651113616141017210999112118761131517141244111216121715162310143147176177951161316421410121553139173112105851119155714",
    "answer": "bwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1170": {
    "question": "141311115105162881553714324148413331112111491521017112411591281657316126142671091810127511021616141616931121413713101711135963145216813121471278911314159171262109115481014371681221511101761415610912138132212315513141668917416917122134819863111310835710414910462121310171415121012139721617141668516312981461071711144158131418724171623161516141289511917111321614154153216121571071513171142931613473118151114144241210117921334",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1171": {
    "question": "9317213212896551141446151212108171618513714121613267106143616481549121395124148152841049171413116715111597112614131010178281710313111616151161211210789211131108363917167514141356515161677141216717912131521241665101563811614111168971271051381415364316141512515111349171636816612121141710741148115139476101343156610127231431745613152148119121741413161511039311211131651271281413731531713104613117932683916141141112131141017",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1172": {
    "question": "2173787914331163114101610372313619108512811515175296101611101412157685411782171431051241616283124537813410151613176241081342717531611967341101071334161415164591211163915411151571781216261310991751110121513414613141381615141161512386113823121785821051712341016782114131121063115121311314171661541463158813132710154177111551234161081742133169141569813541713332101214116616811010111514121517155167241514171225716812114141034",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1173": {
    "question": "682615116915511131061016215561647101871716581231625141112381311106151334917971113101521681192315122691611215113612141771010514361371216917112108151971641281516171491351113138321213172111013513415861691411113156169162101389155327101128812316121391125474514101258631421071661713316101679721286168411131541712841315147327139621210415867151713514113211161328153171612719962714914217131645281215110147711914431510111161716213438",
    "answer": "bwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1174": {
    "question": "41727123114149810911215611514159168743151116912913101412119653381611171081111411831612151222714416151017161115310815142164136712151151225426156516813910371310447515121161131728610916515101110710192374313151711816221112451091316545155142910118738131731013161481781641541113325617154113861371211210141112104114526113138976392215148112161061113317164557651710113931541012111216111654131716126139314237871157613931413176127165",
    "answer": "wwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1175": {
    "question": "1041971172158121196316251383148131171621615411101110491512171316613141313728291116415621393121762166145139381117110814811497161681114313139541217112813114961611108113315121512244104171357913117161611101171535712961314821116831732712271116569947171115691110145315413148211452413112119107817399157815151517101612101946173362111082116615157515715121665398817111010111516212175211114141096103145811229911151410472112",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1176": {
    "question": "814572628491612391417813810111213496221714168716210941413615115171283121103461161071591614813141516519141416111159115102451315671212171461051641114391615881311014517941110621111691110136124713658431417116161313101012651072248410872231139141791161217131511152126851076116553117121581610521191371427131689116421136515311761512105109221111158161261716341911121614815121101379111216171287146151321583841129155413113111616114106",
    "answer": "bwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1177": {
    "question": "9148109111317641291416261181331621343146712916177171145151641211296101482127113946811214151514121281016127791741369161195114107161521129121442653151649121631015118101151713933122613139571781416105413451511683115158812316715161610142161085173385131717113991064165513117149316131024122175271613861144210115138121648139481485815710910213471611117121511581461611731121047101627164816782115312171512210111712157173613891115",
    "answer": "wbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1178": {
    "question": "4103622512179271181615121613149167941012101486137211121591611354103328171465910165121551617713211810521037164101415817621913101713101216141315117516122131363413782161521129101414161015827910121016814518814151017159614231245471015312761768271512114752341361514171651019121411161727313191636116101510124613131841125781151410171281416219321141112746141715485751112141391217111215121611735614131113817112151875841211316176111413213",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1179": {
    "question": "139151531134141325161210371217132816101611141236964216141087312851348915811121512411482173416136675116612119213111910144271417831328712246111105159124101161315161117432141081331211617159141271481671131049151310396171171516161211147161214981210511151213917617105714391271761123159132111128151761084631431015838514123966147134210613154514153114711716261214410112715159884231151062213151561611131216143111121664615857117288",
    "answer": "wwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1180": {
    "question": "1069416311571051813111615102965921615312141215146116121014310152131141317397147131116149611165127151515967101248123411617144516381214815113917161147225913171676111412451521310215114122643101076611129745131011217515621091431313817132314164159121536101415197416911514310121771161248315131215144616615155143125616417231011287916351015131475112891018116101525511121886439172913269101714165811563142116151714531619114710412",
    "answer": "bwwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1181": {
    "question": "1061813111415173163261289691021035161312118951451436151284551311102119168124616141317361195914279141510101316316157128141710512591464171413717131215167101011911671012685171543145136102123121416171115857467211014158161241035166111416514153101271771314111114151671775963121316121119101871431416112155491710612112162410811141421721345431581153121410497614271331107159510157274613128411145899131131621512610961712139215481411016133",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwbbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1182": {
    "question": "1656817311141210159781421414139161491317111310115131517104118139159916144821215134414615711977831231963119413102641515521771515167812165151310171114921612713151116737151221171171081315316567111712169712107634514341579111610191677153547141138103131214311127231115481661345101411161073871093217161584191012917111421687415131614493111310105714215161316311717141410121316165743167913910563814163121611154111517651393106251312848",
    "answer": "wwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwbww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1183": {
    "question": "3151610511104121214681213131012104615311141817913951226161131131354597101099145381469925111131114717138614124101513675171179316276311212898165616106116935151351024121565111475129514581410311151823481792151151391210468717161315163105121471511214119211171549101714613121611242133177151171391281569127171010681311414631610111217107137711868195101544128141714361541614592741063161249137112115176813166111016271284837135",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1184": {
    "question": "11610915101312142127521117913611811110524161015141113310813121016411159215814611317926314372912151348127111221441510377511188161154415511210101713762110121491314161115763415657921714114574105118385151141051626131416313141113191216212956581315134314121716671042141011493115714161833710813952212111713413103710152891141713511133146645827178151091114153435795111231261610613152101716412316458979105816171117126121471391116",
    "answer": "bwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwbwbbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1185": {
    "question": "213121961011151314641716111442611121293516110613117113916514129101549817113210141151315815152561710139851567169111051621353128178791210631631012411312551011143151134978121226161131611811742261219491517431516284131015111659714111612689121451313275113129155716141146123510913101511221617143144213621416261743587111415122410131317168121131410211125231511921512101642671711318105116143175811283151416713431275151452106816996111",
    "answer": "wbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwbbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1186": {
    "question": "4171764157916531211271361515721271051017131661343164851731621568571151312115163171031710134101481271017514116415149111381412151951115161131411646771131777172111571310141324859169131051826110141615935111713119101141215712132851571113269381721215101411613215710781012537176161214171268191241671314615115151111218310168107611151295152161017114141810111211541164812411172571514126278107415211110312895116641431215151361316122510115",
    "answer": "bwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1187": {
    "question": "716323105451711512111915147175116112131511811121013812510158141716121154101616151263108113211143117105111399112173493101611657281615171315315651511512110113151710911712941656151315107151511185713171143161249612911515634141452416761013122659115817151314711157115141351710688152376161117515814331321391517161531416436497513526127310161292991447148121161081461121611105153717826171496511710159106311382131141131712156255133738",
    "answer": "wwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwbbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwbw",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1188": {
    "question": "855101017154121116491133125161546141041757131116112165314181510141716121471115132116126135133847101471715315131461814162173123466154961714127431315816106381112101356911168179216114761581577115914173151415131315751615836111313149117127111131618149145213321091141531210131210141061617561791621134129671138814111441031516125632158139171610613641712378133210151111111913211103116171357617113127941316241813104112416312106121113981351286",
    "answer": "wwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwbbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwb",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1189": {
    "question": "91147134141481172261751514149418371510151210616910171115347134151431623611217515151087615431148131015168102671416171151112431617106516111414188151639156311151641613171221891161445131213172687911152761231641051566177131413112178723102161119634571141653174911158103147110121211611015165357981348141436144166124151316789413271311214148513154111103119158872115101613117155313741215106151161121158161354516811784101211314137210",
    "answer": "wwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwwbwbbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbbwwbwwwwbwwbwbwww",
    "size": 17
  },
  "1190": {
    "question": "12111413108201018618103161551091191212161175336171184206972616208256171191887124414181016141012520861891928151711811758921967251712101619141613201151255416714167148261512816111814141112179161388101191771818206171548994122017131411318316231931617161241434156179202316131485716151036132114139108111613209131017911141862119855271212101318205310121173191615291374161868115213941636175161482017241491818191123716513101741519610124121819151381412720131119631216165316181017871512101112133892101858152414118163139914661917111920131673101415658421124461572262010172113812161552112113641019147182013175319128515",
    "answer": "wwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwwbwbbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbbwwwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwww",
    "size": 20
  },
  "1191": {
    "question": "7101611292314141719441317131551111813199821751573493111116169196117161423201151211154183141056911128171748188151412191318212041197171351151915710121128181118124171520117141119181326318191711133161822015732138192117112948103151414913122131819261820610165201159918196106117131231745148113412711169111719351619112477151161912112194161018209118531756511151981811231510103139131059182041018161071261212873191431821651213191611201110817741712019417816191961781674111121318111219281891419171119152051086141919171341231215101411815824516716117184314771513109617192122715121431941017172016118149127813316810210410163181981712126220",
    "answer": "wwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbbwbwwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwbwbwwwbbwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 20
  },
  "1192": {
    "question": "71511115313161317518127141684611697819214132204121058151665201111713358915101316113641568613315417191041882875201010741117151121913101665161923715141188211911620461117101317712121141786101851917317157213481416551318119157111914147692616438183111472131222010106134151915159141921091661471314172135151219212201261071816511814191411317421641017118315141610510992017191318141681812157113932019617515115716461161018143131519191020811192015316917211101241618152691104156751371817214149181032120717111220414131655131111051223179913141371741101911158121718361662011178715912103191541415421851816121417181818191391320121215813",
    "answer": "bwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwwbwwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwwwwwbwbwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbbwwbwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwwwwbbwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwb",
    "size": 20
  },
  "1193": {
    "question": "172141020101319613114151681513112181274832013915141715101072181916620121241018191710713713281551795518101261019410171814142016913811811121353212419161441716151371918131175271117141011121314732046312071841121512113917181051479125414311161517101849681228110161698661920193218111810213742710151817127818111341951914142011121669158113419185758841861913113622075911217141098161911768131498252411317141611191121320131115191614531781149517106133139214110671918161415191319121417115181419316518720122910131317313171931041112161663810145189146147191381831215216531159101515513161414218311819921461717101810201812415131151716194131611416",
    "answer": "wwwbwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwbwwbwbwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwbwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwbwwwwbbwwwwwwbwbwwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwb",
    "size": 20
  },
  "1194": {
    "question": "15251611181614181320179171019161331311323621813121412195418101891541020438141913946113742121651151761853854111610142132019127131884162010101151917814395121724161241010520159149171781644119853414121111320215112141781916144122021119110517128161115651875143814612154109181017203211118941057111616613171312919172081415161135317214144431013121219132017419141712318816131511116916206201912759164121116181731176101385610181213411191731525811014958109131827114315820165121481064126171315751141711171914187515117179561413911061449201118119184119101719671941621154137121713236159101520356181244714117318201511176196101212141639113",
    "answer": "bwwbwwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwwbwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwwwbwwbwwwwwbwwwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwbwwbwbwwwwbwbwbwbwwwwwwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwbwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbwwbwbwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwwwwbbwwwbwwbwwbwwwbwbwwwwwwbwbwwbwwbwwwbwwbwbwwwwwwbwwbwbwbwwbwbwwbwbwbwwwwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwbwwbwwbwwbwbwwbwwwwbwwwwbwwwwwbwwwwwbwbwbwbwwbwbwbwwbbwbwbwwwbwwbwbwbwwwwwbwwwwbwwbwwwwwwbwbwwwwbwbwwbwwwbwwbwwwwbwbwwwbwwwbwwbwwbwbw",
    "size": 20
  }
}